<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Root>
  <AllLanguage>
    <Language N="EN" BaseLanguage="True">English</Language>
    <Language N="CH">中文</Language>
    <Language N="FL">Flag</Language>
    <Language N="MX">未知</Language>
    <Language N="TH">未知</Language>
  </AllLanguage>
  <Describes>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The 360DV configuration failed because OBD was not connected.</EN>
      <CH>360标定失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_360Cali_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La configuración 360DV falló porque OBD no estaba conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่า 360DV ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The 360DV configuration calibration failed because of an unknown error.</EN>
      <CH>360DV配置标定失败,原因为：未知错误。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_360Cali_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de configuración 360DV falló por un error desconocido.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบการกำหนดค่า 360DV ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดที่ไม่รู้จัก</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The 360DV configuration calibration failed because: aborted or not started.</EN>
      <CH>360DV配置标定失败,原因为：终止或未启动。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_360Cali_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de configuración 360DV falló debido a: cancelada o no iniciada.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบการกำหนดค่า 360DV ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากถูกยกเลิกหรือไม่เริ่มต้น</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The DCU Yaw rate calibration failed because normal stop exception.

</EN>
      <CH>360DV配置标定失败,原因为：常规停止异常。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_360Cali_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de Tasa de viraje DCU falló debido a excepción de paro normal.

</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบอัตราการส่าย DCU ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อยกเว้นสำหรับการหยุดตามปกติ

</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>360DV configuration calibration failed, reading the calibration result was a calibration failure</EN>
      <CH>360DV配置标定失败,读取标定结果为标定失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_360Cali_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de configuración 360DV falló, la lectura del resultado de calibración fue una falla de calibración</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบการกำหนดค่า 360DV ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการอ่านผลการปรับเทียบล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Calibration triggered successfully.</EN>
      <CH>标定触发成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_360Cali_Out1</FL>
      <MX>Calibración activada con éxito.</MX>
      <TH>การกระตุ้นการปรับเทียบสำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>1. Calibration trigger is successful, please follow the screen prompt for calibration operation; 2. The diagnostic instrument can be disconnected.</EN>
      <CH>1.标定触发成功，请按屏幕提示进行标定操作；2.可以断开诊断仪。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_360Cali_Success</FL>
      <MX>1. Disparo de calibración exitoso, por favor siga el aviso en pantalla para la operación de calibración; 2. El instrumento de diagnóstico se puede desconectar.</MX>
      <TH>1. การกระตุ้นการปรับเทียบสำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปฏิบัติตามคำแนะนำบนหน้าจอสำหรับการดำเนินการปรับเทียบ; 2 เครื่องมือตรวจหาข้อบกพร่องอาจถูกปลดออก</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ABS online configuration failed because: failure to clear fault code.</EN>
      <CH>ABS在线配置失败，原因为：清故障码失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ABS_OnlineCon_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de ABS falló debido a: falla en borrar el código de falla.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ ABS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการลบรหัสข้อบกพร่องล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ABS online configuration failed because the after-sales server could not be accessed.</EN>
      <CH>ABS在线配置失败，原因为：无法访问售后服务器。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ABS_OnlineCon_Fail10</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea ABS falló debido a que no se pudo tener acceso al servidor post-venta.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ ABS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าถึงเซิร์ฟเวอร์หลังการขายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ABS online configuration failed because OBD was disconnected.</EN>
      <CH>ABS在线配置失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ABS_OnlineCon_Fail11</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de ABS falló debido a que el OBD estaba desconectado.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ ABS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก OBD ถูกปลดออก</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ABS online configuration failed because failed to read the online configuration.</EN>
      <CH>ABS在线配置失败，原因为：读取在线配置失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ABS_OnlineCon_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de ABS falló debido a que falló en leer la configuración en línea.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ ABS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถอ่านการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ABS online configuration failed because write failed.</EN>
      <CH>ABS在线配置失败，原因为：写入失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ABS_OnlineCon_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de ABS falló debido a falla de escritura.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ ABS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเขียนล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ABS online configuration failed because security access failed.</EN>
      <CH>ABS在线配置失败，原因为：安全访问失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ABS_OnlineCon_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de ABS falló debido a falla de acceso de seguridad.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ ABS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเข้าถึงระบบนิรภัยล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ABS online configuration failed because failed to enter the extended session.</EN>
      <CH>ABS在线配置失败，原因为：进入扩展会话失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ABS_OnlineCon_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de ABS falló debido a que falló en ingresar la sesión extendida.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ ABS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าสู่เซสชั่นแบบขยายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ABS online configuration failed.</EN>
      <CH>ABS在线配置失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ABS_OnlineCon_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de ABS falló.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ ABS ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ABS online configuration failed because VIN confirms failure.</EN>
      <CH>ABS在线配置失败，原因为：VIN确认失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ABS_OnlineCon_Fail7</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de ABS falló debido a que el VIN confirma la falla.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ ABS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถยืนยัน VIN ได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ABS online configuration result upload failed.</EN>
      <CH>ABS在线配置结果上传失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ABS_OnlineCon_Fail8</FL>
      <MX>Falla de carga de resultado de configuración en línea de ABS.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ ABS ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ABS online configuration failed because the car does not need online configuration or there is no car information on the server.</EN>
      <CH>ABS在线配置失败，原因为：该车无需在线配置或服务器上无该车信息。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ABS_OnlineCon_Fail9</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de ABS falló debido a que el vehículo no necesita configuración en línea o no hay información de vehículo en el servidor.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ ABS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากรถไม่จำเป็นต้องทำการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ หรือไม่มีข้อมูลของรถอยู่บนเซิร์ฟเวอร์</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ABS online configuration was successful.</EN>
      <CH>ABS在线配置成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ABS_OnlineCon_Success</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de ABS fue exitosa.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ ABS สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The online configuration of ABS has been uploaded successfully. Please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>ABS在线配置结果上传成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ABS_OnlineCon_Success1</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de ABS se cargó con éxito. Cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ ABS สำเร็จแล้ว ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Automatic clutch communication malfunction!
Repair suggestion: please check the wiring harness, connector, insurance of the automatic clutch module, or replace the automatic clutch module.</EN>
      <CH>自动离合器通讯故障！
返修建议：请检查自动离合器模块相关线束、接插件、保险，或者更换自动离合器模块。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>¡Falla de comunicación de embrague automático!
Sugerencia de reparación: verifique el arnés de cableado, el conector, el fusible del módulo de embrague automático, o reemplace el módulo de embrague automático.</MX>
      <TH>การทำงานผิดปกติของการติดต่อสื่อสารกับคลัตช์อัตโนมัติ
คำแนะนำการซ่อม: ตรวจสอบชุดสายไฟ, ขั้วต่อ, ฟิวส์ของโมดูลคลัตช์อัตโนมัติ หรือเปลี่ยนโมดูลคลัตช์อัตโนมัติ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failed to store learning value;
Repair Suggestions: 1. Repair and re-study; 2. Replace the automatic clutch module;</EN>
      <CH>存储学习值失败；
返修建议：1、返修重新学习；
2、更换自动离合器模块；</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Falla en almacenar el valor de programación;
Sugerencias de reparación: 1. Repare y vuelva a programar; 2. Reemplace el módulo de embrague automático;</MX>
      <TH>การบันทึกค่าที่เรียนรู้ไว้ล้มเหลว;
คำแนะนำการซ่อม: 1. ทำการซ่อมและเรียนรู้ค่าอีกครั้ง; 2. เปลี่ยนโมดูลคลัตช์อัตโนมัติ;</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EOL check failed;
Repair Suggestions: 1. Repair and re-study; 2. Replace the automatic clutch module;</EN>
      <CH>EOL校验失败；
返修建议：1、返修重新学习；
2、更换自动离合器模块；</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Falla de verificación EOL;
Sugerencias de reparación: 1. Repare y vuelva a programar; 2. Reemplace el módulo de embrague automático;</MX>
      <TH>การตรวจสอบ EOL ล้มเหลว;
คำแนะนำการซ่อม: 1. ทำการซ่อมและเรียนรู้ค่าอีกครั้ง; 2. เปลี่ยนโมดูลคลัตช์อัตโนมัติ;</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Query learning results failed;
Repair Suggestions: 1. Repair and re-study; 2. Replace the automatic clutch module;</EN>
      <CH>查询学习结果失败；
返修建议：1、返修重新学习；2、更换自动离合器模块；</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>Fallaron los resultados de programación de consulta;
Sugerencias de reparación: 1. Repare y vuelva a programar; 2. Reemplace el módulo de embrague automático;</MX>
      <TH>การสอบถามผลการเรียนรู้ค่าล้มเหลว;
คำแนะนำการซ่อม: 1. ทำการซ่อมและเรียนรู้ค่าอีกครั้ง; 2. เปลี่ยนโมดูลคลัตช์อัตโนมัติ;</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure in learning!
Re-construction suggestions: 1. Re-study;
2. Replacement of automatic clutch;</EN>
      <CH>学习失败！
返修建议：1、重新学习；
2、更换自动离合器；</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_GearFail1</FL>
      <MX>¡Falla en programación!
Sugerencias de reconstrucción: 1. Vuelva a programar;
2. Reemplazo de embrague automático;</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าล้มเหลว!
ข้อเสนอแนะสำหรับการทำซ้ำ: 1. เรียนรู้ค่าอีกครั้ง;
2. การเปลี่ยนคลัตช์อัตโนมัติ;</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Put the gear in</EN>
      <CH>请挂</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_GearTip1_1</FL>
      <MX>Por favor conecte </MX>
      <TH>เข้าเกียร์ </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>, keep your hands stay away from Shift Lever and click OK.</EN>
      <CH>，挂完后手离开换档手柄，踩脚刹，点击“确认”</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_GearTip1_2</FL>
      <MX>Después de conectar, deje la manija de cambio y dé clic en "Confirmar"</MX>
      <TH>หลังจากเข้าเกียร์แล้ว ให้ปล่อยคันเกียร์แล้วคลิก "ยืนยัน"</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>For the first time</EN>
      <CH>第一次</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_GearTip2_1</FL>
      <MX>Por primera vez</MX>
      <TH>ในครั้งแรก</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>failure in study, please hang up</EN>
      <CH>学习失败，请挂</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_GearTip2_2</FL>
      <MX>falla en programación, por favor conecte</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าล้มเหลว โปรดเข้าเกียร์</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN> keep your hands stay away from Shift Lever and click OK.” </EN>
      <CH>挂完后手离开换挡手柄，点击“确认”</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_GearTip2_3</FL>
      <MX>Después de conectar, deje la manija de cambio y dé clic en "OK"</MX>
      <TH>หลังจากเข้าเกียร์แล้ว ให้ปล่อยคันเกียร์แล้วคลิก "ตกลง"</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>自动离合器学习成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_Success</FL>
      <MX>Cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please hang up the N gear, step on the foot brake, pull the hand brake, start the engine at least 30S and click OK.</EN>
      <CH>请挂N档，踩脚刹，拉手刹，启动发动机起码30S后点击确定。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Coloque la velocidad N, pise el pedal de freno, jale el freno de mano, arranque el motor al menos 30S y dé clic en OK.</MX>
      <TH>เข้าเกียร์ N, เหยียบเบรกเท้า, ดึงเบรกมือ, สตาร์ทเครื่องยนต์เป็นเวลาอย่างน้อย 30 วินาที แล้วคลิก OK</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Put the gear in 1st, keep your hands stay away from Shift Lever, depress the brake pedal and wait for around 18s then Click OK.</EN>
      <CH>请挂一档，20S内点击确定</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Por favor conecte y dé clic en OK en 20S</MX>
      <TH>เข้าเกียร์แล้วคลิก 'ตกลง' ภายในเวลา 20 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>CSC system exhaust failure, please confirm whether the system exhaust is re-carried out?</EN>
      <CH>CSC系统排气失败，请确认是否重新进行系统排气？</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC_AMT100203_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Falla de purga de sistema CSC, ¿confirme si la purga del sistema se vuelve a realizar?</MX>
      <TH>การไล่ลมระบบ CSC ล้มเหลว โปรดยืนยันว่ามีการทำการไล่ลมระบบซ้ำอีกครั้งหรือไม่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Tips:

Now the CSC system exhaust, please ensure that the following conditions are met and click "Next step"

1. Open the ignition key to ON gear.

2. Release the brake and re-press the brake.

3. The gear is in N gear.

4. Pull up the hand brake.

5. Engine does not start

Note: If there is a failure in the operation, please confirm whether the condition is satisfied, and then operate the ignition key switch from OFF to ON once.</EN>
      <CH>提示语：
现在进行CSC系统排气，请确保以下条件均满足后点击“下一步”
1、点火钥匙开到ON档；
2、松开刹车，并重新踩住刹车；
3、档位在N档；
4、将手刹拉起；
5、发动机不启动
注意：如果在操作过程中出现失败，请先确认条件是否满足；再将点火钥匙开关从OFF至ON操作一次</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC_AMT100203_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Consejos:

Ahora la purga del sistema de CSC, asegúrese que se cumplan las siguientes condiciones y dé clic en "Siguiente paso"

1. Coloque la llave de ignición en ON (encendido).

2. Libere el freno y vuelva a presionar el freno.

3. La velocidad está en la velocidad N.

4. Jale el freno de mano.

5. El motor no arranca

Nota: Si hay una falla en la operación, confirme si se cumple la condición, y después vuelva a operar el interruptor de la llave de ignición de OFF (apagado) a ON (encendido) una vez.</MX>
      <TH>เคล็ดลับ:

ทำการไล่ลมระบบ CSC โปรดตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขต่อไปนี้ แล้วคลิก "ขั้นตอนถัดไป"

1. ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง ON

2. ปล่อยเบรกแล้วเหยียบเบรกอีกครั้ง

3. เกียร์อยู่ในเกียร์ N

4. ดึงเบรกมือ

5. เครื่องยนต์ไม่สตาร์ท

หมายเหตุ: ถ้าเกิดการทำงานล้มเหลวขึ้นในการทำงาน โปรดตรวจสอบยืนยันว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขทั้งหมด แล้วปรับสวิตช์กุญแจจากตำแหน่ง OFF ไปที่ ON</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Successful exhaust of CSC system, prompt:

Please re-check the level of the kettle to ensure that the level is between the upper and lower limit marks. If not, re-add the hydraulic oil, exhaust again, and observe the level again until the level is between the upper and lower limit marks.

If you need to re-add hydraulic oil and re-exhaust, Please add hydraulic oil and choose "yes" to re-exhaust; if you do not need to re-exhaust, please choose "no".</EN>
      <CH>CSC系统排气成功\n提示：
请重新对油壶液位进行检查，确保液位处于上下限标识之间，如不在，重加液压油，再次排气，并再次观察液位，直到液位处于上下限标识之间。

若需要重新添加液压油，并再次排气，请添加液压油后选择“是”重新排气；若不需要再次排气请选择“否”</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC_AMT100203_Tip3</FL>
      <MX>Éxito de purga de sistema CSC, aviso:

Vuelva a verificar el nivel del recipiente para asegurar que el nivel esté entre las marcas de límite superior e inferior. De lo contrario, vuelva a agregar el aceite hidráulico, purgue de nuevo, y observe el nivel de nuevo hasta que el nivel esté entre las marcas de límite superior e inferior.

Si necesita volver a agregar aceite hidráulico y volver a purgar, agregue el aceite hidráulico y elija "sí" para volver a purgar; si no necesita volver a purgar, elija "no".</MX>
      <TH>การไล่ลมระบบ CSC สำเร็จแล้ว คำแนะนำ:

โปรดตรวจสอบระดับในกระปุกน้ำมันไฮดรอลิกเพื่อให้แน่ใจว่าระดับอยู่ระหว่างเครื่องหมายขีดจำกัดด้านบนและด้านล่าง ถ้าไม่เป็นเช่นนั้น ให้เติมน้ำมันไฮดรอลิกและทำการไล่ลมอีกครั้ง จากนั้นให้สังเกตระดับจนกระทั่งระดับอยู่ระหว่างเครื่องหมายขีดจำกัดด้านบนและด้านล่าง

ถ้าคุณจำเป็นต้องเติมน้ำมันไฮดรอลิกและทำการไล่ลมอีกครั้ง ให้เติมน้ำมันไฮดรอลิกแล้วเลือก "ใช่" เพื่อทำการไล่ลมอีกครั้ง ถ้าคุณไม่จำเป็นต้องทำการไล่ลมอีกครั้ง ให้เลือก "ไม่"</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Successful exhaust</EN>
      <CH>系统排气成功</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC_AMT100203_Tip4</FL>
      <MX>Purga exitosa</MX>
      <TH>การไล่ลมสำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Make sure that the following conditions are met and click "Next" to perform KIT pressure relief operation:

1. Open the ignition key to ON gear.

2. Stay on the brake;

3. The gear is in N gear.

4. Pull up the hand brake.

5. Engine does not start

Note: If there is a failure in the operation, please confirm whether the condition is satisfied, and then operate the ignition key switch from OFF to ON once.</EN>
      <CH>确保以下条件均满足后点击“下一步”进行KIT泄压操作：
1、点火钥匙开到ON档；
2、踩住刹车；
3、档位在N档；
4、将手刹拉起；
5、发动机不启动
注意：如果在操作过程中出现失败，请先确认条件是否满足；再将点火钥匙开关从OFF至ON操作一次</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC_AMTF002_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Asegúrese que se cumplan las siguientes condiciones y dé clic en "Siguiente" para realizar la operación de alivio de presión KIT:

1. Coloque la llave de ignición en ON (encendido).

2. Continúe presionando el freno;

3. La velocidad está en la velocidad N.

4. Jale el freno de mano.

5. El motor no arranca

Nota: Si hay una falla en la operación, confirme si se cumple la condición, y después vuelva a operar el interruptor de la llave de ignición de OFF (apagado) a ON (encendido) una vez.</MX>
      <TH>ตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขต่อไปนี้แล้วคลิก "ถัดไป" เพื่อทำการระบายความดันของ KIT:

1. ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง ON

2. เหยียบเบรกค้างไว้;

3. เกียร์อยู่ในเกียร์ N

4. ดึงเบรกมือ

5. เครื่องยนต์ไม่สตาร์ท

หมายเหตุ: ถ้าเกิดการทำงานล้มเหลวขึ้นในการทำงาน โปรดตรวจสอบยืนยันว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขทั้งหมด แล้วปรับสวิตช์กุญแจจากตำแหน่ง OFF ไปที่ ON</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>AMT actuator assembly KIT decompression failed. Please confirm whether AMT actuator assembly decompression is resumed.</EN>
      <CH>AMT执行器总成KIT泄压失败，请确认是否重新进行AMT执行器总成泄压？</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC_AMTF002_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Falló la descompresión KIT del ensamble del actuador AMT. Confirme si se reanudó la descompresión de ensamble del actuador AMT.</MX>
      <TH>การระบายความดันชุดตัวสั่งงาน AMT KIT ล้มเหลว โปรดยืนยันว่าการระบายความดันชุดตัวสั่งงาน AMT ทำงานต่อหรือไม่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Tips:

Firstly, please type the ignition key to the OFF file, then open the lid of the oil pot and add hydraulic oil (pay attention to wearing clean and pollution-free gloves to ensure that no pollutants fall into the oil pot causing other functional problems);

(2) Check the liquid level of the oil pot to ensure that the liquid level is between the upper and lower limit marks;

(3) After completing the above operation, re-set the ignition key to ON file, and ensure that the following conditions are met, then click "Next":

1. Stay on the brake;

2. The gear is in N gear.

3. Pull up the hand brake;

4. Engine does not start

Note: If there is a failure in the operation, please confirm whether the condition is satisfied, and then operate the ignition key switch from OFF to ON once.</EN>
      <CH>提示：
①请先将点火钥匙打至OFF档后再打开油壶盖添加液压油 （注意佩带干净无污染物的手套，确保无污染物掉落油壶内造成其他功能问题）；
②对油壶液位进行检查，确保液位处于上下限标识之间后；
③完成以上操作后，重新将点火钥匙打至ON档，并确保以下条件均满足后点击“下一步”：
1、踩住刹车；
2、档位在N档；
3、将手刹拉起；
4、发动机不启动
注意：如果在操作过程中出现失败，请先确认条件是否满足；再将点火钥匙开关从OFF至ON操作一次</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC_AMTF002_Tip3</FL>
      <MX>Consejos:

Primero, coloque la llave de ignición en la posición OFF (apagado), después abra la tapa del recipiente de aceite y agregue aceite (ponga atención en utilizar guantes limpios y libres de contaminación para asegurar que no caigan contaminantes en el recipiente de aceite que causen otros problemas funcionales);

(2) Revise el nivel de líquido del recipiente de aceite para asegurarse que el nivel de líquido esté entre las marcas de límite superior e inferior;

(3) Después de completar la operación anterior, vuelva a colocar la llave de ignición en la posición ON (encendido), y asegúrese que se cumplan las siguientes condiciones, y después dé clic en "Siguiente":

1. Continúe presionando el freno;

2. La velocidad está en la velocidad N.

3. Jale el freno de mano;

4. El motor no arranca

Nota: Si hay una falla en la operación, confirme si se cumple la condición, y después vuelva a operar el interruptor de la llave de ignición de OFF (apagado) a ON (encendido) una vez.</MX>
      <TH>เคล็ดลับ:

ขั้นแรก ให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF จากนั้นให้เปิดฝาปิดกระปุกน้ำมันไฮดรอลิกแล้วเติมน้ำมันไฮดรอลิก (ต้องสวมถุงมือที่สะอาดและไม่มีสารปนเปื้อน เพื่อให้แน่ใจว่าไม่มีสารปนเปื้อนใดๆ ตกลงไปในกระปุกน้ำมัน ซึ่งอาจเป็นสาเหตุให้เกิดปัญหาการทำงานอื่นๆ ได้)

(2) ตรวจสอบระดับน้ำมันในกระปุกน้ำมันไฮดรอลิกเพื่อให้แน่ใจว่าระดับน้ำมันอยู่ระหว่างเครื่องหมายขีดจำกัดด้านบนและด้านล่าง;

(3) หลังจากทำการดำเนินการด้านบนเสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว ให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง ON อีกครั้ง และตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขต่อไปนี้แล้วคลิก "ถัดไป":

1. เหยียบเบรกค้างไว้;

2. เกียร์อยู่ในเกียร์ N

3. ดึงเบรกมือ;

4. เครื่องยนต์ไม่สตาร์ท

หมายเหตุ: ถ้าเกิดการทำงานล้มเหลวขึ้นในการทำงาน โปรดตรวจสอบยืนยันว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขทั้งหมด แล้วปรับสวิตช์กุญแจจากตำแหน่ง OFF ไปที่ ON</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>AMT Actuator Assembly Pressure Relief Successful</EN>
      <CH>AMT执行器总成泄压成功</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC_AMTF002_Tip4</FL>
      <MX>Alivio de presión de ensamble de actuador AMT exitoso</MX>
      <TH>การระบายความดันของชุดตัวสั่งงาน AMT สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The clues:
Now for the clutch of self-learning, please start the engine, stepping on the brakes, pull the hand brake, gear in the N, confirm the conditions are met and then click the "next"</EN>
      <CH>提示语：
现在进行离合器啮合点的自学习，请启动发动机，踩住刹车、拉起手刹、档位在N档，确认条件均满足后点击“下一步”</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC_AMTF003_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Pistas:
Ahora para la programación automática del embrague, arranque el motor, pise el freno, jale el freno de mano, coloque la velocidad en N, confirme que se cumplan las condiciones y después dé clic en "siguiente"</MX>
      <TH>เคล็ดลับ:
สำหรับการเรียนรู้ค่าด้วยตัวเองของคลัตช์ ให้สตาร์ทเครื่องยนต์, เหยียบเบรก, ดึงเบรกมือ, เข้าเกียร์ N และตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไข จากนั้นให้คลิก "ถัดไป"</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Ongoing clutch engaging point of self learning, please wait for 30 s.</EN>
      <CH>正在进行离合器啮合点的自学习，请等待30S。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC_AMTF003_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Punto de conexión de embrague en curso de programación automática, por favor espere 30 s.</MX>
      <TH>กำลังทำการเรียนรู้ค่าด้วยตัวเองสำหรับจุดจับเข้าของคลัตช์อยู่ โปรดรอเป็นเวลา 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The clutch self learning success</EN>
      <CH>离合器啮合点的自学习成功</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC_AMTF003_Tip3</FL>
      <MX>Éxito de programación automática del embrague</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าด้วยตัวเองของคลัตช์สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The module the return value is wrong, the clutch engaging point of self learning failure, please confirm whether or not to clutch point since the study?</EN>
      <CH>该模块返回值有误，离合器啮合点的自学习失败，请确认是否重新进行离合器啮合点的自学习？</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC_AMTF003_Tip4</FL>
      <MX>El valor de retorno del módulo es incorrecto, falla de programación automática de punto de conexión de embrague, ¿por favor confirme si se reprogramó el punto de embrague desde la programación?</MX>
      <TH>ค่าที่โมดูลส่งกลับไม่ถูกต้อง การเรียนรู้ด้วยตัวเองสำหรับจุดจับเข้าของคลัตช์ล้มเหลว โปรดยืนยันว่าต้องการทำการเรียนรู้ค่าจุดจับเข้าของคลัตช์อีกครั้งหรือไม่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
Now for the clutch of self learning, please make sure that the following conditions are met and then click the "next"
1, the ignition key to ON file;
2, foot on the brake;
3, gear in the N file;
4, pull hand brake;
5, engine starting
Note: if in appeared in the process of operation failure, please confirm whether conditions; Then the ignition key switch from OFF to ON a operation</EN>
      <CH>
现在进行离合器啮合点的自学习，请确保以下条件均满足后点击“下一步”
1、点火钥匙开到ON档；
2、踩住刹车；
3、档位在N档；
4、将手刹拉起；
5、发动机启动
注意：如果在操作过程中出现失败，请先确认条件是否满足；再将点火钥匙开关从OFF至ON操作一次</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC_AMTF003_Tip5</FL>
      <MX>
Ahora para la programación automática del embrague, asegúrese que se cumplan las siguientes condiciones y después dé clic en "siguiente"
1. llave de ignición en posición ON (encendido);
2. pie en el freno;
3. velocidad en posición N;
4. jale el freno de mano;
5. arranque del motor
Nota: si aparece en el proceso una falla de operación, confirme las siguientes condiciones; después cambie el interruptor de ignición de OFF (apagado) a ON (encendido) para operación</MX>
      <TH>
สำหรับการเรียนรู้ค่าด้วยตัวเองของคลัตช์ โปรดตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขต่อไปนี้แล้วให้คลิก "ถัดไป"
1. ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง ON;
2. เหยียบเบรกค้างไว้;
3. เกียร์อยู่ในตำแหน่ง N;
4. ดึงเบรกมือ;
5. สตาร์ทเครื่องยนต์
หมายเหตุ: ถ้าการดำเนินการล้มเหลว โปรดยืนยันว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขหรือไม่ จากนั้นให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจจากตำแหน่ง OFF ไปที่ ON อีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Tip: ready for self learning transmission gear, please put the ignition key switch from ON to OFF after 5 seconds, until ON again, to ensure that the following conditions are met and then click the "next" to transmission gear self-learning operation:
1, stepping on the brakes;
2, the gears in the N file;
3, pull hand brake;
4, don't start the engine
Note: if in appeared in the process of operation failure, please confirm whether conditions; Then the ignition key switch from OFF to ON a operation</EN>
      <CH>提示：准备进行变速箱档位自学习，请将点火钥匙开关从ON至OFF 5秒钟后，再打至ON，确保以下条件均满足后点击“下一步”进行变速箱档位自学习操作：
1、踩住刹车；
2、档位在N档；
3、将手刹拉起；
4、发动机不启动
注意：如果在操作过程中出现失败，请先确认条件是否满足；再将点火钥匙开关从OFF至ON操作一次</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC_AMTF004_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Consejo: listo para programación automática de velocidad de transmisión, coloque el interruptor de llave de ignición de ON (encendido) en OFF (apagado) después de 5 segundos, a ON de nuevo, para asegurarse que se cumplan las siguientes condiciones y después dé clic en "siguiente" para la operación de programación automática de velocidad de la transmisión:
1. pise el freno;
2. velocidades en posición N;
3. jale el freno de mano;
4. no arranque el motor
Nota: si aparece en el proceso una falla de operación, confirme las siguientes condiciones; después cambie el interruptor de ignición de OFF (apagado) a ON (encendido) para operación</MX>
      <TH>เคล็ดลับ: เมื่อพร้อมสำหรับการเรียนรู้ด้วยตัวเองสำหรับตำแหน่งเกียร์ของระบบเกียร์แล้ว ให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจจากตำแหน่ง ON ไปที่ OFF หลังจากผ่านไป 5 วินาที ให้ปรับไปที่ตำแหน่ง ON อีกครั้ง แล้วตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไข จากนั้นให้คลิก "ถัดไป" เพื่อทำการเรียนรู้ค่าด้วยตัวเองสำหรับตำแหน่งเกียร์ของระบบเกียร์:
1. เหยียบเบรก;
2. เกียร์อยู่ในตำแหน่ง N;
3. ดึงเบรกมือ;
4. ไม่ต้องสตาร์ทเครื่องยนต์
หมายเหตุ: ถ้าการดำเนินการล้มเหลว โปรดยืนยันว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขหรือไม่ จากนั้นให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจจากตำแหน่ง OFF ไปที่ ON อีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Self-learning ongoing transmission gear, please wait for 60 s.</EN>
      <CH>正在进行变速箱档位自学习，请等待60S。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC_AMTF004_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Programación automática de velocidad de transmisión en curso, por favor espere 60 s.</MX>
      <TH>กำลังทำการเรียนรู้ค่าด้วยตัวเองสำหรับตำแหน่งเกียร์ของระบบเกียร์อยู่ โปรดรอเป็นเวลา 60 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Gear self learning success</EN>
      <CH>档位自学习成功</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC_AMTF004_Tip3</FL>
      <MX>Éxito de programación automática de velocidad</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าด้วยตัวเองสำหรับตำแหน่งเกียร์สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The module the return value is wrong, since learning failure transmission gear, please confirm whether a new gearbox gear self learning</EN>
      <CH>该模块返回值有误，变速箱档位自学习失败，请确认是否重新进行变速箱档位自学习</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC_AMTF004_Tip4</FL>
      <MX>El valor de retorno del módulo es incorrecto, debido a falla de programación de velocidad de transmisión, por favor confirme la nueva programación automática de la caja de engranes</MX>
      <TH>ค่าที่โมดูลส่งกลับไม่ถูกต้อง การเรียนรู้ค่าสำหรับตำแหน่งเกียร์ของระบบเกียร์ล้มเหลว โปรดยืนยันว่าต้องการทำการเรียนรู้ค่าด้วยตัวเองของระบบเกียร์อีกครั้งหรือไม่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure in operation of adding hydraulic oil process</EN>
      <CH>添加液压油流程操作失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC01_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falla en operación de proceso de adición de aceite hidráulico</MX>
      <TH>การเติมน้ำมันไฮดรอลิกล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Successful exhaust of the system, complete operation of adding hydraulic oil process</EN>
      <CH>系统排气成功，添加液压油流程操作完成</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC01_Success</FL>
      <MX>Purga exitosa de sistema, operación completa de proceso de adición de aceite</MX>
      <TH>การไล่ลมระบบสำเร็จแล้ว โปรดดำเนินการเติมน้ำมันไฮดรอลิกให้เสร็จสมบูรณ์</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Before re-adding hydraulic oil, please do KIT pressure relief first.</EN>
      <CH>在重新添加液压油之前，请先进行KIT泄压。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC01_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Antes de volver a agregar aceite hidráulico, realice el alivio de presión KIT primero.</MX>
      <TH>ก่อนที่จะเติมน้ำมันไฮดรอลิกอีกครั้ง ให้ทำการระบายความดันของ KIT ก่อน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Tips:

1. Please open the lid of the oil pot and add hydraulic oil (pay attention to wearing clean and pollution-free gloves to ensure that no pollutants fall into the oil pot causing other functional problems);

2. Check the level of the oil pot to ensure that the level is between the upper and lower limit marks, then click "Next step"</EN>
      <CH>提示：
1、请打开油壶盖，添加液压油 （注意佩带干净无污染物的手套，确保无污染物掉落油壶内造成其他功能问题）；
2、对油壶液位进行检查，确保液位处于上下限标识之间后，点击“下一步”</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC01_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Consejos:

1. Abra la tapa del recipiente de aceite y agregue aceite (ponga atención en utilizar guantes limpios y libres de contaminación para asegurar que no caigan contaminantes en el recipiente de aceite que causen otros problemas funcionales);

2. Revise el nivel del recipiente de aceite para asegurarse que el nivel de líquido esté entre las marcas de límite superior e inferior, después dé clic en "Siguiente paso"</MX>
      <TH>เคล็ดลับ:

1. เปิดฝาปิดกระปุกน้ำมันไฮดรอลิกแล้วเติมน้ำมันไฮดรอลิก (ต้องสวมถุงมือที่สะอาดและไม่มีสารปนเปื้อน เพื่อให้แน่ใจว่าไม่มีสารปนเปื้อนใดๆ ตกลงไปในกระปุกน้ำมัน ซึ่งอาจเป็นสาเหตุให้เกิดปัญหาการทำงานอื่นๆ ได้)

2. ตรวจสอบระดับในกระปุกน้ำมันไฮดรอลิกเพื่อให้แน่ใจว่าระดับอยู่ระหว่างเครื่องหมายขีดจำกัดด้านบนและด้านล่าง จากนั้นให้คลิก "ขั้นตอนถัดไป"</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>AMT Executor Assembly KIT Replacement Process Operation Failed</EN>
      <CH>AMT执行器总成KIT更换流程操作失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC02_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falla de operación de proceso de reemplazo de KIT de ensamble de ejecutor de AMT</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนชุดตัวสั่งงาน AMT KIT ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Replacement of AMT actuator assembly KIT operation completed!</EN>
      <CH>更换AMT执行器总成KIT操作完成！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC02_Success</FL>
      <MX>¡Reemplazo de operación KIT de ensamble de actuador AMT completo!</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนชุดตัวสั่งงาน AMT KIT เสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว!</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Before replacing the AMT actuator assembly to relieve KIT, please do KIT first.</EN>
      <CH>在更换AMT执行器总成泄压KIT之前，请先进行KIT泄压。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC02_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Antes de reemplazar el ensamble del actuador AMT para liberar el KIT, realice KIT primero.</MX>
      <TH>ก่อนที่จะเปลี่ยนชุดตัวสั่งงาน AMT KIT ให้ทำการระบายความดันของ KIT ก่อน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please type the ignition key to OFF shift, replace AMT actuator assembly KIT again, after the installation is complete, please click "next"</EN>
      <CH>请先将点火钥匙打至OFF档后，再更换AMT执行器总成KIT，安装完成后请点击“下一步”</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC02_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Coloque la llave de ignición en la posición OFF (apagado), reemplace el KIT de ensamble del actuador AMT de nuevo, después que se complete la instalación, dé clic en "siguiente"</MX>
      <TH>ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF, เปลี่ยนชุดตัวสั่งงาน AMT KIT อีกครั้ง หลังจากการติดตั้งเสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว ให้คลิก "ถัดไป"</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Tip:
1) please check the oil pot liquid level, ensure the liquid level between upper and lower identification;
(2) the completion of the above operation, restore the ignition key to ON file, and ensure that the following conditions are met and then click the "next" :
1, stepping on the brakes;
2, the gears in the N file;
3, pull hand brake;
4, don't start the engine
Note: if in appeared in the process of operation failure, please confirm whether conditions; Then the ignition key switch from OFF to ON a operation</EN>
      <CH>提示：
①请对油壶液位进行检查，确保液位处于上下限标识之间；
②完成以上操作后，重新将点火钥匙打至ON档，并确保以下条件均满足后点击“下一步”：
1、踩住刹车；
2、档位在N档；
3、将手刹拉起；
4、发动机不启动
注意：如果在操作过程中出现失败，请先确认条件是否满足；再将点火钥匙开关从OFF至ON操作一次</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC02_Tip3</FL>
      <MX>Sugerencia:
1) verifique el nivel de líquido del recipiente de aceite, asegúrese que el nivel de líquido esté entre la identificación superior e inferior;
(2) Al completar la operación anterior, restablezca la llave de ignición en la posición ON (encendido), y asegúrese que se cumplan las siguientes condiciones, y después dé clic en "siguiente":
1. pise el freno;
2. velocidades en posición N;
3. jale el freno de mano;
4. no arranque el motor
Nota: si aparece en el proceso una falla de operación, confirme las siguientes condiciones; después cambie el interruptor de ignición de OFF (apagado) a ON (encendido) para operación</MX>
      <TH>เคล็ดลับ:
1) โปรดตรวจสอบระดับของกระปุกน้ำมัน ต้องแน่ใจว่าระดับน้ำมันอยู่ระหว่างเครื่องหมายขีดจำกัดด้านบนและด้านล่าง;
(2) หลังจากทำการดำเนินการด้านบนเสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว ให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง ON อีกครั้ง และตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขต่อไปนี้แล้วคลิก "ถัดไป":
1. เหยียบเบรก;
2. เกียร์อยู่ในตำแหน่ง N;
3. ดึงเบรกมือ;
4. ไม่ต้องสตาร์ทเครื่องยนต์
หมายเหตุ: ถ้าการดำเนินการล้มเหลว โปรดยืนยันว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขหรือไม่ จากนั้นให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจจากตำแหน่ง OFF ไปที่ ON อีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Replace the low pressure pipeline process operation failure</EN>
      <CH>更换低压油管流程操作失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC03_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falla de operación de proceso de reemplazo de tubería de baja presión</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนท่อความดันต่ำล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Replace the low pressure pipeline process operation is completed!</EN>
      <CH>更换低压油管流程操作完成！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC03_Success</FL>
      <MX>¡Operación de proceso de reemplazo de tubería de baja presión completa!</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนท่อความดันต่ำเสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Before replacing the original low pressure oil pipe, please for the leakage of the AMT actuator assembly KIT.</EN>
      <CH>在更换原始低压油管之前，请先进行AMT执行器总成KIT泄压。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC03_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Antes de reemplazar el tubo de aceite de baja presión original, libere la presión del KIT del ensamble del actuador AMT.</MX>
      <TH>ก่อนที่จะเปลี่ยนท่อน้ำมันความดันต่ำท่อเดิม ให้ระบายความดันของชุดตัวสั่งงาน AMT KIT ก่อน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please type the ignition key to OFF shift, then remove the low pressure oil pipe, and install the new low pressure oil pipe. After the installation is complete, please click "next"</EN>
      <CH>请先将点火钥匙打至OFF档后，再拆卸低压油管，并安装新低压油管。安装完成后请点击“下一步”</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC03_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Coloque la llave de ignición en la posición OFF (apagado), después retire el tubo de aceite de baja presión, e instale el nuevo tubo de aceite de baja presión. Después que la instalación esté completa, dé clic en "siguiente"</MX>
      <TH>ปรับตำแหน่งสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF จากนั้นให้ถอดท่อน้ำมันความดันต่ำ แล้วติดตั้งท่อน้ำมันความดันต่ำท่อใหม่ หลังจากการติดตั้งเสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว ให้คลิก "ถัดไป"</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Tip:
1) please check the oil pot liquid level, ensure the liquid level between upper and lower identification;
(2) the completion of the above operation, restore the ignition key to ON file, and ensure that the following conditions are met and then click the "next" :
1, stepping on the brakes;
2, the gears in the N file;
3, pull hand brake;
4, don't start the engine
Note: if in appeared in the process of operation failure, please confirm whether conditions; Then the ignition key switch from OFF to ON a operation</EN>
      <CH>提示：
①请对油壶液位进行检查，确保液位处于上下限标识之间；
②完成以上操作后，重新将点火钥匙打至ON档，并确保以下条件均满足后点击“下一步”：
1、踩住刹车；
2、档位在N档；
3、将手刹拉起；
4、发动机不启动
注意：如果在操作过程中出现失败，请先确认条件是否满足；再将点火钥匙开关从OFF至ON操作一次</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC03_Tip3</FL>
      <MX>Sugerencia:
1) verifique el nivel de líquido del recipiente de aceite, asegúrese que el nivel de líquido esté entre la identificación superior e inferior;
(2) Al completar la operación anterior, restablezca la llave de ignición en la posición ON (encendido), y asegúrese que se cumplan las siguientes condiciones, y después dé clic en "siguiente":
1. pise el freno;
2. velocidades en posición N;
3. jale el freno de mano;
4. no arranque el motor
Nota: si aparece en el proceso una falla de operación, confirme las siguientes condiciones; después cambie el interruptor de ignición de OFF (apagado) a ON (encendido) para operación</MX>
      <TH>เคล็ดลับ:
1) โปรดตรวจสอบระดับของกระปุกน้ำมัน ต้องแน่ใจว่าระดับน้ำมันอยู่ระหว่างเครื่องหมายขีดจำกัดด้านบนและด้านล่าง;
(2) หลังจากทำการดำเนินการด้านบนเสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว ให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง ON อีกครั้ง และตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขต่อไปนี้แล้วคลิก "ถัดไป":
1. เหยียบเบรก;
2. เกียร์อยู่ในตำแหน่ง N;
3. ดึงเบรกมือ;
4. ไม่ต้องสตาร์ทเครื่องยนต์
หมายเหตุ: ถ้าการดำเนินการล้มเหลว โปรดยืนยันว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขหรือไม่ จากนั้นให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจจากตำแหน่ง OFF ไปที่ ON อีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Replace the high-pressure tubing (horse to shift module assembly process operation failure</EN>
      <CH>更换高压油管（马达到换档模块总成）流程操作失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC04_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Reemplace la tubería de alta presión (falla de operación de proceso de ensamble de manguera a módulo de cambio</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนท่อความดันสูง (ท่อไปยังโมดูลการเปลี่ยนเกียร์) ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Replace the high-pressure tubing (horse to shift module assembly) process is finished!</EN>
      <CH>更换高压油管（马达到换档模块总成）流程操作完成！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC04_Success</FL>
      <MX>¡Proceso de reemplazo de tubería de alta presión (ensamble de manguera a módulo de cambio) completado!</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนท่อความดันสูง (ท่อไปยังโมดูลการเปลี่ยนเกียร์) เสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>In the replacement of high-pressure tubing (horse to shift module assembly), please first for the leakage of the AMT actuator assembly KIT.</EN>
      <CH>在更换高压油管（马达到换档模块总成）之前，请先进行AMT执行器总成KIT泄压。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC04_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>En el reemplazo de la tubería de alta presión (ensamble de manguera a módulo de cambio), primero pruebe respecto a fugas del KIT de ensamble del actuador AMT.</MX>
      <TH>ในการเปลี่ยนท่อความดันสูง (ท่อไปยังโมดูลการเปลี่ยนเกียร์) ให้ระบายความดันของชุดตัวสั่งงาน AMT KIT ก่อน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please type the ignition key to OFF shift, then remove the pump and high pressure tubing (horse to shift module), and install the new high-pressure tubing. After the installation is complete, please click "next"</EN>
      <CH>请先将点火钥匙打至OFF档后，再拆卸泵高压油管（马达到换档模块），并安装新高压油管。安装完成后请点击“下一步”</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC04_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Coloque la llave de ignición en la posición OFF (apagado), después retire la bomba y la tubería de alta presión (manguera a módulo de cambio), e instale la nueva tubería de alta presión. Después que la instalación esté completa, dé clic en "siguiente"</MX>
      <TH>ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF จากนั้นให้ถอดปั๊มและท่อความดันสูง (ท่อไปยังโมดูลการเปลี่ยนเกียร์) และติดตั้งท่อความดันสูงท่อใหม่ หลังจากการติดตั้งเสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว ให้คลิก "ถัดไป"</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Tip:
1) please check the oil pot liquid level, ensure the liquid level between upper and lower identification;
(2) the completion of the above operation, restore the ignition key to ON file, and ensure that the following conditions are met and then click the "next" :
1, stepping on the brakes;
2, the gears in the N file;
3, pull hand brake;
4, don't start the engine
Note: if in appeared in the process of operation failure, please confirm whether conditions; Then the ignition key switch from OFF to ON a operation</EN>
      <CH>提示：
①请对油壶液位进行检查，确保液位处于上下限标识之间；
②完成以上操作后，重新将点火钥匙打至ON档，并确保以下条件均满足后点击“下一步”：
1、踩住刹车；
2、档位在N档；
3、将手刹拉起；
4、发动机不启动
注意：如果在操作过程中出现失败，请先确认条件是否满足；再将点火钥匙开关从OFF至ON操作一次</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC04_Tip3</FL>
      <MX>Sugerencia:
1) verifique el nivel de líquido del recipiente de aceite, asegúrese que el nivel de líquido esté entre la identificación superior e inferior;
(2) Al completar la operación anterior, restablezca la llave de ignición en la posición ON (encendido), y asegúrese que se cumplan las siguientes condiciones, y después dé clic en "siguiente":
1. pise el freno;
2. velocidades en posición N;
3. jale el freno de mano;
4. no arranque el motor
Nota: si aparece en el proceso una falla de operación, confirme las siguientes condiciones; después cambie el interruptor de ignición de OFF (apagado) a ON (encendido) para operación</MX>
      <TH>เคล็ดลับ:
1) โปรดตรวจสอบระดับของกระปุกน้ำมัน ต้องแน่ใจว่าระดับน้ำมันอยู่ระหว่างเครื่องหมายขีดจำกัดด้านบนและด้านล่าง;
(2) หลังจากทำการดำเนินการด้านบนเสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว ให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง ON อีกครั้ง และตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขต่อไปนี้แล้วคลิก "ถัดไป":
1. เหยียบเบรก;
2. เกียร์อยู่ในตำแหน่ง N;
3. ดึงเบรกมือ;
4. ไม่ต้องสตาร์ทเครื่องยนต์
หมายเหตุ: ถ้าการดำเนินการล้มเหลว โปรดยืนยันว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขหรือไม่ จากนั้นให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจจากตำแหน่ง OFF ไปที่ ON อีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Replace the high-pressure tubing (clutch actuators to shift module) process operation failure</EN>
      <CH>更换高压油管（离合器执行器到换档模块）流程操作失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC05_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falla de operación de proceso de reemplazo de tubería de alta presión (actuadores de embrague a módulo de cambio)</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนท่อความดันสูง (ตัวสั่งงานคลัตช์ไปยังโมดูลการเปลี่ยนเกียร์) ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Replace the high-pressure tubing (clutch actuators to shift module) process is finished!</EN>
      <CH>更换高压油管（离合器执行器到换档模块）流程操作完成！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC05_Success</FL>
      <MX>¡Proceso de reemplazo de tubería de alta presión (actuadores de embrague a módulo de cambio) completado!</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนท่อความดันสูง (ตัวสั่งงานคลัตช์ไปยังโมดูลการเปลี่ยนเกียร์) เสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>In replacement of high-pressure tubing (clutch actuators to shift module) before, please first to the leakage of the AMT actuator assembly KIT.</EN>
      <CH>在更换高压油管（离合器执行器到换档模块）之前，请先进行AMT执行器总成KIT泄压。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC05_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>En el reemplazo de la tubería de alta presión (actuadores de embrague a módulo de cambio) antes, primero pruebe respecto a fugas del KIT de ensamble del actuador AMT.</MX>
      <TH>ในการเปลี่ยนท่อความดันสูง (ตัวสั่งงานคลัตช์ไปยังโมดูลการเปลี่ยนเกียร์) ให้ระบายความดันของชุดตัวสั่งงาน AMT KIT ก่อน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please type the ignition key to OFF shift, then remove the pump and high pressure tubing (horse to shift module), and install the new high-pressure tubing. After the installation is complete, please click "next"</EN>
      <CH>请先将点火钥匙打至OFF档后，再拆卸泵高压油管（马达到换档模块），并安装新高压油管。安装完成后请点击“下一步”</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC05_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Coloque la llave de ignición en la posición OFF (apagado), después retire la bomba y la tubería de alta presión (manguera a módulo de cambio), e instale la nueva tubería de alta presión. Después que la instalación esté completa, dé clic en "siguiente"</MX>
      <TH>ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF จากนั้นให้ถอดปั๊มและท่อความดันสูง (ท่อไปยังโมดูลการเปลี่ยนเกียร์) และติดตั้งท่อความดันสูงท่อใหม่ หลังจากการติดตั้งเสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว ให้คลิก "ถัดไป"</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Tip:
1) please check the oil pot liquid level, ensure the liquid level between upper and lower identification;
(2) the completion of the above operation, restore the ignition key to ON file, and ensure that the following conditions are met and then click the "next" :
1, stepping on the brakes;
2, the gears in the N file;
3, pull hand brake;
4, don't start the engine
Note: if in appeared in the process of operation failure, please confirm whether conditions; Then the ignition key switch from OFF to ON a operation</EN>
      <CH>提示：
①请对油壶液位进行检查，确保液位处于上下限标识之间；
②完成以上操作后，重新将点火钥匙打至ON档，并确保以下条件均满足后点击“下一步”：
1、踩住刹车；
2、档位在N档；
3、将手刹拉起；
4、发动机不启动
注意：如果在操作过程中出现失败，请先确认条件是否满足；再将点火钥匙开关从OFF至ON操作一次</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC05_Tip3</FL>
      <MX>Sugerencia:
1) verifique el nivel de líquido del recipiente de aceite, asegúrese que el nivel de líquido esté entre la identificación superior e inferior;
(2) Al completar la operación anterior, restablezca la llave de ignición en la posición ON (encendido), y asegúrese que se cumplan las siguientes condiciones, y después dé clic en "siguiente":
1. pise el freno;
2. velocidades en posición N;
3. jale el freno de mano;
4. no arranque el motor
Nota: si aparece en el proceso una falla de operación, confirme las siguientes condiciones; después cambie el interruptor de ignición de OFF (apagado) a ON (encendido) para operación</MX>
      <TH>เคล็ดลับ:
1) โปรดตรวจสอบระดับของกระปุกน้ำมัน ต้องแน่ใจว่าระดับน้ำมันอยู่ระหว่างเครื่องหมายขีดจำกัดด้านบนและด้านล่าง;
(2) หลังจากทำการดำเนินการด้านบนเสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว ให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง ON อีกครั้ง และตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขต่อไปนี้แล้วคลิก "ถัดไป":
1. เหยียบเบรก;
2. เกียร์อยู่ในตำแหน่ง N;
3. ดึงเบรกมือ;
4. ไม่ต้องสตาร์ทเครื่องยนต์
หมายเหตุ: ถ้าการดำเนินการล้มเหลว โปรดยืนยันว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขหรือไม่ จากนั้นให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจจากตำแหน่ง OFF ไปที่ ON อีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Replace the valve body assembly VB process operation failure</EN>
      <CH>更换阀体总成VB流程操作失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC06_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falla de operación de proceso de reemplazo de VB de ensamble de cuerpo de válvula</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนชุดตัวเรือนวาล์ว VB ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Replace the valve body assembly VB process operation is completed!</EN>
      <CH>更换阀体总成VB流程操作完成！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC06_Success</FL>
      <MX>¡Operación de proceso de reemplazo de VB de ensamble de cuerpo de válvula completo!</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนชุดตัวเรือนวาล์ว VB เสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Before replacing the valve body assembly VB, please for the leakage of the AMT actuator assembly KIT.</EN>
      <CH>在更换阀体总成VB之前，请先进行AMT执行器总成KIT泄压。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC06_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Antes de reemplazar el VB del ensamble del cuerpo de la válvula, libere la presión del KIT den ensamble del actuador de AMT.</MX>
      <TH>ก่อนที่จะเปลี่ยนชุดตัวเรือนวาล์ว VB ให้ระบายความดันของชุดตัวสั่งงาน AMT KIT ก่อน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please type the ignition key to OFF shift, then remove the valve assembly VB, and install the new VB. After the installation is complete, please click "next"</EN>
      <CH>请先将点火钥匙打至OFF档后，再拆卸阀体总成VB，并安装新VB。安装完成后请点击“下一步”</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC06_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Coloque la llave de ignición en la posición OFF, después retire el VB del ensamble de válvula, e instale el nuevo VB. Después de completar la instalación, dé clic en "siguiente"</MX>
      <TH>ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF จากนั้นให้ถอดชุดวาล์ว VB แล้วติดตั้ง VB ตัวใหม่ หลังจากที่การติดตั้งเสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว ให้คลิก "ถัดไป"</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Tip:
1) please check the oil pot liquid level, ensure the liquid level between upper and lower identification;
(2) the completion of the above operation, restore the ignition key to ON file, and ensure that the following conditions are met and then click the "next" :
1, stepping on the brakes;
2, the gears in the N file;
3, pull hand brake;
4, don't start the engine
Note: if in appeared in the process of operation failure, please confirm whether conditions; Then the ignition key switch from OFF to ON a operation</EN>
      <CH>提示：
①请对油壶液位进行检查，确保液位处于上下限标识之间；
②完成以上操作后，重新将点火钥匙打至ON档，并确保以下条件均满足后点击“下一步”：
1、踩住刹车；
2、档位在N档；
3、将手刹拉起；
4、发动机不启动
注意：如果在操作过程中出现失败，请先确认条件是否满足；再将点火钥匙开关从OFF至ON操作一次</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC06_Tip3</FL>
      <MX>Sugerencia:
1) verifique el nivel de líquido del recipiente de aceite, asegúrese que el nivel de líquido esté entre la identificación superior e inferior;
(2) Al completar la operación anterior, restablezca la llave de ignición en la posición ON (encendido), y asegúrese que se cumplan las siguientes condiciones, y después dé clic en "siguiente":
1. pise el freno;
2. velocidades en posición N;
3. jale el freno de mano;
4. no arranque el motor
Nota: si aparece en el proceso una falla de operación, confirme las siguientes condiciones; después cambie el interruptor de ignición de OFF (apagado) a ON (encendido) para operación</MX>
      <TH>เคล็ดลับ:
1) โปรดตรวจสอบระดับของกระปุกน้ำมัน ต้องแน่ใจว่าระดับน้ำมันอยู่ระหว่างเครื่องหมายขีดจำกัดด้านบนและด้านล่าง;
(2) หลังจากทำการดำเนินการด้านบนเสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว ให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง ON อีกครั้ง และตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขต่อไปนี้แล้วคลิก "ถัดไป":
1. เหยียบเบรก;
2. เกียร์อยู่ในตำแหน่ง N;
3. ดึงเบรกมือ;
4. ไม่ต้องสตาร์ทเครื่องยนต์
หมายเหตุ: ถ้าการดำเนินการล้มเหลว โปรดยืนยันว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขหรือไม่ จากนั้นให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจจากตำแหน่ง OFF ไปที่ ON อีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Replace the oil pump motor process operation failure</EN>
      <CH>更换油泵马达流程操作失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC07_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falla de operación de proceso de reemplazo de motor de bomba de aceite</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนมอเตอร์ปั๊มน้ำมันล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Replace the oil pump motor process operation is completed!</EN>
      <CH>更换油泵马达流程操作完成！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC07_Success</FL>
      <MX>¡Operación de proceso de reemplazo de motor de bomba de aceite completada!</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนมอเตอร์ปั๊มน้ำมันเสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Before replacing the original oil pump motor, please for the leakage of the AMT actuator assembly KIT.</EN>
      <CH>在更换原始油泵马达之前，请先进行AMT执行器总成KIT泄压。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC07_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Antes de reemplazar el motor de la bomba de aceite original, libere la presión del KIT del ensamble del actuador AMT.</MX>
      <TH>ก่อนที่จะเปลี่ยนมอเตอร์ปั๊มน้ำมันตัวเดิม ให้ระบายความดันของชุดตัวสั่งงาน AMT KIT ก่อน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>First the ignition key to OFF file after, then please remove the oil pump motor, and install the new oil pump motor. After the installation is complete, please click "next"</EN>
      <CH>先将点火钥匙打至OFF档后，再请拆卸油泵马达，并安装新油泵马达。安装完成后请点击“下一步”</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC07_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Primero coloque la llave de ignición en la posición OFF (apagado), retire el motor de la bomba de aceite, e instale el nuevo motor de la bomba de aceite. Después que la instalación esté completa, dé clic en "siguiente"</MX>
      <TH>ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF จากนั้นให้ถอดมอเตอร์ปั๊มน้ำมัน แล้วติดตั้งมอเตอร์ปั๊มน้ำมันตัวใหม่ หลังจากการติดตั้งเสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว ให้คลิก "ถัดไป"</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Replace the TCM transmission control unit process operation failure</EN>
      <CH>更换TCM变速器控制单元流程操作失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC08_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falla de operación de proceso de reemplazo de unidad de control de transmisión TCM</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนชุดควบคุมระบบเกียร์ TCM ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Replace TCM transmission control unit process operation is completed!</EN>
      <CH>更换TCM变速器控制单元流程操作完成！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC08_Success</FL>
      <MX>¡Operación de proceso de reemplazo de unidad de control de transmisión TCM completa!</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนชุดควบคุมระบบเกียร์ TCM เสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Completion of new TCM transmission control unit of the replacement, please make sure that the following conditions are met, and click "next"
1, the ignition key to ON file;
2, foot on the brake;
3, gear in the N file;
4, pull hand brake;
5, don't start the engine
Note: if in appeared in the process of operation failure, please confirm whether conditions; Then the ignition key switch from OFF to ON a operation</EN>
      <CH>完成新TCM变速器控制单元的更换后，请确保以下条件均满足，并点击“下一步”
1、点火钥匙开到ON档；
2、踩住刹车；
3、档位在N档；
4、将手刹拉起；
5、发动机不启动
注意：如果在操作过程中出现失败，请先确认条件是否满足；再将点火钥匙开关从OFF至ON操作一次</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC08_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Al completar el reemplazo de la nueva unidad de control de transmisión TCM, asegúrese que se cumplan las siguientes condiciones, y dé clic en "siguiente"
1. llave de ignición en posición ON (encendido);
2. pie en el freno;
3. velocidad en posición N;
4. jale el freno de mano;
5. no arranque el motor
Nota: si aparece en el proceso una falla de operación, confirme las siguientes condiciones; después cambie el interruptor de ignición de OFF (apagado) a ON (encendido) para operación</MX>
      <TH>เมื่อการเปลี่ยนชุดควบคุมระบบเกียร์ TCM ชุดใหม่เสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว โปรดตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขต่อไปนี้ จากนั้นให้คลิก "ถัดไป"
1. ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง ON;
2. เหยียบเบรกค้างไว้;
3. เกียร์อยู่ในตำแหน่ง N;
4. ดึงเบรกมือ;
5. ไม่ต้องสตาร์ทเครื่องยนต์
หมายเหตุ: ถ้าการดำเนินการล้มเหลว โปรดยืนยันว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขหรือไม่ จากนั้นให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจจากตำแหน่ง OFF ไปที่ ON อีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Replace power unit assembly PU process operation failure</EN>
      <CH>更换动力单元总成PU流程操作失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC09_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falla de operación de proceso de reemplazo de PU de ensamble de unidad de potencia</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนชุดจ่ายกำลัง PU ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Replace power unit assembly PU process operation is completed!</EN>
      <CH>更换动力单元总成PU流程操作完成！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC09_Success</FL>
      <MX>¡Operación de proceso de reemplazo de PU de ensamble de unidad de potencia completa!</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนชุดจ่ายกำลัง PU เสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Before replacing original power unit assembly PU, please first for the leakage of the AMT actuator assembly KIT.</EN>
      <CH>在更换原始动力单元总成PU之前，请先进行AMT执行器总成KIT泄压。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC09_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Antes de reemplazar la PU del ensamble de unidad de potencia original, primer realice la prueba de fuga del KIT de ensamble de actuador AMT.</MX>
      <TH>ก่อนที่จะเปลี่ยนชุดจ่ายกำลัง PU ให้ระบายความดันของชุดตัวสั่งงาน AMT KIT ก่อน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please type the ignition key to OFF shift, then remove the power unit assembly PU, and install the new PU. After the installation is complete, please click "next"</EN>
      <CH>请先将点火钥匙打至OFF档后，再拆卸动力单元总成PU，并安装新PU。安装完成后请点击“下一步”</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC09_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Coloque la llave de ignición en la posición OFF, después retire la PU del ensamble de unidad de potencia, e instale la nueva PU. Después de completar la instalación, dé clic en "siguiente"</MX>
      <TH>ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF จากนั้นให้ถอดชุดจ่ายกำลัง PU แล้วติดตั้ง PU ตัวใหม่ หลังจากที่การติดตั้งเสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว ให้คลิก "ถัดไป"</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Tip:
1) please check the oil pot liquid level, ensure the liquid level between upper and lower identification;
(2) the completion of the above operation, restore the ignition key to ON file, and ensure that the following conditions are met and then click the "next" :
1, stepping on the brakes;
2, the gears in the N file;
3, pull hand brake;
4, don't start the engine
Note: if in appeared in the process of operation failure, please confirm whether conditions; Then the ignition key switch from OFF to ON a operation</EN>
      <CH>提示：
①请对油壶液位进行检查，确保液位处于上下限标识之间；
②完成以上操作后，重新将点火钥匙打至ON档，并确保以下条件均满足后点击“下一步”：
1、踩住刹车；
2、档位在N档；
3、将手刹拉起；
4、发动机不启动
注意：如果在操作过程中出现失败，请先确认条件是否满足；再将点火钥匙开关从OFF至ON操作一次</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_AMT_RC09_Tip3</FL>
      <MX>Sugerencia:
1) verifique el nivel de líquido del recipiente de aceite, asegúrese que el nivel de líquido esté entre la identificación superior e inferior;
(2) Al completar la operación anterior, restablezca la llave de ignición en la posición ON (encendido), y asegúrese que se cumplan las siguientes condiciones, y después dé clic en "siguiente":
1. pise el freno;
2. velocidades en posición N;
3. jale el freno de mano;
4. no arranque el motor
Nota: si aparece en el proceso una falla de operación, confirme las siguientes condiciones; después cambie el interruptor de ignición de OFF (apagado) a ON (encendido) para operación</MX>
      <TH>เคล็ดลับ:
1) โปรดตรวจสอบระดับของกระปุกน้ำมัน ต้องแน่ใจว่าระดับน้ำมันอยู่ระหว่างเครื่องหมายขีดจำกัดด้านบนและด้านล่าง;
(2) หลังจากทำการดำเนินการด้านบนเสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว ให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง ON อีกครั้ง และตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขต่อไปนี้แล้วคลิก "ถัดไป":
1. เหยียบเบรก;
2. เกียร์อยู่ในตำแหน่ง N;
3. ดึงเบรกมือ;
4. ไม่ต้องสตาร์ทเครื่องยนต์
หมายเหตุ: ถ้าการดำเนินการล้มเหลว โปรดยืนยันว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขหรือไม่ จากนั้นให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจจากตำแหน่ง OFF ไปที่ ON อีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Add key result upload failed, the reason is: upload add key result failed.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙结果上传失败，原因为：上传添加钥匙结果失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_AddKey_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falla de carga de resultado de adición de llave, razón: falla de carga de resultado de adición de llave.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการเพิ่มกุญแจล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการอัพโหลดผลการเพิ่มกุญแจล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The key was added and uploaded successfully. Please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙结果上传成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_AddKey_Success</FL>
      <MX>La llave se agregó y cargó con éxito. Cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจและการอัพโหลดสำเร็จแล้ว ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are:  the after-sales server could not be accessed.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：无法访问售后服务器。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: no se pudo acceder al servidor post-venta.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าถึงเซิร์ฟเวอร์หลังการขายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are:  security decryption failed.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：安全解密失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Fail10</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: falla de descripción de seguridad.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการถอดรหัสนิรภัยล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The car has no matching keys.</EN>
      <CH>该车无已匹配的钥匙。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Fail11</FL>
      <MX>El vehículo no tiene llaves coincidentes.</MX>
      <TH>รถไม่มีกุญแจที่จับคู่ไว้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Key deletion failed because: delete failed.</EN>
      <CH>删除钥匙失败，原因为：删除失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Fail12</FL>
      <MX>Falla de eliminación de llave debido a: falla de eliminación.</MX>
      <TH>การลบกุญแจล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการลบล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Key deletion failed because: all keys were not deleted.</EN>
      <CH>删除钥匙失败，原因为：未删除所有钥匙。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Fail13</FL>
      <MX>Falla de eliminación de llave debida a: no se eliminaron todas las llaves.</MX>
      <TH>การลบกุญแจล้มเหลวเนื่องจากลบกุญแจไม่หมดทุกชุด</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Anti-theft match failed because: VIN failed to write.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：写入VIN失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Fail14</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate anti-robo debida a: Falla en escribir el VIN.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเขียน VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Security match failed because: write PIN failed.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：写入PIN失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Fail15</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate de seguridad debida a: Falla de escritura de NIP.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบนิรภัยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเขียน PIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Anti-theft matching failed, the reason is: No ECM.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：No ECM.</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Fail16</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate anti-robo, razón: No hay ECM.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มี ECM</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are:  OBD is not connected.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: OBD no está conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are:  VIN confirms failure.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：VIN确认失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: el VIN confirma la falla.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการยืนยัน VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are: </EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: </MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are: failed to get the number of keys.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：获取钥匙数量失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: falla en obtener el número de llaves.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเรียกข้อมูลจำนวนกุญแจได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are:  IMMO is not locked.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：IMMO未锁定。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: IMMO no está bloqueado.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก IMMO ไม่ล็อค</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are:  number of keys read</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：读取到钥匙数量</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Fail7</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: número de llaves leídas</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการอ่านจำนวนกุญแจ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are:  the maximum number of keys matching has been reached.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：已达最大钥匙匹配数量。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Fail8</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: se alcanzó el número máximo de empate de llaves.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากถึงจำนวนสูงสุดของการจับคู่กุญแจแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are: failed to enter the extension session.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：进入扩展会话失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Fail9</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: falla en ingresar la sesión de extensión.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าสู่เซสชั่นแบบขยายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are: reading and writing memory errors; repair prompt: "1. BCM KL30 retries the service after power down;
2. Replace BCM;</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：读写内存错误；返修提示："1，BCM KL30 下电后重试该服务；
2, 更换BCM；"

</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5800_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: errores de memoria de lectura y escritura; aviso de reparación: "1. BCM KL30 reintenta el servicio después de apagado;
2. Reemplazar el BCM;</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดในการอ่านและการเขียนหน่วยความจำ; คำแนะนำการซ่อม: "1. BCM KL30 ลองใช้บริการอีกครั้งหลังจากปิดระบบ;
2. เปลี่ยน BCM;</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reason for the failure of anti-theft matching is: Writing RKE error; Repair prompt: "1, you can try to add the key again."
2. Change the new key abnormally.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：写RKE错误；返修提示："1，可尝试重新添加该钥匙
2，钥匙状态异常更换全新钥匙；"

</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5800_Fail10</FL>
      <MX>La razón para la falla del empate anti-robo es: Error de escritura de RKE; Aviso de reparación: "1. puede intentar agregar la llave de nuevo."
2. Cambio de nueva llave anormal.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดในการเขียน RKE; คำแนะนำการซ่อม: "1. ลองเพิ่มกุญแจอีกครั้ง"
2. การเปลี่ยนกุญแจชุดใหม่ผิดปกติ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reason for the failure of anti-theft matching is unknown error.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：未知错误。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5800_Fail11</FL>
      <MX>La razón para la falla de empate anti-roo es un error desconocido.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดที่ไม่รู้จัก</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are: IMMO is not locked; repair prompt: 1, read the status of BCM IMMO module;
2. Ensure that BCM has the correct PIN, SK, VIN and lock BCM</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：IMMO未锁定；返修提示：1, 读取BCM IMMO模块状态；
2, 确保BCM具备正确的PIN，SK，VIN后锁定BCM</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5800_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: IMMO no bloqueado; aviso de reparación: 1. lea el estado del módulo IMMO de BCM;
2. Asegúrese que el BCM tenga el NIP, SK, VIN correctos y bloquee el BCM</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก IMMO ไม่ล็อค ; คำแนะนำการซ่อม: 1. อ่านสถานะของโมดูล BCM IMMO;
2. ต้องแน่ใจว่า BCM มี PIN, SK, VIN ที่ถูกต้อง และ BCM ล็อคอยู่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are: the key slot is full; repair tips: 1. BCM has learned the key to reach the upper limit, it is recommended to delete the key and try again; (old keys need to be re-added)</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：钥匙槽已满；返修提示：1,BCM中已经学习的钥匙达到上限，建议删除钥匙后重试；（旧钥匙需重新添加）
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5800_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: la ranura de la llave está llena; consejos de reparación: 1. El BCM programó la llave para alcanzar el límite superior, se recomienda eliminar la llave e intentar de nuevo; (las llaves anteriores se necesitan volver a agregar)</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากช่องสำหรับกุญแจเต็มแล้ว; คำแนะนำการซ่อม: 1. BCM ได้เรียนรู้กุญแจจนถึงขีดจำกัดสูงสุดแล้ว ขอแนะนำให้ลบกุญแจออกแล้วลองอีกครั้ง; (จำเป็นต้องเพิ่มกุญแจชุดเดิมอีกครั้ง)</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure of anti-theft matching due to: Transponder authentication error; repair prompt: "1, confirm that the key is in normal condition, may not match the key."
2. Use the KeyTest service to confirm that the key is a new key or a legitimate old key</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：Transponder认证错误；返修提示："1, 确认钥匙状态正常，可能是不匹配的钥匙
2,使用KeyTest服务确认钥匙为新钥匙或者合法的旧钥匙

</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5800_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate anti-robo debido a: Error de autenticación de transpondedor; aviso de reparación: "1. confirme que la llave esté en condición normal, puede no coincidir con la llave."
2. Use el servicio KeyTest para confirmar que la llave sea una llave nueva o una llave anterior legítima</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดในการตรวจสอบความถูกต้องของตัวรับส่งสัญญาณ; คำแนะนำการซ่อม: "1. ยืนยันว่ากุญแจอยู่ในสภาพปกติ, ไม่สามารถจับคู่กุญแจได้"
2. ใช้บริการ KeyTest เพื่อยืนยันว่ากุญแจเป็นกุญแจชุดใหม่หรือเป็นกุญแจชุดเก่าที่สามารถใช้งานได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are: ABIC or Key communication timeout; repair prompt: "1. Make sure that the base station's wire harness is connected correctly and there is no loosening;
2. Make sure that the base station is fixed on the lock head tightly and reliably without loosening.
3. Try to replace the base station.
4. Try to replace the base station connection harness or key.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：ABIC 或 Key通讯超时；返修提示："1，确认基站的线束连接正确，无松动；
2，确认基站安装在锁头上紧固可靠，无松动；
3，尝试更换基站；
4，尝试更换基站连接线束或者钥匙"

</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5800_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: Expiración de tiempo de comunicación de ABIC o Llave; aviso de reparación: "1. Asegúrese que el arnés de cableado de la estación base esté conectado correctamente y no haya holgura;
2. Asegúrese que la estación base esté fija en el dispositivo de bloqueo firmemente y de forma confiable sin aflojarse.
3. Intente reemplazar la estación base.
4. Intente reemplazar el arnés de conexión o la llave de la estación base.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการติดต่อสื่อสารของกุญแจหรือ ABIC หมดเวลาแล้ว; คำแนะนำการซ่อม: "1. ต้องแน่ใจว่าชุดสายไฟของสถานีฐานเชื่อมต่ออยู่อย่างถูกต้องและไม่มีการหลวม;
2. ต้องแน่ใจว่าสถานีฐานยึดอยู่บนตัวล็อคอย่างแน่นหนาและไม่มีการคลายตัวออก
3. ลองเปลี่ยนสถานีฐาน
4. ลองเปลี่ยนชุดสายไฟเชื่อมต่อสถานีฐานหรือกุญแจ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are: no keys; repair tips: "1. Make sure that the base station is fixed on the lock head tightly and reliably, without loosening;
2. The key should be inserted into the lock head completely.
3. Make sure that there is no metal shield between the key and the coil.
4. The key condition is abnormal, the key is recommended.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：无钥匙；返修提示："1，确认基站安装在锁头上紧固可靠，无松动；
2，钥匙需完全插入锁头；
3，确认钥匙与线圈之间没有金属的屏蔽物体；
4，钥匙状态异常，建议钥匙；"

</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5800_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: no hay llaves; consejos de reparación: "1. Asegúrese que la estación base esté fija en el dispositivo de bloqueo firmemente y de forma confiable, sin aflojarse;
2. La llave se debe insertar en el dispositivo de bloqueo completamente.
3. Asegúrese que no hay una protección de metal entre la llave y la bobina.
4. La condición de la llave es anormal, llave recomendada.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีกุญแจ; คำแนะนำการซ่อม: "1. ต้องแน่ใจว่าสถานีฐานยึดอยู่บนตัวล็อคอย่างแน่นหนาโดยไม่มีการคลายตัวออก;
2. กุญแจควรเสียบเข้าไปในตัวล็อคจนสุด
3. ต้องแน่ใจว่าไม่มีโลหะกั้นระหว่างกุญแจกับขดลวด
4. สภาพของกุญแจผิดปกติ กุญแจที่แนะนำ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are: Writing a memory error in Transponder; Repair Tips: "1. The key status is abnormal to replace a new key;
2. Make sure that the base station's wiring harness is connected correctly without loosening.
3. Make sure that the base station is fixed on the lock head tightly and reliably without loosening.
4. Try to replace the base station.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：写Transponder内存错误；返修提示："1，钥匙状态异常更换全新钥匙；
2，确认基站的线束连接正确，无松动；
3，确认基站安装在锁头上紧固可靠，无松动；
4，尝试更换基站；"

</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5800_Fail7</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: Escritura de error de memoria en el transpondedor; Consejos de reparación: "1. El estado de llave es anormal para reemplazar una llave nueva;
2. Asegúrese que el arnés de cableado de la estación base esté conectado correctamente sin aflojarse.
3. Asegúrese que la estación base esté fija en el dispositivo de bloqueo firmemente y de forma confiable sin aflojarse.
4. Intente reemplazar la estación base.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดในการเขียนข้อมูลหน่วยความจำในตัวรับส่งสัญญาณ; คำแนะนำการซ่อม: "1. สถานะของกุญแจผิดปกติ ให้เปลี่ยนกุญแจใหม่;
2. ต้องแน่ใจว่าชุดสายไฟของสถานีฐานเชื่อมต่ออยู่อย่างถูกต้องโดยไม่มีการหลวม
3. ต้องแน่ใจว่าสถานีฐานยึดอยู่บนตัวล็อคอย่างแน่นหนาและไม่มีการคลายตัวออก
4. ลองเปลี่ยนสถานีฐาน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure of anti-theft matching due to: authentication error; repair prompt: "1, you can try to add the key again."
2. Change the new key abnormally.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：认证错误；返修提示："1，可尝试重新添加该钥匙
2，钥匙状态异常更换全新钥匙；"

</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5800_Fail8</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate anti-robo debido a: Error de autenticación; aviso de reparación: "1. puede intentar agregar la llave de nuevo."
2. Cambio de nueva llave anormal.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดในการตรวจสอบความถูกต้อง; คำแนะนำการซ่อม: "1. ลองเพิ่มกุญแจอีกครั้ง"
2. การเปลี่ยนกุญแจชุดใหม่ผิดปกติ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure of anti-theft matching due to: incorrect configuration of Transponder; repair prompt:
1. Change the new key abnormally.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：Transponder配置错误；返修提示：
1，钥匙状态异常更换全新钥匙；
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5800_Fail9</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate anti-robo debido a: configuración incorrecta de transpondedor; aviso de reparación:
1. Cambio de nueva llave anormal.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการกำหนดค่าตัวรับส่งสัญญาณไม่ถูกต้อง; คำแนะนำการซ่อม:
1. การเปลี่ยนกุญแจชุดใหม่ผิดปกติ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Successful addition of keys</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙成功</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5800_Success</FL>
      <MX>Adición exitosa de llaves</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจสำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The key has been added.</EN>
      <CH>该钥匙已添加。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5800_Success1</FL>
      <MX>La llave se agregó.</MX>
      <TH>กุญแจได้รับการเพิ่มแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reason for the failure of anti-theft matching is: IMMO is not locked; repair prompt: "1. BCM KL30 retries the service after power down;
2. Replace BCM;</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：IMMO未锁定；返修提示："1，BCM KL30 下电后重试该服务；
2, 更换BCM；"

</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5804_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La razón para la falla del empate anti-robo es: IMMO no bloqueado; aviso de reparación: "1. BCM KL30 reintenta el servicio después de apagado;
2. Reemplazar el BCM;</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก IMMO ไม่ล็อค ; คำแนะนำการซ่อม: "1. BCM KL30 ลองใช้บริการอีกครั้งหลังจากปิดระบบ;
2. เปลี่ยน BCM;</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The anti-theft matching failed because IMMO was locked</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：IMMO已锁定
。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5804_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>El empate anti-robo falló debido a que el IMMO estaba bloqueado</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก IMMO ถูกล็อคไว้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure of anti-theft matching due to unmatched ECM</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：未匹配过的ECM
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5804_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate anti-robo debida a ECM no coincidente</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก ECM ไม่ตรงกัน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure of anti-theft matching due to invalid PIN code</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：无效的PIN码
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5804_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate anti-robo debida a código NIP no válido</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากรหัส PIN ไม่ถูกต้อง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure of anti-theft matching due to ECM communication error</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：ECM通讯错误
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5804_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate anti-robo debida a error de comunicación de ECM</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดในการติดต่อสื่อสาร ECM</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure of anti-theft matching due to CRC error</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：CRC错误
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5804_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate anti-robo debida a error de CRC</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดของ CRC</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure of anti-theft matching due to unknown error</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：未知错误</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5804_Fail7</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate anti-robo debida a error desconocido</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดที่ไม่รู้จัก</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The anti-theft matching failed because ECM has learned SK, but SK does not match.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：ECM已学习SK，但SK不匹配
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5805_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate anti-robo debida a ECM programó el SK, pero el SK no coincide.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก ECM ได้เรียนรู้ค่า SK แล้ว แต่ SK ไม่ตรงกัน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reason for the failure of anti-theft matching is: IMMO is not locked; repair prompt: "1, read the status of BCM IMMO module;
2. Ensure that BCM has the correct PIN, SK, VIN and lock BCM "</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：IMMO未锁定；返修提示："1, 读取BCM IMMO模块状态；
2, 确保BCM具备正确的PIN，SK，VIN后锁定BCM"

</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5805_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>La razón para la falla del empate anti-robo es: IMMO no bloqueado; aviso de reparación: "1. lea el estado del módulo IMMO de BCM;
2. Asegúrese que el BCM tenga el NIP, SK, VIN correctos y bloquee el BCM "</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก IMMO ไม่ล็อค; คำแนะนำการซ่อม: "1. อ่านสถานะของโมดูล BCM IMMO;
2. ต้องแน่ใจว่า BCM มี PIN, SK, VIN ที่ถูกต้อง และ BCM ล็อคอยู่ "</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure of anti-theft matching due to ECM communication error</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：ECM通讯错误
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5805_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate anti-robo debida a error de comunicación de ECM</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดในการติดต่อสื่อสาร ECM</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are: CRC error; repair tips: 1. It is recommended to check whether the ECM model is correct and the BCM model is correct; 2. If they are all correct, you can check whether there is interference in the bus;</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：CRC错误；返修提示：1，建议排查ECM型号是否正确，BCM型号是否正确；2，如果均正确，可以检查总线是否存在干扰；

</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5805_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: error de CRC; consejos de reparación: 1. Se recomienda revisar su el modelo de ECM es correcto y el modelo de BCM es correcto; 2. Si todos son correctos, puede revisar si hay interferencia en el bus;</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดของ CRC; คำแนะนำการซ่อม: 1. ขอแนะนำให้ตรวจสอบว่ารุ่นของ ECM ถูกต้อง และรุ่นของ BCM ถูกต้อง; 2. ถ้าถูกต้องทั้งสองรายการ คุณสามารถตรวจสอบว่ามีการรบกวนในบัสหรือไม่;</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are: reading and writing memory errors; repair prompt: "1. BCM KL30 retries the service after power down;
2. Replace BCM;</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：读写内存错误；返修提示："1，BCM KL30 下电后重试该服务；
2, 更换BCM；"

</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5806_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: errores de memoria de lectura y escritura; aviso de reparación: "1. BCM KL30 reintenta el servicio después de apagado;
2. Reemplazar el BCM;</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดในการอ่านและการเขียนหน่วยความจำ; คำแนะนำการซ่อม: "1. BCM KL30 ลองใช้บริการอีกครั้งหลังจากปิดระบบ;
2. เปลี่ยน BCM;</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure of anti-theft matching due to: no SK</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：无SK
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5806_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate anti-robo debida a: no hay SK</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มี SK</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure of anti-theft matching due to: no PIN code</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：无PIN码
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5806_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate anti-robo debida a: no hay código NIP</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีรหัส PIN</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure of anti-theft matching due to: no VIN code</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：无VIN码
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5806_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate anti-robo debida a: no hay código VIN</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีรหัส VIN</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>No ECM.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：No ECM.</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5808_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>No hay ECM.</MX>
      <TH>ไม่มี ECM</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ECM has SK.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：ECM has SK.</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5808_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>El ECM tiene SK.</MX>
      <TH>ECM มี SK</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ECM has PIN.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：ECM has PIN.</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5808_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>El ECM tiene NIP.</MX>
      <TH>ECM มี PIN</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Virgin ECM.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：Virgin ECM.</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5808_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>ECM virgen.</MX>
      <TH>ECM ที่ไม่มีข้อมูลใดๆ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reason for the failure of anti-theft matching is that ECM has learned PIN code, but PIN is inconsistent.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：ECM已学习PIN码，但PIN不一致
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5809_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La razón para la falla de empate anti-robo es que el ECM programó el código NIP, pero el NIP es inconsistente.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก ECM ได้เรียนรู้รหัส PIN แล้ว แต่ PIN ไม่สอดคล้องกัน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reason for the failure of anti-theft matching is: IMMO is not locked; repair prompt: "1, read the status of BCM IMMO module;
2. Ensure that BCM has the correct PIN, SK, VIN and lock BCM "</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：IMMO未锁定；返修提示："1, 读取BCM IMMO模块状态；
2, 确保BCM具备正确的PIN，SK，VIN后锁定BCM"

</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5809_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>La razón para la falla del empate anti-robo es: IMMO no bloqueado; aviso de reparación: "1. lea el estado del módulo IMMO de BCM;
2. Asegúrese que el BCM tenga el NIP, SK, VIN correctos y bloquee el BCM "</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก IMMO ไม่ล็อค; คำแนะนำการซ่อม: "1. อ่านสถานะของโมดูล BCM IMMO;
2. ต้องแน่ใจว่า BCM มี PIN, SK, VIN ที่ถูกต้อง และ BCM ล็อคอยู่ "</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure of anti-theft matching due to invalid PIN code</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：无效的PIN码
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5809_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate anti-robo debida a código NIP no válido</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากรหัส PIN ไม่ถูกต้อง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure of anti-theft matching due to ECM communication error</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：ECM通讯错误
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5809_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>Falla de empate anti-robo debida a error de comunicación de ECM</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดในการติดต่อสื่อสาร ECM</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reasons for the failure of anti-theft matching are: CRC error; repair tips: 1. It is recommended to check whether the ECM model is correct and the BCM model is correct; 2. If they are all correct, you can check whether there is interference in the bus;</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：CRC错误；返修提示：1，建议排查ECM型号是否正确，BCM型号是否正确；2，如果均正确，可以检查总线是否存在干扰；

</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_RC5809_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>Las razones para la falla del empate anti-robo son: error de CRC; consejos de reparación: 1. Se recomienda revisar su el modelo de ECM es correcto y el modelo de BCM es correcto; 2. Si todos son correctos, puede revisar si hay interferencia en el bus;</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดของ CRC; คำแนะนำการซ่อม: 1. ขอแนะนำให้ตรวจสอบว่ารุ่นของ ECM ถูกต้อง และรุ่นของ BCM ถูกต้อง; 2. ถ้าถูกต้องทั้งสองรายการ คุณสามารถตรวจสอบว่ามีการรบกวนในบัสหรือไม่;</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reason for the failure of anti-theft matching is: IMMO not locked.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：IMMO not locked.</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_REC807_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La razón para la falla del empate anti-robo es: IMMO no bloqueado.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก IMMO ไม่ล็อค</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The anti-theft matching failed because PIN writing failed.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：PIN写入失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_REC807_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>El empate anti-robo falló debido a falla de escritura de NIP.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเขียน PIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The anti-theft matching failed because SK writing failed.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：SK写入失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_REC807_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>El empate anti-robo falló debido a falla de escritura de SK.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเขียน SK ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reason for the failure of anti-theft matching is the failure of VIN writing</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配失败，原因为：VIN写入失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_REC807_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>La razón para la falla del empate anti-robo es la falla de escritura de VIN</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเขียน VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Number of keys matched:</EN>
      <CH>已匹配钥匙数量：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Tip1_1</FL>
      <MX>Número de llaves coincidentes:</MX>
      <TH>จำนวนกุญแจที่จับคู่แล้ว:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Number of remaining matching keys:</EN>
      <CH> 剩余匹配钥匙数量：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Tip1_2</FL>
      <MX>Número de llaves coincidentes restantes:</MX>
      <TH>จำนวนกุญแจที่จะจับคู่ที่เหลืออยู่:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>. Are keys added?</EN>
      <CH>。是否添加钥匙？</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Tip1_3</FL>
      <MX>. ¿Se agregaron llaves?</MX>
      <TH>มีการเพิ่มกุญแจหรือไม่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>keys,Are you sure you want to remove all keys that match?</EN>
      <CH>把钥匙，确实要删除已匹配的所有钥匙？</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Tip1_4</FL>
      <MX>llaves, ¿Está seguro que desea eliminar todas las llaves que coinciden?</MX>
      <TH>กุญแจ คุณแน่ใจว่าคุณต้องการลบกุญแจทั้งหมดที่จับคู่หรือไม่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The number of key matches has reached the maximum.</EN>
      <CH>钥匙匹配数已达最大。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Common_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>El número de llaves coincidentes alcanzó el máximo.</MX>
      <TH>จำนวนกุญแจที่จับคู่ถึงจำนวนสูงสุดแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Delete key result upload failed, the reason is: upload key result upload failed.</EN>
      <CH>删除钥匙结果上传失败，原因为：上传删除钥匙结果失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_DeleteKey_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falla de carga de resultado de eliminación de llave, razón: falla de carga de resultado de llave.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการลบกุญแจล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการอัพโหลดผลของกุญแจล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The key was deleted and uploaded successfully. Please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>删除钥匙结果上传成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_DeleteKey_Success</FL>
      <MX>La llave se eliminó y cargó con éxito. Cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การลบกุญแจและการอัพโหลดสำเร็จแล้ว ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Key deleted successfully.</EN>
      <CH>删除钥匙成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_DeleteKey_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Llave eliminada con éxito.</MX>
      <TH>ลบกุญแจสำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Anti-theft matching results upload failure, the reason is: upload multi-function version of the results failed.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配结果上传失败，原因为：上传多功能版结果失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Mult_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falla de carga de resultados de empate anti-robo, razón: falla de versión multifuncional de carga de resultados.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการอัพโหลดเวอร์ชั่นแบบมัลติฟังก์ชันล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Security match successful.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Mult_Success</FL>
      <MX>Empate de seguridad exitoso.</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่ระบบนิรภัยสำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Anti-theft matching result uploaded successfully, please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>防盗匹配结果上传成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Mult_Success1</FL>
      <MX>Resultado de empate anti-robo cargado con éxito, gire el interruptor de ignición a la posición OFF (apagado) por más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการจับคู่ระบบกันขโมยสำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ECM reset result upload failed, because: upload ECM reset result failed.</EN>
      <CH>ECM复位结果上传失败，原因为：上传ECM复位结果失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Reset_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falló la carga de resultado de restablecimiento de ECM debido a: falla de resultado de restablecimiento de ECM de carga.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการรีเซ็ต ECM ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการอัพโหลดผลการรีเซ็ต ECM ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reason of ECM reset failure is: reset failure.</EN>
      <CH>ECM复位失败，原因为：复位失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Reset_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>La razón de falla de restablecimiento de ECM es: falla de restablecimiento.</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ECM ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการรีเซ็ตล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ECM reset failed due to invalid PIN code</EN>
      <CH>ECM复位失败，原因为：无效的PIN码</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Reset_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Restablecimiento de ECM falló debido a código NIP no válido</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ECM ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากรหัส PIN ไม่ถูกต้อง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ECM reset failed due to ECM communication error</EN>
      <CH>ECM复位失败，原因为：ECM通讯错误
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Reset_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>Restablecimiento de ECM falló debido a error de comunicación de ECM</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ECM ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดในการติดต่อสื่อสารของ ECM</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ECM reset failed because of an unknown error.</EN>
      <CH>ECM复位失败，原因为：未知错误。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Reset_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>Restablecimiento de ECM falló debido a un error desconocido.</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ECM ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดที่ไม่รู้จัก</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ECM reset result has been uploaded successfully. Please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>ECM复位结果上传成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。
</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Reset_Success</FL>
      <MX>El resultado de restablecimiento de ECM se cargó con éxito. Cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการรีเซ็ต ECM สำเร็จแล้ว ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>1. ECM reset IMMO anti-theft information must be carried out on the "original vehicle";\n2, the IMMO function of vehicle BCM must be normal, otherwise there may be the risk that ECM reset fails or the key cannot continue to use after the successful reset;Item 3. IMMO anti-theft information stored in the ECM will be permanently deleted after successful reset;Item 4. After successful reset, the ECM can be used for this vehicle and other vehicles to re-match IMMO anti-theft system.</EN>
      <CH>1、ECM复位IMMO防盗信息，必须在“原车”上进行；\n2、车辆BCM的IMMO功能必须正常，否则将有可能出现ECM复位失败或复位成功后钥匙无法继续使用风险；\n3、复位成功后，该ECM内的存储的IMMO防盗信息将被永久删除；\n4、复位成功后，该ECM将可用于本车和其他车辆，重新匹配IMMO防盗系统。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Reset_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>1. La información anti-robo de IMMO de restablecimiento de ECM se debe realizar en el "vehículo original"; \n2. la función IMMO del BCM del vehículo debe ser normal, de otra manera puede haber un riesgo de que el restablecimiento del ECM falle o la llave no puede continuar usándose después del restablecimiento exitoso; Elemento 3. La información anti-robo de IMMO almacenada en el ECM se eliminará permanentemente después del restablecimiento exitoso; Elemento 4. Después del restablecimiento exitoso, el ECM se puede usar para este vehículo y otros vehículos para volver a empatar el sistema anti-robo IMMO.</MX>
      <TH>1. การรีเซ็ต ECM สำหรับข้อมูลระบบกันขโมย IMMO จะต้องทำบน "รถคันเดิม";\n2. ฟังก์ชัน IMMO ของ BCM ของรถจะต้องเป็นปกติ ไม่เช่นนั้นแล้ว อาจมีความเสี่ยงที่การรีเซ็ต ECM ล้มเหลว หรือไม่สามารถใช้งานกุญแจต่อได้หลังจากที่การรีเซ็ตสำเร็จแล้ว; 3. ข้อมูลระบบกันขโมย IMMO ที่บันทึกอยู่ใน ECM จะถูกลบไปโดยถาวรหลังจากการรีเซ็ตสำเร็จแล้ว: 4. หลังจากการรีเซ็ตสำเร็จแล้ว จะสามารถใช้ ECM สำหรับรถคันนี้และรถคันอื่นๆ ในการจับคู่กับระบบกันขโมย IMMO อีกครั้งได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ECM reset successful! Please turn OFF the key at least 45 seconds before removing the engine control module (ECM).</EN>
      <CH>ECM复位成功！请将钥匙至OFF，至少45秒后，才能拆卸发动机控制模块（ECM）</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_IMMO_Reset_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>¡Restablecimiento de ECM exitoso! Apague la llave por lo menos 45 segundos después de retirar el módulo de control del motor (ECM).</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ECM สำเร็จแล้ว ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลาอย่างน้อย 45 วินาที ก่อนที่จะถอดโมดูลควบคุมเครื่องยนต์ (ECM)</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The BCM online configuration failed because OBD is not connected.</EN>
      <CH>BCM在线配置失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_OnlineCon_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de BCM falló debido a que el OBD no está conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ BCM ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The BCM online configuration failed.</EN>
      <CH>BCM在线配置失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_OnlineCon_Fail10</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de BCM falló.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ BCM ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The BCM online configuration result upload failed.</EN>
      <CH>BCM在线配置结果上传失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_OnlineCon_Fail11</FL>
      <MX>Falla de carga de resultado de configuración en línea de BCM.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ BCM ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The BCM online configuration failed because the after-sales server could not be accessed.</EN>
      <CH>BCM在线配置失败，原因为：无法访问售后服务器。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_OnlineCon_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea BCM falló debido a que no se pudo tener acceso al servidor post-venta.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ BCM ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าถึงเซิร์ฟเวอร์หลังการขายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The BCM online configuration failed because VIN confirms failure.</EN>
      <CH>BCM在线配置失败，原因为：VIN确认失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_OnlineCon_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de BCM falló debido a que el VIN confirma la falla.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ BCM ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถยืนยัน VIN ได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The BCM online configuration failed because: the car does not need online configuration or there is no car information on the server.</EN>
      <CH>BCM在线配置失败，原因为：该车无需在线配置或服务器上无该车信息。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_OnlineCon_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de BCM falló debido a que el vehículo no necesita configuración en línea o no hay información de vehículo en el servidor.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ BCM ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากรถไม่จำเป็นต้องทำการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ หรือไม่มีข้อมูลของรถอยู่บนเซิร์ฟเวอร์</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The BCM online configuration failed because failed to enter the extended session.</EN>
      <CH>BCM在线配置失败，原因为：进入扩展会话失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_OnlineCon_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de BCM falló debido a que falló en ingresar la sesión extendida.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ BCM ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าสู่เซสชั่นแบบขยายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The BCM online configuration failed because security access failed.</EN>
      <CH>BCM在线配置失败，原因为：安全访问失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_OnlineCon_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de BCM falló debido a falla de acceso de seguridad.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ BCM ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเข้าถึงระบบนิรภัยล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The BCM online configuration failed because write online configuration failed.</EN>
      <CH>BCM在线配置失败，原因为：写入在线配置失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_OnlineCon_Fail7</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de BCM falló debido a que falló la escritura de configuración en línea.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ BCM ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเขียนการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The BCM online configuration failed because failed to read the online configuration.</EN>
      <CH>BCM在线配置失败，原因为：读取在线配置失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_OnlineCon_Fail8</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de BCM falló debido a que falló en leer la configuración en línea.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ BCM ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถอ่านการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The BCM online configuration failed because failure to clear fault code.</EN>
      <CH>BCM在线配置失败，原因为：清故障码失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_OnlineCon_Fail9</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de BCM falló debido a: falla en borrar el código de falla.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ BCM ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการลบรหัสข้อบกพร่องล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The online configuration result of BCM has been uploaded successfully. Please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>BCM在线配置结果上传成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_OnlineCon_Success</FL>
      <MX>El resultado de configuración en línea de BCM se cargó con éxito. Cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ BCM สำเร็จแล้ว ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The BCM online configuration was successful.</EN>
      <CH>BCM在线配置成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_OnlineCon_Success1</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de BCM fue exitosa.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ BCM สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failed to add the key, the reason is: BCM program error, please contact BCM engineer to deal with!</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙失败，原因为：BCM程序错误，请联系BCM工程师处理！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_RKE_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falla en agregar la llave, razón: error de programa de BCM, ¡póngase en contacto con el ingeniero de BCM para resolverlo!</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดในการตั้งโปรแกรม BCM โปรดติดต่อวิศวกร BCM เพื่อแก้ไขปัญหา</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Add key failed because: add failed.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙失败，原因为：添加失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_RKE_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Falla de adición de llave debido a: falló la adición.</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเพิ่มล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failed to add key, because: key query error.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙失败，原因为：钥匙查询错误。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_RKE_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Falla en agregar la llave, debido a: error de búsqueda de llave.</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดในการสอบถามกุญแจ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The key was added successfully. Please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_RKE_Success</FL>
      <MX>La llave se agregó con éxito. Cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>เพิ่มกุญแจสำเร็จแล้ว ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Rematching keys will delete all previous keys. Do you want to continue?</EN>
      <CH>重新匹配钥匙会删除之前的所有钥匙，是否继续？</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_RKE_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Volver a empatar las llaves eliminará todas las llaves anteriores. ¿Desea continuar?</MX>
      <TH>การจับคู่กุญแจอีกครั้งจะเป็นการลบกุญแจก่อนหน้านี้ทั้งหมด คุณต้องการทำต่อหรือไม่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please press both the remote unlock key and the lock key to exceed 2S</EN>
      <CH>请同时按下遥控解锁键和闭锁键超过2S</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_RKE_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Presione la tecla de desbloqueo y la tecla de bloqueo remoto más de 2S</MX>
      <TH>กดปุ่มปลดล็อคและปุ่มล็อคบนรีโมทพร้อมกันค้างไว้เป็นเวลานานกว่า 2 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Does it continue to match the second key?</EN>
      <CH>是否继续匹配第二把钥匙？</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_RKE_Tip3</FL>
      <MX>¿Desea continuar empatando la segunda llave?</MX>
      <TH>ทำการจับคู่กุญแจชุดที่สองต่อหรือไม่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please change the second key and press the remote unlock key and lock key more than 2S at the same time</EN>
      <CH>请换第二把钥匙并同时按下遥控解锁键和闭锁键超过2S</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_RKE_Tip4</FL>
      <MX>Cambie la segunda llave y presione la tecla de desbloqueo y la tecla de bloqueo remoto más de 2S al mismo tiempo</MX>
      <TH>เปลี่ยนเป็นกุญแจชุดที่สอง และกดปุ่มปลดล็อคและปุ่มล็อคบนรีโมทพร้อมกันค้างไว้เป็นเวลานานกว่า 2 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Maximum support matches 2 remote control keys, currently matches 2</EN>
      <CH>最大支持匹配2把遥控钥匙，当前已匹配2把</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_RKE_Tip5</FL>
      <MX>El soporte máximo empata 2 llaves de control remoto, actualmente empata 2</MX>
      <TH>รองรับการจับคู่กุญแจรีโมทคอนโทรลสูงสุด 2 ชุด กุญแจที่จับคู่ไว้ในขณะนี้ 2 ชุด</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>One-key startup configuration failed because OBD was not connected.</EN>
      <CH>写入失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_WriteIMMO_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de arranque de una llave falló debido a que el OBD no estaba conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าการเริ่มทำงานด้วยกุญแจชุดเดียวล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Write failed.</EN>
      <CH>写入失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_WriteIMMO_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Falla de escritura.</MX>
      <TH>การเขียนล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Write failed, get ESK failed.</EN>
      <CH>写入失败，获取ESK失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_WriteIMMO_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Falla de escritura, falló el ESK.</MX>
      <TH>การเขียนล้มเหลว การรับ ESK ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Write failed, write VIN failed.</EN>
      <CH>写入失败，写入VIN失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_WriteIMMO_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>Falla de escritura, falló la escritura de VIN.</MX>
      <TH>การเขียนล้มเหลว การเขียน VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Write successfully.</EN>
      <CH>写入成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_BCM_WriteIMMO_Success</FL>
      <MX>Escritura exitosa.</MX>
      <TH>การเขียนสำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The user has chosen to end.</EN>
      <CH>用户已选择结束。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Common_ChoiceEnd</FL>
      <MX>El usuario eligió finalizar.</MX>
      <TH>ผู้ใช้เลือกที่จะสิ้นสุด</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please confirm whether the current vehicle VIN is:</EN>
      <CH>请确认当前车辆VIN是否为:</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Common_ConfirmVIN</FL>
      <MX>Por favor confirme si el VIN del vehículo actual es:</MX>
      <TH>โปรดยืนยันว่า VIN ของรถในปัจจุบันคือ:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Security access failed.</EN>
      <CH>安全访问失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Common_SAFail</FL>
      <MX>Falló el acceso de seguridad.</MX>
      <TH>การเข้าถึงระบบนิรภัยล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Switch the power of the whole vehicle to ON state</EN>
      <CH>将整车电源切换至ON状态</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Common_TurnON</FL>
      <MX>Cambie la energía del vehículo completo al estado ON (encendido)</MX>
      <TH>ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจของรถไปที่ตำแหน่ง ON</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please enter VIN manually</EN>
      <CH>请手动输入VIN</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Common_WriteVIN</FL>
      <MX>¡Por favor introduzca el VIN manualmente</MX>
      <TH>โปรดป้อน VIN ในแบบแมนนวล</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>CSM After-sales inspection failed.</EN>
      <CH>CSM售后检测失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_CSM_Instructions_Fail</FL>
      <MX>Falló la inspección post-venta de CSM.</MX>
      <TH>การตรวจสอบระบบหลังการขาย CSM ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>CSM after sales detection is successful, please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>CSM售后检测成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_CSM_Instructions_Success</FL>
      <MX>La detección post-venta de CSM es exitosa, cambie el interruptor de ignición a la posición OFF durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การตรวจสอบระบบหลังการขาย CSM สำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Parity clutch pressure is beyond the scope</EN>
      <CH>奇偶离合器压力都超出范围</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error1</FL>
      <MX>La presión de embrague par e impar es mayor al alcance</MX>
      <TH>ความดันคลัตช์เกียร์เลขคู่และเลขคี่อยู่นอกขอบเขตที่กำหนดไว้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>6 / R fork the median position is not in the normal range</EN>
      <CH>6/R拨叉中位位置不在正常范围</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error10</FL>
      <MX>Posición neutral de horquilla 6 / R no está en el rango normal</MX>
      <TH>ตำแหน่งปกติของก้ามปูเปลี่ยนเกียร์ 6/R ไม่อยู่ในช่วงปกติ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>1 gear position is not in the normal range</EN>
      <CH>1档齿轮位置不在正常范围</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error11</FL>
      <MX>La posición de velocidad 1 no esté en el rango normal</MX>
      <TH>ตำแหน่งเกียร์ 1 ไม่อยู่ในช่วงปกติ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>2 gear position is not in the normal range</EN>
      <CH>2档齿轮位置不在正常范围</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error12</FL>
      <MX>La posición de velocidad 2 no esté en el rango normal</MX>
      <TH>ตำแหน่งเกียร์ 2 ไม่อยู่ในช่วงปกติ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>3 gear position is not in the normal range</EN>
      <CH>3档齿轮位置不在正常范围</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error13</FL>
      <MX>La posición de velocidad 3 no esté en el rango normal</MX>
      <TH>ตำแหน่งเกียร์ 3 ไม่อยู่ในช่วงปกติ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>4 gear position is not in the normal range</EN>
      <CH>4档齿轮位置不在正常范围</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error14</FL>
      <MX>La posición de velocidad 4 no esté en el rango normal</MX>
      <TH>ตำแหน่งเกียร์ 4 ไม่อยู่ในช่วงปกติ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>5 gear position is not in the normal range</EN>
      <CH>5档齿轮位置不在正常范围</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error15</FL>
      <MX>La posición de velocidad 5 no esté en el rango normal</MX>
      <TH>ตำแหน่งเกียร์ 5 ไม่อยู่ในช่วงปกติ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>6 gear position is not in the normal range</EN>
      <CH>6档齿轮位置不在正常范围</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error16</FL>
      <MX>La posición de velocidad 6 no esté en el rango normal</MX>
      <TH>ตำแหน่งเกียร์ 6 ไม่อยู่ในช่วงปกติ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Reverse gear position is not in the normal range</EN>
      <CH>倒档齿轮位置不在正常范围</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error17</FL>
      <MX>La posición de velocidad de reversa no esté en el rango normal</MX>
      <TH>ตำแหน่งเกียร์ถอยหลังไม่อยู่ในช่วงปกติ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Unable to find a strange clutch contact</EN>
      <CH>奇离合器接触点无法找到</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error18</FL>
      <MX>No se puede encontrar un contacto de embrague impar</MX>
      <TH>ไม่พบจุดสัมผัสของคลัตช์เกียร์เลขคี่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>I cannot find the clutch contact</EN>
      <CH>偶离合器接触点无法找到</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error19</FL>
      <MX>No puedo encontrar el contacto de embrague</MX>
      <TH>ไม่พบจุดสัมผัสของคลัตช์</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Only the odd clutch pressure is beyond the scope</EN>
      <CH>只有奇离合器的压力超出范围</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error2</FL>
      <MX>Sólo la presión del embrague impar es mayor al alcance</MX>
      <TH>ความดันคลัตช์เกียร์เลขคี่เท่านั้นที่อยู่นอกขอบเขตที่กำหนดไว้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Function request timeout</EN>
      <CH>功能请求超时</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error20</FL>
      <MX>Expiración de tiempo de solicitud de función</MX>
      <TH>การร้องขอการทำงานหมดเวลาแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Not in p mode</EN>
      <CH>不在p档</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error21</FL>
      <MX>No se encuentra en modo p</MX>
      <TH>ไม่อยู่ในโหมด P</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The engine is not running</EN>
      <CH>发动机未运行</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error22</FL>
      <MX>El motor no está en funcionamiento</MX>
      <TH>เครื่องยนต์ไม่ทำงาน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Does not meet the condition of temperature (clutch oil temperature 45-70 ℃, the engine temperature 80-140 ℃)</EN>
      <CH>温度条件不满足（离合器油温45-70℃，发动机水温80-140℃）</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error23</FL>
      <MX>No cumple la condición de temperatura (temperatura de aceite de embrague 45-70 ℃, temperatura de motor 80-140 ℃)</MX>
      <TH>ไม่เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขเกี่ยวกับอุณหภูมิ (อุณหภูมิน้ำมันคลัตช์ 45-70 ℃, อุณหภูมิเครื่องยนต์ 80-140 ℃)</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>DTC gearbox fault codes</EN>
      <CH>DTC变速器有故障码</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error24</FL>
      <MX>Códigos DTC de falla de caja de engranes</MX>
      <TH>DTC รหัสข้อบกพร่องของชุดเกียร์</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Engine torque torque instability</EN>
      <CH>发动机扭矩扭矩不稳定</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error25</FL>
      <MX>Inestabilidad de torque de motor</MX>
      <TH>แรงบิดเครื่องยนต์ไม่คงที่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>An odd number of clutch pressure torque linearity inflection point or exceed the range cannot be found</EN>
      <CH>奇数离合器压力扭矩线性关系拐点无法找到或超出范围</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error26</FL>
      <MX>No se puede encontrar la relación lineal de presión-torque para el embrague impar o excede el rango</MX>
      <TH>ไม่พบการเปลี่ยนแปลงความสัมพันธ์แบบเชิงเส้นระหว่างความดันกับแรงบิดของคลัตช์เกียร์เลขคี่ หรือการเปลี่ยนแปลงเกินช่วงที่กำหนดไว้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Even the clutch pressure torque linearity inflection point or exceed the range cannot be found</EN>
      <CH>偶数离合器压力扭矩线性关系拐点无法找到或超出范围</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error27</FL>
      <MX>No se puede encontrar la relación lineal de presión-torque para el embrague par o excede el rango</MX>
      <TH>ไม่พบการเปลี่ยนแปลงความสัมพันธ์แบบเชิงเส้นระหว่างความดันกับแรงบิดของคลัตช์เกียร์เลขคู่ หรือการเปลี่ยนแปลงเกินช่วงที่กำหนดไว้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>An odd number of clutch pressure torque linearity inflection point since the study values are not stable</EN>
      <CH>奇数离合器压力扭矩线性关系拐点自学习值不稳定</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error28</FL>
      <MX>Número impar de punto de inflexión de linealidad de torque de presión de embrague ya que los valores de programación no son estables</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนแปลงความสัมพันธ์แบบเชิงเส้นระหว่างความดันกับแรงบิดของคลัตช์เกียร์เลขคี่นับตั้งแต่การเรียนรู้ค่าไม่คงที่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Even the clutch pressure torque linearity inflection point since the study values are not stable</EN>
      <CH>偶数离合器压力扭矩线性关系拐点自学习值不稳定</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error29</FL>
      <MX>Número par de punto de inflexión de linealidad de torque de presión de embrague ya que los valores de programación no son estables</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนแปลงความสัมพันธ์แบบเชิงเส้นระหว่างความดันกับแรงบิดของคลัตช์เกียร์เลขคู่นับตั้งแต่การเรียนรู้ค่าไม่คงที่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Only I clutch pressure is beyond the scope</EN>
      <CH>只有偶离合器的压力超出范围</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error3</FL>
      <MX>Sólo la presión del embrague par es mayor al alcance</MX>
      <TH>ความดันคลัตช์เกียร์เลขคู่เท่านั้นที่อยู่นอกขอบเขตที่กำหนดไว้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The speed is not zero</EN>
      <CH>车速不为零</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error30</FL>
      <MX>La velocidad no es cero</MX>
      <TH>ความเร็วไม่เป็นศูนย์</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Communicate transmission ontology</EN>
      <CH>无法与变速器本体通讯</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error31</FL>
      <MX>No se puede comunicar con el cuerpo de la transmisión</MX>
      <TH>ไม่สามารถติดต่อสื่อสารกับระบบเกียร์ได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>TCU internal fault</EN>
      <CH>TCU内部故障</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error32</FL>
      <MX>Falla interna de TCU</MX>
      <TH>ความผิดปกติภายใน TCU</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>An unknown error</EN>
      <CH>未知错误</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error33</FL>
      <MX>Error desconocido</MX>
      <TH>ข้อผิดพลาดที่ไม่รู้จัก</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Parity curve of the clutch monotonicity test failure</EN>
      <CH>奇偶离合器曲线单调性检验失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error4</FL>
      <MX>Falló la prueba de monotonicidad de curva para los embragues impar y par</MX>
      <TH>การทดสอบ Monotonicity ของเส้นกราฟของคลัตช์เกียร์เลขคี่และเกียร์เลขคู่ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Only clutch curve monotonicity test failure</EN>
      <CH>只有奇离合器曲线单调性检验失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error5</FL>
      <MX>Sólo falló la prueba de monotonicidad de curva para los embragues impares</MX>
      <TH>เฉพาะการทดสอบ Monotonicity ของเส้นกราฟของคลัตช์เกียร์เลขคี่เท่านั้นที่ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Only clutch curve monotonicity test failure</EN>
      <CH>只有奇离合器曲线单调性检验失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error6</FL>
      <MX>Sólo falló la prueba de monotonicidad de curva para los embragues impares</MX>
      <TH>เฉพาะการทดสอบ Monotonicity ของเส้นกราฟของคลัตช์เกียร์เลขคี่เท่านั้นที่ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>A third fork the median position is not in the normal range</EN>
      <CH>1/3拨叉中位位置不在正常范围</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error7</FL>
      <MX>Posición neutral de horquilla de tercera no está en el rango normal</MX>
      <TH>ตำแหน่งปกติของก้ามปูเปลี่ยนเกียร์ 3 ไม่อยู่ในช่วงปกติ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>By 2/4 fork the median position is not in the normal range</EN>
      <CH>2/4拨叉中位位置不在正常范围</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error8</FL>
      <MX>Posición neutral de horquilla 2/4 no está en el rango normal</MX>
      <TH>ตำแหน่งปกติของก้ามปูเปลี่ยนเกียร์ 2/4 ไม่อยู่ในช่วงปกติ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>5 / N fork the median position is not in the normal range</EN>
      <CH>5/N拨叉中位位置不在正常范围</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF02_Error9</FL>
      <MX>Posición neutral de horquilla 5 / N no está en el rango normal</MX>
      <TH>ตำแหน่งปกติของก้ามปูเปลี่ยนเกียร์ 5/N ไม่อยู่ในช่วงปกติ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The routine control failed because:</EN>
      <CH>拨叉位置自学习失败(11)</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0201_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>El control de rutina falló debido a:</MX>
      <TH>การควบคุมขั้นตอนการทำงานล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The routine control is completed because:</EN>
      <CH>拨叉位置自学习失败(12)</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0201_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>El control de rutina se completó debido a:</MX>
      <TH>การควบคุมขั้นตอนการทำงานเสร็จสมบูรณ์เนื่องจาก:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The routine control starts successfully. Please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>拨叉位置自学习成功</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0201_Success</FL>
      <MX>El control de rutina inicia con éxito. Cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การเริ่มการควบคุมขั้นตอนการทำงานสำเร็จแล้ว ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Clutch temperature is too high, please wait for the clutch temperature &lt; 70 degree C and try again.</EN>
      <CH>离合器温度过高，请等待离合器温度＜70°C后再试</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0202_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La temperatura del embrague es demasiado alta, espere que la temperatura del embrague sea &lt; 70 grados C e intente de nuevo.</MX>
      <TH>อุณหภูมิคลัตช์สูงเกินไป โปรดรอจนอุณหภูมิคลัตช์ &lt; 70 องศาเซลเซียส แล้วลองอีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Engine water temperature is too high. Please try again after power off for a period of time.</EN>
      <CH>发动机水温过高，请断电一段时间后重试</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0202_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Temperatura de agua del motor demasiado alta. Espere de nuevo después de apagar por un periodo de tiempo.</MX>
      <TH>อุณหภูมิน้ำหล่อเย็นเครื่องยนต์สูงเกินไป โปรดลองอีกครั้งหลังจากดับเครื่องแล้วเป็นระยะเวลาช่วงหนึ่ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Ambient atmospheric temperature does not satisfy self-learning conditions</EN>
      <CH>环境大气温度不满足自学习条件</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0202_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>La temperatura atmosférica ambiente no cumple las condiciones de programación automática</MX>
      <TH>อุณหภูมิอากาศภายนอกไม่เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขสำหรับการเรียนรู้ค่าด้วยตัวเอง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The routine control failed because:</EN>
      <CH>离合器啮合点自学习失败(11)</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0202_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>El control de rutina falló debido a:</MX>
      <TH>การควบคุมขั้นตอนการทำงานล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The routine control is completed for the following reasons:</EN>
      <CH>离合器啮合点自学习失败(12)</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0202_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>El control de rutina se completó por las siguientes razones:</MX>
      <TH>การควบคุมขั้นตอนการทำงานเสร็จสมบูรณ์เนื่องจากสาเหตุต่อไปนี้:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The routine control is successful, please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>离合器啮合点自学习成功</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0202_Success</FL>
      <MX>El control de rutina es exitoso, cambie el interruptor de ignición a la posición OFF durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การควบคุมขั้นตอนการทำงานสำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Continue high idling speed to heat the clutch temperature to 45 C-70 C\n Current clutch temperature:</EN>
      <CH>请持续高怠速以加热离合器温度至45°C-70°C之间\n当前离合器温度：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0202_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Continúe en velocidad de marcha en vacío alta para calentar la temperatura del embrague a 45 C-70 C\n Temperatura de embrague actual:</MX>
      <TH>เดินเครื่องยนต์ที่รอบเดินเบาระดับสูงต่อไปเพื่อให้อุณหภูมิคลัตช์สูงขึ้นจนอยู่ในช่วง 45 -70 องศาเซลเซียส\n อุณหภูมิคลัตช์ในปัจจุบัน:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Continue high idling speed to heat engine water temperature between 80 C and 140 C \n Current engine water temperature:</EN>
      <CH>请持续高怠速以加热发动机水温至80°C-140°C之间\n当前发动机水温：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0202_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Continúe en velocidad de marcha en vacío alta para calentar la temperatura del agua del motor entre 80 C y 140 C \n Temperatura de agua de motor actual:</MX>
      <TH>เดินเครื่องยนต์ที่รอบเดินเบาระดับสูงต่อไปเพื่อให้อุณหภูมิน้ำหล่อเย็นเครื่องยนต์สูงขึ้นจนอยู่ในช่วง 80 -140 องศาเซลเซียส\n อุณหภูมิน้ำหล่อเย็นเครื่องยนต์ในปัจจุบัน:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The routine control failed because:</EN>
      <CH>离合器压力电流映射曲线自学习失败(11)</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0203_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>El control de rutina falló debido a:</MX>
      <TH>การควบคุมขั้นตอนการทำงานล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The routine control is completed for the following reasons:</EN>
      <CH>例离合器压力电流映射曲线自学习失败(12)程控制完成，原因为：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0203_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>El control de rutina se completó por las siguientes razones:</MX>
      <TH>การควบคุมขั้นตอนการทำงานเสร็จสมบูรณ์เนื่องจากสาเหตุต่อไปนี้:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Clutch temperature is too high, please wait for the clutch temperature &lt; 70 degree C and try again.</EN>
      <CH>阀体温度过高，请等待阀体温度＜50°C后再试</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0203_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>La temperatura del embrague es demasiado alta, espere que la temperatura del embrague sea &lt; 70 grados C e intente de nuevo.</MX>
      <TH>อุณหภูมิคลัตช์สูงเกินไป โปรดรอจนอุณหภูมิคลัตช์ &lt; 70 องศาเซลเซียส แล้วลองอีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The routine control is successful, please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>离合器压力电流映射曲线自学习成功</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0203_Success</FL>
      <MX>El control de rutina es exitoso, cambie el interruptor de ignición a la posición OFF durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การควบคุมขั้นตอนการทำงานสำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Continue high idling speed to heat the clutch temperature to 45 C-70 C \n Current clutch temperature:</EN>
      <CH>阀体温度低于35℃\n当前温度：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0203_Tip1_1</FL>
      <MX>Continúe en velocidad de marcha en vacío alta para calentar la temperatura del embrague a 45 C-70 C\n Temperatura de embrague actual:</MX>
      <TH>เดินเครื่องยนต์ที่รอบเดินเบาระดับสูงต่อไปเพื่อให้อุณหภูมิคลัตช์สูงขึ้นจนอยู่ในช่วง 45 -70 องศาเซลเซียส\n อุณหภูมิคลัตช์ในปัจจุบัน:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>℃, please continuous high idle speed to heat the body temperature to 35 ° C - 50 ° C</EN>
      <CH>℃，请持续高怠速以加热阀体温度至35°C-50°C之间</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0203_Tip1_2</FL>
      <MX>℃, continúe la velocidad de marcha en vacío alta para calentar la temperatura de la carrocería a 35 ° C - 50 ° C</MX>
      <TH>℃ เดินเครื่องยนต์ที่รอบเดินเบาระดับสูงต่อไปเพื่อให้อุณหภูมิตัวถังสูงขึ้นจนอยู่ในช่วง 35 - 50 องศาเซลเซียส</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please make sure that the following conditions are met and then click the "next"
1. Please send diagnostic apparatus connected to the vehicle OBD connector
2. The vehicle on the electric start
3. The vehicle hangs in P mode
4. The engine at idle speed control
5. The speed of 0
6. The gearbox body oil temperature of 35 ° C - 50 ° C
7. No claudication fault</EN>
      <CH>请确保以下条件均满足后点击“下一步”
1.请将诊断仪连接至车辆OBD接头
2.整车上电启动
3.整车挂入P档
4.发动机处于怠速控制
5.车速为0
6.变速箱阀体油温为35°C-50°C
7.无跛行故障</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0203_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Asegúrese que las siguientes condiciones se cumplan y después dé clic en "siguiente"
1. Conecte la herramienta de exploración al receptáculo OBD del vehículo
2. Vehículo en arranque eléctrico
3. Vehículo colocado en modo P
4. Motor en control de velocidad de marcha en vacío
5. Velocidad de 0
6. Temperatura de aceite de cuerpo de caja de velocidades de 35 ° C - 50 ° C
7. No hay falla de operación de emergencia</MX>
      <TH>ตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าสภาพต่างๆ เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขต่อไปนี้ แล้วคลิก "ถัดไป"
1. โปรดเชื่อมต่อเครื่องมือสแกนเข้ากับปลั๊ก OBD ของรถ
2. รถอยู่ในโหมดสตาร์ทด้วยไฟฟ้า
3. รถอยู่ในโหมด P
4. เครื่องยนต์ทำงานที่รอบเดินเบา
5. ความเร็วเป็น 0
6. อุณหภูมิชุดเกียร์อยู่ระหว่าง 35 - 50 องศาเซลเซียส
7. ไม่มีความผิดปกติใดๆ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The routine control failed because of data incompatibility.</EN>
      <CH>例程控制失败，原因为：数据不兼容。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF04_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>El control de rutina falló debido a incompatibilidad de datos.</MX>
      <TH>การควบคุมขั้นตอนการทำงานล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อมูลไม่สามารถใช้ร่วมกันได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The routine control failed because: function request timeout.</EN>
      <CH>例程控制失败，原因为：功能请求超时。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF04_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>El control de rutina falló debido a: expiración de tiempo de solicitud de función.</MX>
      <TH>การควบคุมขั้นตอนการทำงานล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการร้องขอการทำงานหมดเวลาแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Routine control failed because:</EN>
      <CH>例程控制失败，原因为：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0501_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Control de rutina falló debido a:</MX>
      <TH>การควบคุมขั้นตอนการทำงานล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Routine control is completed:</EN>
      <CH>例程控制完成：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_CF0501_Success1</FL>
      <MX>Control de rutina completado:</MX>
      <TH>การควบคุมขั้นตอนการทำงานเสร็จสมบูรณ์แล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The routine control failed because: failed to enter extension mode.</EN>
      <CH>例程控制失败，原因为：进入扩展模式失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_Common_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>El control de rutina falló debido a: falló en entrar en modo de extensión.</MX>
      <TH>การควบคุมขั้นตอนการทำงานล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าสู่โหมดแบบขยายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The routine control failed because unknown error.</EN>
      <CH>例程控制失败，原因为：未知错误。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_Common_FailUnknown</FL>
      <MX>El control de rutina falló debido a error desconocido.</MX>
      <TH>การควบคุมขั้นตอนการทำงานล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดที่ไม่รู้จัก</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The routine routine control is successful. Please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>例程控制成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCT_RC_Common_Success</FL>
      <MX>El control de rutina es exitoso. Cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การควบคุมขั้นตอนการทำงานสำเร็จแล้ว ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The DCU online configuration failed because OBD is not connected.</EN>
      <CH>DCU在线配置失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCU_OnlineCon_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de DCU falló debido a que el OBD no está conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ DCU ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The DCU online configuration failed because the after-sales server could not be accessed.</EN>
      <CH>DCU在线配置失败，原因为：无法访问售后服务器。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCU_OnlineCon_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea DCU falló debido a que no se pudo tener acceso al servidor post-venta.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ DCU ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าถึงเซิร์ฟเวอร์หลังการขายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The DCU online configuration failed because VIN failed to confirm.</EN>
      <CH>DCU在线配置失败，原因为：VIN确认失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCU_OnlineCon_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de DCU falló debido a que el VIN falló en confirmar.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ DCU ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการยืนยัน VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>DCU online configuration failed because: the car does not need online configuration or there is no car information on the server.</EN>
      <CH>DCU在线配置失败，原因为：该车无需在线配置或服务器上无该车信息。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCU_OnlineCon_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de DCU falló debido a que el vehículo no necesita configuración en línea o no hay información de vehículo en el servidor.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ DCU ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากรถไม่จำเป็นต้องทำการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ หรือไม่มีข้อมูลของรถอยู่บนเซิร์ฟเวอร์</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The DCU online configuration failed.</EN>
      <CH>DCU在线配置失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCU_OnlineCon_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de DCU falló.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ DCU ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The DCU online configuration result upload failed.</EN>
      <CH>DCU在线配置结果上传失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCU_OnlineCon_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>Falla de carga de resultado de configuración en línea de DCU.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ DCU ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>DCU online configuration succeeded.</EN>
      <CH>DCU在线配置成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCU_OnlineCon_Success</FL>
      <MX>Éxito de configuración en línea de DCU.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ DCU สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>DCU online configuration results uploaded successfully, please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>DCU在线配置结果上传成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCU_OnlineCon_Success1</FL>
      <MX>Resultados de configuración en línea de DCU cargados con éxito, gire el interruptor de ignición a la posición OFF (apagado) por más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลลัพธ์การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ DCU สำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The DCU Yaw rate calibration failed because OBD was not connected.</EN>
      <CH>DCU偏航率标定失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCUCali_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de tasa de viraje de DCU falló debido a que el OBD no estaba conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบอัตราการส่ายของ DCU ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The DCU Yaw rate calibration failed because yaw rate sensor calibration failure.</EN>
      <CH>DCU偏航率传感器标定失败,原因为：偏航率传感器标定失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCUCali_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de tasa de viraje de DCU falló debido a falla de calibración de sensor de tasa de viraje.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบอัตราการส่ายของ DCU ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการปรับเทียบเซ็นเซอร์อัตราการส่ายของ DCU ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The DCU yaw rate sensor calibration is successful, please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>DCU偏航率传感器标定成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCUCali_Success</FL>
      <MX>La calibración del sensor de tasa de viraje de DCU es exitosa, cambie el interruptor de ignición a la posición OFF durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบเซ็นเซอร์อัตราการส่ายของ DCU สำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>1. Do not start the engine and leave the vehicle in a static state. 2. The vehicle shall be placed on the horizontal ground.3. One person or only one person, sitting in the driver's seat (no additional load on the vehicle).</EN>
      <CH>1.不启动发动机，车辆处于静止状态2.车辆需置于水平地面3.需一人也只能一人，坐于驾驶员位置（车上不能再有额外的载荷）</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_DCUCali_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>1. NO arranque el motor y deje el vehículo en estado estático. 2. El vehículo se colocará en terreno horizontal. 3. Sólo una persona, sentada en el asiento del conductor (sin carga adicional en el vehículo).</MX>
      <TH>1. ไม่ต้องสตาร์ทเครื่องยนต์ และจอดรถทิ้งไว้ 2. รถจะต้องจอดอยู่บนพื้นระดับ 3. มีคนนั่งอยู่ในรถเพียงคนเดียวเท่านั้น โดยนั่งอยู่บนที่นั่งคนขับ (ไม่มีสัมภาระอื่นๆ อยู่ในรถ)</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failed because OBD is not connected.</EN>
      <CH>再生失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_DPFRegeneration_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falló debido a que el OBD no está conectado.</MX>
      <TH>ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Coolant temperature is less than 80. Please try again. Coolant temperature is:</EN>
      <CH>冷却液温度小于80，请重新尝试，冷却液温度为：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_DPFRegeneration_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>La temperatura de refrigerante es menor a 80. Por favor intente de nuevo. La temperatura de refrigerante es:</MX>
      <TH>อุณหภูมิน้ำหล่อเย็นต่ำกว่า 80 โปรดลองอีกครั้ง อุณหภูมิน้ำหล่อเย็นเท่ากับ:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Start routine failure</EN>
      <CH>进入DPF服务再生模式失败，请联系系统管理员。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_DPFRegeneration_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Falla de rutina de arranque</MX>
      <TH>การเริ่มขั้นตอนการทำงานล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Waiting for timeout, service regeneration failed</EN>
      <CH>等待超时，服务再生失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_DPFRegeneration_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>Esperando expiración de tiempo, falló la regeneración de servicio</MX>
      <TH>กำลังรอให้หมดเวลาทำงาน การรีเจนเนอเรชั่นในระหว่างการบริการล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The service regeneration was successful.Percentage of soot mass is</EN>
      <CH>服务再生成功,当前的颗粒物百分比为：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_DPFRegeneration_Success</FL>
      <MX>La regeneración de servicio tuvo éxito. El porcentaje de masa de hollín es</MX>
      <TH>การรีเจนเนอเรชั่นในระหว่างการบริการสำเร็จแล้ว เปอร์เซ็นต์ของปริมาณเขม่าคือ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Process End</EN>
      <CH>流程结束</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_DPFRegeneration_Success1</FL>
      <MX>Fin de proceso</MX>
      <TH>สิ้นสุดกระบวนการ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Percentage of soot mass is</EN>
      <CH>当前的颗粒物百分比为：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_DPFRegeneration_Tip1_1</FL>
      <MX>El porcentaje de masa de hollín es</MX>
      <TH>เปอร์เซ็นต์ของปริมาณเขม่าคือ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>%.Please confirm whether the Diesel Particulate Filter regeneration is needed?</EN>
      <CH>%，请确认是否需要进行柴油机颗粒捕捉器DPF再生？</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_DPFRegeneration_Tip1_2</FL>
      <MX>%. ¿Por favor confirme si se necesita la regeneración del Filtro de partículas de diesel?</MX>
      <TH>% โปรดยืนยันว่าจำเป็นต้องทำการรีเจนเนอเรชั่นตัวกรองไอเสียเครื่องยนต์ดีเซลหรือไม่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Service regeneration is under way. Please wait.</EN>
      <CH>正在进行服务再生，请等待。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_DPFRegeneration_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Regeneración de servicio en curso. Por favor, espere.</MX>
      <TH>กำลังทำการรีเจนเนอเรชั่นในระหว่างการบริการอยู่ โปรดรอสักครู่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Nozzle Code Writing Successfully</EN>
      <CH>读取结束。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_IMARead_Success</FL>
      <MX>Escritura de código de boquilla exitosa</MX>
      <TH>การเขียนรหัสหัวฉีดสำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>injector cylinder 1:</EN>
      <CH>喷油嘴1代码：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_IMARead_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>cilindro de inyector 1:</MX>
      <TH>หัวฉีดของกระบอกสูบ 1:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>injector cylinder 2:</EN>
      <CH>喷油嘴2代码：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_IMARead_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>cilindro de inyector 2:</MX>
      <TH>หัวฉีดของกระบอกสูบ 2:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>injector cylinder 3:</EN>
      <CH>喷油嘴3代码：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_IMARead_Tip3</FL>
      <MX>cilindro de inyector 3:</MX>
      <TH>หัวฉีดของกระบอกสูบ 3:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>injector cylinder 4:</EN>
      <CH>喷油嘴4代码：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_IMARead_Tip4</FL>
      <MX>cilindro de inyector 4:</MX>
      <TH>หัวฉีดของกระบอกสูบ 4:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Nozzle Code Writing Successfully</EN>
      <CH>喷油嘴代码写入成功</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_IMAWrite_Success</FL>
      <MX>Escritura de código de boquilla exitosa</MX>
      <TH>การเขียนรหัสหัวฉีดสำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please enter the nozzle 1 code manually</EN>
      <CH>请手动输入喷油嘴1代码</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_IMAWrite_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Ingrese el código de la boquilla 1 manualmente</MX>
      <TH>โปรดป้อนรหัสของหัวฉีด 1 ในแบบแมนนวล</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Make sure the nozzle 1 code is correct</EN>
      <CH>请确认喷油嘴1代码是否准确</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_IMAWrite_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Asegúrese que el código de la boquilla 1 sea correcto</MX>
      <TH>ตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่ารหัสของหัวฉีด 1 ถูกต้อง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please enter the nozzle 2 code manually</EN>
      <CH>请手动输入喷油嘴2代码</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_IMAWrite_Tip3</FL>
      <MX>Ingrese el código de la boquilla 2 manualmente</MX>
      <TH>โปรดป้อนรหัสของหัวฉีด 2 ในแบบแมนนวล</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Make sure the nozzle 2 code is correct</EN>
      <CH>请确认喷油嘴2代码是否准确</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_IMAWrite_Tip4</FL>
      <MX>Asegúrese que el código de la boquilla 2 sea correcto</MX>
      <TH>ตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่ารหัสของหัวฉีด 2 ถูกต้อง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please enter the nozzle 3 code manually</EN>
      <CH>请手动输入喷油嘴3代码</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_IMAWrite_Tip5</FL>
      <MX>Ingrese el código de la boquilla 3 manualmente</MX>
      <TH>โปรดป้อนรหัสของหัวฉีด 3 ในแบบแมนนวล</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Make sure the nozzle 3 code is correct</EN>
      <CH>请确认喷油嘴3代码是否准确</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_IMAWrite_Tip6</FL>
      <MX>Asegúrese que el código de la boquilla 3 sea correcto</MX>
      <TH>ตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่ารหัสของหัวฉีด 3 ถูกต้อง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please enter the nozzle 4 code manually</EN>
      <CH>请手动输入喷油嘴4代码</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_IMAWrite_Tip7</FL>
      <MX>Ingrese el código de la boquilla 4 manualmente</MX>
      <TH>โปรดป้อนรหัสของหัวฉีด 4 ในแบบแมนนวล</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Make sure the nozzle 4 code is correct</EN>
      <CH>请确认喷油嘴4代码是否准确</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_IMAWrite_Tip8</FL>
      <MX>Asegúrese que el código de la boquilla 4 sea correcto</MX>
      <TH>ตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่ารหัสของหัวฉีด 4 ถูกต้อง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ECM self-learning cleared successfully, please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>ECM自学习清除成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_Reset_Success</FL>
      <MX>Programación automática de ECM completada con éxito, gire el interruptor de ignición a la posición OFF (apagado) por más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การลบข้อมูลการเรียนรู้ค่าด้วยตัวเองของ ECM สำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Throttle VVT self-learning failure</EN>
      <CH>节气门DVE自学习失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_Throttle_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falla de programación automática de VVT de acelerador</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าด้วยตัวเองของปีกผีเสื้อ VVT ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Throttle DVE self learning success, electricity at least the 660 s, which is under the keys to ensure the throttle self learning success</EN>
      <CH>节气门DVE自学习成功，请将钥匙下电至少660s，以确保节气门自学习成功存储</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_Throttle_Success</FL>
      <MX>Éxito de programación automática de DVE de acelerador, mantenga la llave fuera de encendido por lo menos 660 s, debajo de las llaves para asegurar el éxito de programación automática del acelerador</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าด้วยตัวเองของปีกผีเสื้อ DVE สำเร็จแล้ว ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลาอย่างน้อย 660 วินาที เพื่อให้แน่ใจว่าการเรียนรู้ค่าด้วยตัวเองของปีกผีเสื้อเป็นผลสำเร็จ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The current battery voltage:</EN>
      <CH>当前电池电压：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_Throttle_Tip1_1</FL>
      <MX>Voltaje de batería actual:</MX>
      <TH>แรงดันไฟฟ้าของแบตเตอรี่ในปัจจุบัน:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>\n n current inlet temperature:</EN>
      <CH>\n当前进气温度：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_Throttle_Tip1_2</FL>
      <MX>\n n temperatura de entrada actual:</MX>
      <TH>\n อุณหภูมิทางเข้าในปัจจุบัน:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The module the return value is wrong, variable valve timing system VVT self-learning failure.</EN>
      <CH>该模块返回值有误，可变气门正时系统VVT自学习失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_VVTLearning_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>El valor de retorno del módulo es incorrecto, falla de programación automática de VVT de sistema de sincronización de válvula variable.</MX>
      <TH>ค่าที่โมดูลส่งกลับไม่ถูกต้อง การเรียนรู้ค่าด้วยตัวเองของระบบควบคุมจังหวะการทำงานของวาล์วแบบปรับได้ VVT ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Removal of VVT parts self learning value, please key under electric after 660 s, at least to the electric start the engine, and the idle engine for at least 15 s, to complete the VVT new self learning</EN>
      <CH>清除VVT零部件自学习值完成，请钥匙下电至少660s后，重新上电启动发动机，并怠速热机至少15s，以完成VVT新的自学习</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_VVTLearning_Success</FL>
      <MX>Eliminación de valor de programación automática de partes de VVT, coloque la llave en encendido después de 660 s, por lo menos para el arranque eléctrico del vehículo, y el motor en marcha en vacío durante por lo menos 15 s, para completar la programación automática del VVT</MX>
      <TH>การลบค่าที่เรียนรู้ด้วยตัวเองของ VVT ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลา 660 วินาที จากนั้นให้สตาร์ทเครื่องยนต์แล้วเดินเบาเครื่องยนต์เป็นเวลาอย่างน้อย 15 วินาที เพื่อทำการเรียนรู้ค่าด้วยตัวเองของ VVT ครั้งใหม่ให้เสร็จสมบูรณ์</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Write VIN failed because OBD is not connected.</EN>
      <CH>写入VIN失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_WriteVIN_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falla de escritura de VIN debido a que el OBD no está conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การเขียน VIN ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Write VIN failed, the reason is: read VIN code failed.</EN>
      <CH>写入VIN失败，原因为：读取VIN码失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_WriteVIN_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Falla de escritura de VIN, razón: falla de lectura de código VIN.</MX>
      <TH>การเขียน VIN ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการอ่านรหัส VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The reason why the VIN failed to be written is that the VIN to be written is consistent with the current vehicle VIN.</EN>
      <CH>待写入VIN和当前车辆VIN一致，无需重新写VIN。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_WriteVIN_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>La razón por la que el VIN falló en escribirse es que el VIN escrito es consistente con el VIN del vehículo actual.</MX>
      <TH>การเขียน VIN ล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก VIN ที่จะเขียนเหมือนกันกับ VIN ที่มีอยู่ในรถในปัจจุบัน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failed to write VIN, the reason is: failed to write VIN.</EN>
      <CH>写入VIN失败，原因为：写入VIN失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_WriteVIN_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>Falla en escribir VIN, razón: falla en escribir el VIN.</MX>
      <TH>การเขียน VIN ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเขียน VIN ได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Write VIN failed, the reason is: read VIN code failed.</EN>
      <CH>写入VIN失败，原因为：读取VIN码失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_WriteVIN_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>Falla de escritura de VIN, razón: falla de lectura de código VIN.</MX>
      <TH>การเขียน VIN ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการอ่านรหัส VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failed to write VIN, because the write value is inconsistent with the read value.</EN>
      <CH>写入VIN失败，原因为：写入值与读取值不一致。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_WriteVIN_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>Falla en escribir el VIN, debido a que el valor de escritura es inconsistente con el valor leído.</MX>
      <TH>การเขียน VIN ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากค่าที่เขียนไม่ตรงกับค่าที่อ่านได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>VIN failed because: failed to enter the extended session.</EN>
      <CH>写入VIN失败，原因为：进入扩展会话失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_WriteVIN_Fail7</FL>
      <MX>Falla de VIN debida a: falló ingresar la sesión extendida.</MX>
      <TH>VIN ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าสู่เซสชั่นแบบขยายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>VIN failed to write because: security decryption failed.</EN>
      <CH>写入VIN失败，原因为：安全解密失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_WriteVIN_Fail8</FL>
      <MX>Falla de escritura de VIN debido a: falla de decodificación de seguridad.</MX>
      <TH>การเขียน VIN ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการถอดรหัสนิรภัยล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>VIN has been written successfully. Please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>写入VIN成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECM_WriteVIN_Success</FL>
      <MX>El VIN se escribió con éxito. Cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การเขียน VIN สำเร็จแล้ว ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPB electronic handbrake calipers maintenance -E100EPB initialization failed because OBD was not connected.</EN>
      <CH>EPB电子手刹卡钳维修-E100EPB初始化失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPB_Repair_E100Init_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Mantenimiento de calibradores de freno de mano electrónico de EPB -Falló inicialización de E100EPB debido a que el OBD no estaba conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การเริ่มการบำรุงรักษาก้ามปูเบรกมือแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ EPB - E100EPB ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Pull up EPB switch to perform manual parking function.Press the brake pedal and EPB switch to perform manual release function.</EN>
      <CH>拉起EPB开关，执行手动驻车功能。踩下制动踏板，按下EPB开关，执行手动释放功能。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPB_Repair_E100Init_Success</FL>
      <MX>Jale el interruptor de EPB hacia arriba para realizar la función de estacionamiento manual. Presione el pedal del freno y el interruptor de EPB para realizar la función de liberación manual.</MX>
      <TH>ดึงสวิตช์ EPB ขึ้นเพื่อทำการจอดในแบบแมนนวล เหยียบเบรกและกดสวิตช์ EPB เพื่อทำการปลดในแบบแมนนวล</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPB electronic handbrake caliper maintenance failed to enter the electronic handbrake maintenance mode, because OBD was not connected.</EN>
      <CH>EPB电子手刹卡钳维修进入电子手刹维修模式失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPB_Repair_EnterRepair_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>El mantenimiento de calibrador de freno de mano electrónico de EPB falló en ingresar al modo de mantenimiento del freno de mano electrónico, debido a que el OBD no estaba conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การบำรุงรักษาก้ามปูเบรกมือแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ EPB ไม่สามารถเข้าสู่โหมดการบำรุงรักษาเบรกมือแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ได้เนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPB electronic handbrake caliper maintenance failed to enter the electronic handbrake maintenance mode, because: the state of electronic handbrake does not meet the calibration requirements.</EN>
      <CH>EPB电子手刹卡钳维修进入电子手刹维修模式失败，原因为：电子手刹状态不符合标定要求。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPB_Repair_EnterRepair_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>El mantenimiento de calibrador de freno de mano electrónico de EPB falló en ingresar al modo de mantenimiento del freno de mano electrónico, debido a: el estado del freno de mano electrónico no cumple los requerimientos de calibración.</MX>
      <TH>การบำรุงรักษาก้ามปูเบรกมือแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ EPB ไม่สามารถเข้าสู่โหมดการบำรุงรักษาเบรกมือแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ได้เนื่องจากสถานะของเบรกมือแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ไม่เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขของการปรับเทียบ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPB electronic handbrake caliper maintenance failed to enter the electronic handbrake maintenance mode, the reason is: unknown reasons.</EN>
      <CH>EPB电子手刹卡钳维修进入电子手刹维修模式失败，原因为：未知原因。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPB_Repair_EnterRepair_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>El mantenimiento de calibrador de freno de mano electrónico de EPB falló en ingresar al modo de mantenimiento del freno de mano electrónico, razón: razones desconocidas.</MX>
      <TH>การบำรุงรักษาก้ามปูเบรกมือแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ EPB ไม่สามารถเข้าสู่โหมดการบำรุงรักษาเบรกมือแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ได้โดยไม่ทราบสาเหตุ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPB electronic brake calipers maintenance failed to enter the electronic brake maintenance mode, the reason is: general reasons.</EN>
      <CH>EPB电子手刹卡钳维修进入电子手刹维修模式失败，原因为：一般原因。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPB_Repair_EnterRepair_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>El mantenimiento de calibradores de freno electrónico de EPB falló en ingresar al modo de mantenimiento del freno electrónico, razón: razones generales.</MX>
      <TH>การบำรุงรักษาก้ามปูเบรกแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ EPB ไม่สามารถเข้าสู่โหมดการบำรุงรักษาเบรกแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ได้เนื่องจากสาเหตุทั่วไป</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPB Electronic brake calipers maintenance entered the electronic brake maintenance mode successfully.</EN>
      <CH>EPB电子手刹卡钳维修进入电子手刹维修模式成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPB_Repair_EnterRepair_Success</FL>
      <MX>El mantenimiento de calibradores de freno electrónico de EPB ingresó al modo de mantenimiento de freno electrónico con éxito.</MX>
      <TH>การบำรุงรักษาก้ามปูเบรกแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ EPB เข้าสู่โหมดการบำรุงรักษาเบรกแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please operate the electronic handbrake switch and put down the handbrake!</EN>
      <CH>请操作电子手刹开关，放下手刹！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPB_Repair_EnterRepair_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>¡Por favor opere el interruptor del freno de mano electrónico y baje el freno de mano!</MX>
      <TH>โปรดสั่งงานสวิตช์เบรกมือแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์และดันเบรกมือลง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPB electronic handbrake caliper maintenance exit electronic handbrake maintenance mode failed, the reason is: OBD is not connected.</EN>
      <CH>EPB电子手刹卡钳维修退出电子手刹维修模式失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPB_Repair_ExitRepair_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falló el modo de mantenimiento de freno de mano electrónico de salida de mantenimiento de calibrador de freno de mano electrónico de EPB, razón: OBD no está conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การบำรุงรักษาก้ามปูเบรกแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ EPB ไม่สามารถออกจากโหมดการบำรุงรักษาเบรกแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ได้เนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPB electronic brake calipers maintenance exit electronic brake maintenance mode failure, the reason is: general reasons.</EN>
      <CH>EPB电子手刹卡钳维修退出电子手刹维修模式失败，原因为：一般原因。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPB_Repair_ExitRepair_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Falla de modo de mantenimiento de freno electrónico de salida de mantenimiento de calibradores de freno electrónico de EPB, razón: razones generales.</MX>
      <TH>การบำรุงรักษาก้ามปูเบรกแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ EPB ไม่สามารถออกจากโหมดการบำรุงรักษาเบรกแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ได้เนื่องจากสาเหตุทั่วไป</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPB Electronic handbrake caliper maintenance initialization was successful.</EN>
      <CH>EPB电子手刹卡钳维修退出电子手刹维修模式成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPB_Repair_ExitRepair_Success</FL>
      <MX>Inicialización de mantenimiento de calibrador de freno de mano electrónico de EPB exitosa.</MX>
      <TH>การเริ่มการบำรุงรักษาก้ามปูเบรกแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ EPB สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPB electronic handbrake calipers maintenance initialization failed, the reason is: OBD is not connected.</EN>
      <CH>EPB电子手刹卡钳维修初始化失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPB_Repair_Init_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falló la inicialización de mantenimiento de calibradores de freno de mano electrónico de EPB, razón: OBD no está conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การเริ่มการบำรุงรักษาก้ามปูเบรกแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ EPB ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPB electronic handbrake calipers maintenance initialization failure, the reason is: electronic handbrake status does not meet the calibration requirements.</EN>
      <CH>EPB电子手刹卡钳维修初始化失败，原因为：电子手刹状态不符合标定要求。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPB_Repair_Init_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Falla de inicialización de mantenimiento de calibradores de freno de mano electrónico de EPB, razón: el estado del freno de mano electrónico no cumple los requerimientos de calibración.</MX>
      <TH>การเริ่มการบำรุงรักษาก้ามปูเบรกแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ EPB ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากสถานะของเบรกมือแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ไม่เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขของการปรับเทียบ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPB electronic handbrake calipers maintenance initialization failed, the reason is: unknown reasons.</EN>
      <CH>EPB电子手刹卡钳维修初始化失败，原因为：未知原因。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPB_Repair_Init_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Falló la inicialización de mantenimiento de calibradores de freno de mano electrónico de EPB, razón: razones desconocidas.</MX>
      <TH>การเริ่มการบำรุงรักษาก้ามปูเบรกแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ EPB ล้มเหลวโดยไม่ทราบสาเหตุ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPB Electronic handbrake caliper maintenance initialization was successful.</EN>
      <CH>EPB电子手刹卡钳维修初始化成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPB_Repair_Init_Success</FL>
      <MX>Inicialización de mantenimiento de calibrador de freno de mano electrónico de EPB exitosa.</MX>
      <TH>การเริ่มการบำรุงรักษาก้ามปูเบรกแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์ EPB สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please operate the electronic handbrake switch and put down the handbrake!</EN>
      <CH>请操作电子手刹开关，放下手刹！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPB_Repair_Init_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>¡Por favor opere el interruptor del freno de mano electrónico y baje el freno de mano!</MX>
      <TH>โปรดสั่งงานสวิตช์เบรกมือแบบอิเล็กทรอนิกส์และดันเบรกมือลง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The EPS online configuration failed because OBD is not connected.</EN>
      <CH>EPS在线配置失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_OnlineCon_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de EPS falló debido a que el OBD no está conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ EPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The EPS online configuration failed because the after-sales server could not be accessed.</EN>
      <CH>EPS在线配置失败，原因为：无法访问售后服务器。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_OnlineCon_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea EPS falló debido a que no se pudo tener acceso al servidor post-venta.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ EPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าถึงเซิร์ฟเวอร์หลังการขายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The EPS online configuration failed because VIN failed to confirm.</EN>
      <CH>EPS在线配置失败，原因为：VIN确认失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_OnlineCon_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de EPS falló debido a que el VIN falló en confirmar.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ EPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการยืนยัน VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The EPS online configuration failed because the car does not need online configuration or there is no car information on the server.</EN>
      <CH>EPS在线配置失败，原因为：该车无需在线配置或服务器上无该车信息。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_OnlineCon_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de EPS falló debido a que el vehículo no necesita configuración en línea o no hay información de vehículo en el servidor.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ EPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากรถไม่จำเป็นต้องทำการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ หรือไม่มีข้อมูลของรถอยู่บนเซิร์ฟเวอร์</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The EPS online configuration failed.</EN>
      <CH>EPS在线配置失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_OnlineCon_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de EPS falló.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ EPS ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The EPS online configuration result upload failed.</EN>
      <CH>EPS在线配置结果上传失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_OnlineCon_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>Falla de carga de resultado de configuración en línea de EPS.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ EPS ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The online configuration of EPS has been uploaded successfully. Please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>EPS在线配置结果上传成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_OnlineCon_Success</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de EPS se cargó con éxito. Cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ EPS สำเร็จแล้ว ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The EPS online configuration failed because the car does not need online configuration or there is no car information on the server.</EN>
      <CH>EPS在线配置成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_OnlineCon_Success1</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de EPS falló debido a que el vehículo no necesita configuración en línea o no hay información de vehículo en el servidor.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ EPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากรถไม่จำเป็นต้องทำการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ หรือไม่มีข้อมูลของรถอยู่บนเซิร์ฟเวอร์</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPS learning failed because OBD was not connected.</EN>
      <CH>EPS零位学习失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falló la programación de EPS debido a que OBD no estaba conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ EPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPS learning failed because steering wheel Angle verification failed.</EN>
      <CH>EPS零位学习失败，原因为：方向盘转角验证失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Fail10</FL>
      <MX>Falló la programación de EPS debido a que falló la verificación de ángulo del volante.</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ EPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการตรวจสอบยืนยันมุมพวงมาลัยล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPS learning failed because failed to clear the self-learning value stored in the ESP.</EN>
      <CH>EPS零位学习失败，原因为：清除ESP内存储的自学习值失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Fail11</FL>
      <MX>Falló la programación de EPS debido a que falló en eliminar el valor de programación automática almacenado en el ESP.</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ EPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถลบค่าที่เรียนรู้ด้วยตัวเองที่บันทึกไว้ใน ESP ได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPS learning failed because unknown error </EN>
      <CH>EPS零位学习失败，原因为：未知错误</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Fail12</FL>
      <MX>Falló la programación de EPS debido a error desconocido </MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ EPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดที่ไม่รู้จัก </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPS learning failed because failed to read Angle.</EN>
      <CH>EPS零位学习失败，原因为：读取角度失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Falló la programación de EPS debido a que falló leer el ángulo.</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ EPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถอ่านมุมได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPS learning failed because user terminated.</EN>
      <CH>EPS零位学习失败，原因为：用户终止。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Falló la programación de EPS debido a terminación por el usuario.</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ EPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากผู้ใช้สิ้นสุดการทำงาน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure code, unable to learn</EN>
      <CH>有故障码，无法进行零位学习</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>Código de falla, no se puede programar</MX>
      <TH>รหัสการทำงานล้มเหลว, ไม่สามารถเรียนรู้ค่าได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPS learning failed because failed to enter the extended session.</EN>
      <CH>EPS零位学习失败，原因为：进入扩展会话失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>Falla de programación de EPS debida a falla en ingresar la sesión extendida.</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ EPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าสู่เซสชั่นแบบขยายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPS learning failed because security access failed.</EN>
      <CH>EPS零位学习失败，原因为：安全访问失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>Falló la programación de EPS debido a falla de acceso de seguridad.</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ EPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเข้าถึงระบบนิรภัยล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPS learning failed because clear zero learning failure.</EN>
      <CH>EPS零位学习失败，原因为：清除零位学习失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Fail7</FL>
      <MX>Falló la programación de EPS debido a falla de programación de eliminación de cero.</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ EPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการลบข้อมูลการเรียนรู้ค่าศูนย์ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPS learning failed because failed to learn EPS.</EN>
      <CH>EPS零位学习失败，原因为：进行零位学习失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Fail8</FL>
      <MX>Falló la programación de EPS debido a falla de programación de EPS.</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ EPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเรียนรู้ค่าของ EPS</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPS learning failed because fault code check failed.</EN>
      <CH>EPS零位学习失败，原因为：故障码检查失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Fail9</FL>
      <MX>Falló la programación de EPS debido a falla de verificación de código de falla.</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ EPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการตรวจสอบรหัสข้อบกพร่องล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPS learning success.\n 1.ESP (ESC) clear the steering wheel steering Angle self-learning value stored by themselves, and complete the execution;\n2. must switch the power of the whole car to OFF 60 seconds later, and then re-energized, to finally take effect!</EN>
      <CH>EPS零位学习成功。\n1、ESP（ESC）清除自身存储的方向盘转向角自学习值，执行完毕；\n2、必须将整车电源切换至OFF 60秒后，再重新上电，才能最终生效！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Success</FL>
      <MX>Éxito de programación de EPS.\n 1. ESP (ESC) borra el valor de programación automática de ángulo de dirección del volante almacenado en éste mismo, y completa la ejecución; \n2. ¡Debe cambiar la energía del vehículo completo a OFF (apagado) 60 segundos después, y después volver a energizar, para que tenga efecto finalmente!</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ EPS สำเร็จแล้ว\n 1. ESP (ESC) ลบค่าที่เรียนรู้ด้วยตัวเองสำหรับมุมพวงมาลัยที่บันทึกไว้ภายในตัวเอง และทำการดำเนินการให้เสร็จสมบูรณ์;\n2. จะต้องปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลา 60 วินาที จากนั้นให้ปรับไปที่ตำแหน่ง ON เพื่อให้การดำเนินการมีผลใช้!</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EPS learning success.</EN>
      <CH>EPS零位学习成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Success1</FL>
      <MX>Éxito de programación de EPS.</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ EPS สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The current steering wheel Angle is:</EN>
      <CH>当前方向盘转角为:</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Tip1_1</FL>
      <MX>El ángulo de volante actual es:</MX>
      <TH>มุมพวงมาลัยในปัจจุบันคือ:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>°, whether to learn or not</EN>
      <CH> °，是否进行零位学习？</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Tip1_2</FL>
      <MX>°, ¿Desea programar la posición cero?</MX>
      <TH>° ต้องการเรียนรู้ตำแหน่งศูนย์หรือไม่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Steering wheel Angle verified successful.</EN>
      <CH>方向盘转角验证成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Ángulo de volante verificado con éxito.</MX>
      <TH>การตรวจสอบยืนยันมุมพวงมาลัยสำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Make sure the steering wheel is adjusted?</EN>
      <CH>确认方向盘是否已调正?</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Tip3</FL>
      <MX>Asegúrese que el volante está ajustado.</MX>
      <TH>ตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าพวงมาลัยได้รับการปรับแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The car is an ESP model. After successful EPS zero-bit learning, \n should remove the self-learning value of steering wheel Angle sensor stored in ESP.\n click ok and the program sequence will be executed.</EN>
      <CH>该车为ESP车型，需要在进行EPS零位学习成功后，\n清除ESP内部存储的方向盘转角传感器自学习值。\n点击确定后，程序顺序往下执行。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_EPS_ZeroLearning_Tip4</FL>
      <MX>El vehículo es un modelo ESP. Después de la programación de bit cero de EPS exitosa, debe eliminar el valor de programación automática del sensor de ángulo de volante almacenado en el ESP.\n Dé clic en Ok y se ejecutará la secuencia del programa.</MX>
      <TH>รถเป็นรุ่น ESP หลังจากการเรียนรู้ตำแหน่งศูนย์ของ EPS สำเร็จแล้ว ควรลบค่าที่เรียนรู้ด้วยตัวเองของเซ็นเซอร์มุมพวงมาลัยที่บันทึกไว้ใน ESP ออก\n คลิก "ตกลง" จากนั้นขั้นตอนการตั้งโปรแกรมจะเริ่มทำงาน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ESP Yaw rate calibration failed because  unknown error

</EN>
      <CH>ESP偏航率传感器标定失败，原因为：未知错误</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ESPCali_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de tasa de viraje de ESP falló debido a error desconocido

</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบอัตราการส่ายของ ESP ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดที่ไม่รู้จัก

</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The calibration of ESP yaw rate sensor failed because: failure to clear fault code.</EN>
      <CH>ESP偏航率传感器标定失败，原因为：进入默认会话失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ESPCali_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>La calibración del sensor de tasa de viraje de ESP falló debido a: falla para eliminar código de falla.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบเซ็นเซอร์อัตราการส่ายของ ESP ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถลบรหัสข้อบกพร่องได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The calibration of ESP yaw rate sensor failed because: failure to clear fault code.</EN>
      <CH>ESP偏航率传感器标定失败，原因为：清除故障码失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ESPCali_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>La calibración del sensor de tasa de viraje de ESP falló debido a: falla para eliminar código de falla.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบเซ็นเซอร์อัตราการส่ายของ ESP ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถลบรหัสข้อบกพร่องได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ESP yaw rate calibration failed because OBD was not connected.</EN>
      <CH>ESP偏航率标定失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ESPCali_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de tasa de viraje de ESP falló debido a que el OBD no estaba conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบอัตราการส่ายของ ESP ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ESP Yaw rate calibration failed because failed to enter the extension session.

</EN>
      <CH>ESP偏航率标定失败，原因为：进入扩展会话失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ESPCali_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de la tasa de viraje de ESP falló debido a falla en ingresar a sesión de extensión.

</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบอัตราการส่ายของ ESP ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าสู่เซสชั่นแบบขยายได้

</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ESP Yaw rate calibration failed because  calibration failure.

</EN>
      <CH>ESP偏航率标定失败，原因为：标定失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ESPCali_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de tasa de viraje de ESP falló debido a falla de calibración.

</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบอัตราการส่ายของ ESP ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการปรับเทียบล้มเหลว

</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ESP Yaw rate calibration failed because  the calibration result query failed.

</EN>
      <CH>ESP偏航率标定失败，原因为：标定结果查询失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ESPCali_Fail7</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de tasa de viraje de ESP falló debido a falla de búsqueda de resultado de calibración.

</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบอัตราการส่ายของ ESP ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการสอบถามผลการปรับเทียบล้มเหลว

</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ESP yaw rate calibration is successful, please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>ESP偏航率标定成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ESPCali_Success</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de tasa de viraje de ESP es exitosa, cambie el interruptor de ignición a la posición OFF durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบอัตราการส่ายของ ESP สำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The GW online configuration failed because the after-sales server could not be accessed.</EN>
      <CH>GW在线配置失败，原因为：无法访问售后服务器。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_GW_OnlineCon_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea GW falló debido a que no se pudo tener acceso al servidor post-venta.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ GW ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าถึงเซิร์ฟเวอร์หลังการขายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The GW online configuration failed because OBD was disconnected.</EN>
      <CH>GW在线配置失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_GW_OnlineCon_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de GW falló debido a que el OBD estaba desconectado.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ GW ล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก OBD ถูกปลดออก</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The GW online configuration failed because VIN confirmed failure.</EN>
      <CH>GW在线配置失败，原因为：VIN确认失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_GW_OnlineCon_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de GW falló debido a que el VIN confirmó la falla.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ GW ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถยืนยัน VIN ได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The GW online configuration failed because the car does not need online configuration or there is no car information on the server.</EN>
      <CH>GW在线配置失败，原因为：该车无需在线配置或服务器上无该车信息。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_GW_OnlineCon_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de GW falló debido a que el vehículo no necesita configuración en línea o no hay información de vehículo en el servidor.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ GW ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากรถไม่จำเป็นต้องทำการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ หรือไม่มีข้อมูลของรถอยู่บนเซิร์ฟเวอร์</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The GW online configuration failed.</EN>
      <CH>GW在线配置失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_GW_OnlineCon_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de GW falló.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ GW ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The GW online configuration result upload failed.</EN>
      <CH>GW在线配置结果上传失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_GW_OnlineCon_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>Falla de carga de resultado de configuración en línea de GW.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ GW ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The GW online configuration result has been uploaded successfully. Please switch The ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>GW在线配置结果上传成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_GW_OnlineCon_Success</FL>
      <MX>El resultado de configuración en línea GW se cargó con éxito. Cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ GW สำเร็จแล้ว ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The GW online configuration was successful.</EN>
      <CH>GW在线配置成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_GW_OnlineCon_Success1</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea de GW fue exitosa.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ GW สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Maintenance of reset failed.</EN>
      <CH>保养复位失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_IC_Reset_Fail</FL>
      <MX>Falló el restablecimiento de mantenimiento.</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ตการบำรุงรักษาล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ECM self-learning cleared successfully, please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>保养复位成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_IC_Reset_Success</FL>
      <MX>Programación automática de ECM completada con éxito, gire el interruptor de ignición a la posición OFF (apagado) por más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การลบข้อมูลการเรียนรู้ค่าด้วยตัวเองของ ECM สำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ICE replacement failed because the after-sales server could not be accessed.</EN>
      <CH>ICE换件失败，原因为：无法访问售后服务器。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ICE_Replace_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>El reemplazo de ICE falló debido a que no se pudo tener acceso al servidor post-venta.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยน ICE ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าถึงเซิร์ฟเวอร์หลังการขายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>An unknown error call avn interface</EN>
      <CH>调用avn接口未知错误</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ICE_Replace_Fail10</FL>
      <MX>Error desconocido al recuperar interfaz de AVN</MX>
      <TH>ข้อผิดพลาดที่ไม่รู้จักในระหว่างการติดต่อกับอินเตอร์เฟส AVN</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>AVN waiting timeout</EN>
      <CH>AVN等待超时</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ICE_Replace_Fail11</FL>
      <MX>Expiración de tiempo de espera de AVN</MX>
      <TH>การรอ AVN หมดเวลาแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>AVN - Tbox connection interruption</EN>
      <CH>AVN-Tbox连接中断</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ICE_Replace_Fail12</FL>
      <MX>AVN - Interrupción de conexión de Tbox</MX>
      <TH>การเชื่อมต่อระหว่าง AVN - Tbox ขาดหายไป</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Replace the failed.</EN>
      <CH>更换失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ICE_Replace_Fail13</FL>
      <MX>Falla de reemplazo.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ICE replacement failed because OBD is not connected.</EN>
      <CH>ICE换件失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ICE_Replace_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>El reemplazo de ICE falló debido a que el OBD no está conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยน ICE ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ICE replacement failed because VIN code failed.</EN>
      <CH>ICE换件失败，原因为：VIN码失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ICE_Replace_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>El reemplazo de ICE falló debido a falla de código de VIN.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยน ICE ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากรหัส VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ICE in a failure, the reason is: the VIN code written to fail.</EN>
      <CH>ICE换件失败，原因为：VIN码写入失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ICE_Replace_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>ICE tiene falla, razón: Falla en escribir el código VIN.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยน ICE ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเขียนรหัส VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ICE to trigger the failure.</EN>
      <CH>ICE触发失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ICE_Replace_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>ICE falló en activarse.</MX>
      <TH>การกระตุ้น ICE ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Exception handling gateway</EN>
      <CH>网关处理异常    </CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ICE_Replace_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>Excepción de manejo de gateway</MX>
      <TH>เกตเวย์การจัดการข้อยกเว้น</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Length error parameters</EN>
      <CH>参数长度错误    </CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ICE_Replace_Fail7</FL>
      <MX>Parámetros de error de longitud</MX>
      <TH>ข้อผิดพลาดของพารามิเตอร์ความยาว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Call the main data failed</EN>
      <CH>调用主数据失败    </CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ICE_Replace_Fail8</FL>
      <MX>Falla de llamada de datos principales</MX>
      <TH>การเรียกข้อมูลหลักล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Call the avn interface parameter error</EN>
      <CH>调用avn接口参数错误</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ICE_Replace_Fail9</FL>
      <MX>Llamar error de parámetro de interfaz AVN</MX>
      <TH>ข้อผิดพลาดในการเรียกข้อมูลพารามิเตอร์ของอินเตอร์เฟส AVN</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ICE key exchange fails. After the vehicle is powered on again, wait for 2min and check the result of secret key exchange again.</EN>
      <CH>ICE密钥交换失败重新车辆上电后，等待2min后，再次检查秘钥交换结果。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ICE_Replace_Read_Fail</FL>
      <MX>Falla el intercambio de llave ICE. Después que el vehículo se encienda de nuevo, espere 2 minutos y verifique el resultado del intercambio de llave secreta de nuevo.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนรหัส ICE ล้มเหลว หลังจากที่ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง ON อีกครั้ง ให้รอเป็นเวลา 2 นาที แล้วตรวจสอบผลของการเปลี่ยนรหัสลับอีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ICE key exchange successful.</EN>
      <CH>ICE密钥交换成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ICE_Replace_Read_Success</FL>
      <MX>Intercambio de llave ICE.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนรหัส ICE สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ICE is the key change successful.</EN>
      <CH>ICE密钥更改成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ICE_Replace_Success</FL>
      <MX>Cambio de llave ICE exitoso.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนรหัส ICE สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ICE key is triggered successfully. After waiting 2 minutes, the result of key exchange is read.</EN>
      <CH>正在进行换件流程，请保持整车上电状态，并等待2分钟.</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ICE_Replace_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>La llave ICE se activó con éxito. Después de esperar 2 minutos, se lee el resultado del intercambio de llave.</MX>
      <TH>การกระตุ้นรหัส ICE สำเร็จแล้ว หลังจากรอเป็นเวลา 2 นาที ให้อ่านผลการเปลี่ยนรหัส</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ICE replacement failed because OBD is not connected.</EN>
      <CH>反激活失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_IntelligentDriving_Anti_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>El reemplazo de ICE falló debido a que el OBD no está conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยน ICE ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The activation failed, the reason is: to read failure.</EN>
      <CH>反激活失败，原因为：回读失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_IntelligentDriving_Anti_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Falló la activación, razón: falla de lectura.</MX>
      <TH>การเปิดใช้งานล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการอ่านล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The activation is successful, please switch the ignition switch to OFF more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>反激活成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_IntelligentDriving_Anti_Success</FL>
      <MX>La activación es exitosa, cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การเปิดใช้งานสำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ICE replacement failed because OBD is not connected.</EN>
      <CH>激活失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_IntelligentDriving_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>El reemplazo de ICE falló debido a que el OBD no está conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยน ICE ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Activation failed, the reason is: to read failure.</EN>
      <CH>激活失败，原因为：回读失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_IntelligentDriving_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Falló la activación, razón: falla de lectura.</MX>
      <TH>การสั่งงานล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการอ่านล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Write failed, failed to get ESK.</EN>
      <CH>写入失败，获取ESK失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_IntelligentDriving_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Falla de escritura, falla en obtener ESK.</MX>
      <TH>การเขียนล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเรียกข้อมูล ESK ได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Activated, please switch the ignition switch to OFF more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>激活成，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_IntelligentDriving_Success</FL>
      <MX>Activado, cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>เปิดใช้งานแล้ว ให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN> online configuration failed because the after-sales server could not be accessed.</EN>
      <CH>在线配置失败，原因为：无法访问售后服务器。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_OnlineCon_Fail1</FL>
      <MX> La configuración en línea falló debido a que no se pudo tener acceso al servidor post-venta.</MX>
      <TH> การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าถึงเซิร์ฟเวอร์หลังการขายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN> online configuration failed because OBD was disconnected.</EN>
      <CH>在线配置失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_OnlineCon_Fail2</FL>
      <MX> La configuración en línea falló debido a que el OBD estaba desconectado.</MX>
      <TH> การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก OBD ถูกปลดออก</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN> online configuration failed because VIN failed to confirm.</EN>
      <CH>在线配置失败，原因为：VIN确认失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_OnlineCon_Fail3</FL>
      <MX> La configuración en línea falló debido a que el VIN falló en confirmar.</MX>
      <TH> การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการยืนยัน VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN> online configuration failed because: the car does not need online configuration or there is no car information on the server.</EN>
      <CH>在线配置失败，原因为：该车无需在线配置或服务器上无该车信息。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_OnlineCon_Fail4</FL>
      <MX> La configuración en línea falló debido a que el vehículo no necesita configuración en línea o no hay información de vehículo en el servidor.</MX>
      <TH> การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากรถไม่จำเป็นต้องทำการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ หรือไม่มีข้อมูลของรถอยู่บนเซิร์ฟเวอร์</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN> online configuration failed.</EN>
      <CH>在线配置失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_OnlineCon_Fail5</FL>
      <MX> falló la configuración en línea.</MX>
      <TH> การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN> online configuration result upload failed.</EN>
      <CH>在线配置结果上传失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_OnlineCon_Fail6</FL>
      <MX> falló la carga de resultado de configuración en línea.</MX>
      <TH> การอัพโหลดผลการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN> online configuration result has been uploaded successfully. Please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>在线配置结果上传成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_OnlineCon_Success</FL>
      <MX> el resultado de configuración en línea se cargó con éxito. Cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH> การอัพโหลดผลการกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำเร็จแล้ว ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN> online configuration was successful.</EN>
      <CH>在线配置成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_OnlineCon_Success1</FL>
      <MX> configuración en línea exitosa.</MX>
      <TH> การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failed to add key (original key is invalid) because OBD is not connected.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙（原钥匙无效）失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falló en agregar llave (llave original no es válida) debido a que OBD no está conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจ (กุญแจชุดดั้งเดิมไม่สามารถใช้งานได้) ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failed to add the key (the original key was invalid), because the after-sales server could not be accessed.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙（原钥匙无效）失败，原因为：无法访问售后服务器。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Falla en agregar la llave (la llave original no era válida), debido a que no se pudo tener acceso al servidor post-venta.</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจ (กุญแจชุดดั้งเดิมไม่สามารถใช้งานได้) ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าถึงเซิร์ฟเวอร์หลังการขายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failed to add key (the original key is invalid), the reason is: VIN failed to confirm.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙（原钥匙无效）失败，原因为：VIN确认失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Falla en agregar llave (la llave original no es válida), razón: El VIN falló en confirmar.</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจ (กุญแจชุดดั้งเดิมไม่สามารถใช้งานได้) ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการยืนยัน VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failed to add key (the original key is invalid), because the car does not need PEPS configuration or there is no car information on the server.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙（原钥匙无效）失败，原因为：该车无需PEPS配置或服务器上无该车信息。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>Falla en agregar la llave (la llave original no es válida), debido a que el vehículo no necesita configuración PEPS o no hay información del vehículo en el servidor.</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจ (กุญแจชุดดั้งเดิมไม่สามารถใช้งานได้) ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากรถไม่จำเป็นต้องทำการกำหนดค่า PEPS หรือไม่มีข้อมูลของรถอยู่บนเซิร์ฟเวอร์</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>PEPS failed to upload the matching result.</EN>
      <CH>PEPS匹配结果上传失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>PEPS falló en cargar el resultado correspondiente.</MX>
      <TH>PEPS ไม่สามารถอัพโหลดผลการจับคู่ได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The key cannot be added to the car. Please confirm that ESK has been written into PEPS.</EN>
      <CH>该车无法添加钥匙，请确认ESK已写入PEPS。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>La llave no se puede agregar al vehículo. Por favor confirme que ESK se haya escrito en PEPS.</MX>
      <TH>ไม่สามารถเพิ่มกุญแจให้กับรถได้ โปรดยืนยันว่าได้เขียน ESK ลงใน PEPS แล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Error reading key number.</EN>
      <CH>读取钥匙数错误。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail7</FL>
      <MX>Error al leer el número de llave.</MX>
      <TH>ข้อผิดพลาดในการอ่านหมายเลขของกุญแจ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure to enter EOL matching mode: Vehicle voltage failure</EN>
      <CH>进入EOL匹配模式失败，失败原因：车辆电压故障</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail8_1</FL>
      <MX>Falla en ingresar a modo de empate EOL: Falla de voltaje de vehículo</MX>
      <TH>ไม่สามารถเข้าสู่โหมดการจับคู่ EOL ได้: แรงดันไฟฟ้าของรถทำงานล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The key addition failed because the number of keys found was not equal to the number of keys requested for learning.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙（原钥匙无效）失败，原因为：找到的钥匙的数量不等於请求学习的钥匙数量</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail8_10</FL>
      <MX>La adición de llave falló debido a que el número de llaves encontrado no era igual al número de llaves solicitado para programación.</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจล้มเหลวเนื่องจากจำนวนกุญแจที่พบไม่เท่ากับจำนวนกุญแจที่ร้องขอสำหรับการจับคู่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failed to add key (original key is invalid). The reason is: found invalid key</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙（原钥匙无效）失败，原因为：找到无效钥匙</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail8_11</FL>
      <MX>Falla en agregar llave (la llave original no es válida). Razón: llave no válida encontrada</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจ (กุญแจชุดดั้งเดิมไม่สามารถใช้งานได้) ล้มเหลว สาเหตุเนื่องจากพบกุญแจที่ไม่สามารถใช้งานได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure to add key (original key is invalid) due to PEPS ECU failure</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙（原钥匙无效）失败，原因为：PEPS ECU 故障</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail8_12</FL>
      <MX>Falla en agregar llave (la llave original no es válida) debido a falla de ECU de PEPS</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจ (กุญแจชุดดั้งเดิมไม่สามารถใช้งานได้) ล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก PEPS ECU ทำงานล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure to enter EOL matching mode due to incorrect vehicle power supply status</EN>
      <CH>进入EOL匹配模式失败，失败原因：车辆电源状态不对</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail8_2</FL>
      <MX>Falla en ingresar modo de empate EOL debido a estado de suministro de energía de vehículo incorrecto</MX>
      <TH>ไม่สามารถเข้าสู่โหมดการจับคู่ EOL ได้เนื่องจากสถานะของแหล่งจ่ายไฟของรถไม่ถูกต้อง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure to enter EOL matching mode: PEPS is learning process</EN>
      <CH>进入EOL匹配模式失败，失败原因：PEPS正在学习流程</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail8_3</FL>
      <MX>Falla en ingresar a modo de empate EOL: PEPS está en proceso de programación</MX>
      <TH>ไม่สามารถเข้าสู่โหมดการจับคู่ EOL ได้เนื่องจาก PEPS กำลังทำการเรียนรู้ค่าอยู่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure to enter EOL matching mode: ESK data problem</EN>
      <CH>进入EOL匹配模式失败，失败原因：ESK数据问题</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail8_4</FL>
      <MX>Falla en ingresar a modo de empate EOL: Problema de datos ESK</MX>
      <TH>ไม่สามารถเข้าสู่โหมดการจับคู่ EOL ได้เนื่องจากปัญหาของข้อมูล ESK</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure to add key (invalid original key). Cause of failure: Unknown cause.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙（原钥匙无效）失败，失败原因：未知原因。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail8_5</FL>
      <MX>Falla en agregar llave (llave original no válida). Causa de falla: Causa desconocida.</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจ (กุญแจชุดดั้งเดิมไม่สามารถใช้งานได้) ล้มเหลว สาเหตุของความล้มเหลว: ไม่ทราบสาเหตุ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure to add key (invalid original key) due to vehicle voltage failure</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙（原钥匙无效）失败，原因为：车辆电压故障</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail8_6</FL>
      <MX>Falla en agregar llave (la llave original no es válida) debido a falla de voltaje de vehículo</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจ (กุญแจชุดดั้งเดิมไม่สามารถใช้งานได้) ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากแรงดันไฟฟ้าของรถทำงานล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure to add keys (invalid original keys). Reasons for failure are: retry learning</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙（原钥匙无效）失败，原因为：重新尝试学习</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail8_7</FL>
      <MX>Falla en agregar llaves (llaves originales no válidas). Las razones para falla son: reintentar programación</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจ (กุญแจชุดดั้งเดิมไม่สามารถใช้งานได้) ล้มเหลว สาเหตุของความล้มเหลว: การพยายามเรียนรู้ค่าอีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Adding the key (the original key is invalid) failed because the valid key was not found.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙（原钥匙无效）失败，原因为：未找到有效钥匙.</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail8_8</FL>
      <MX>Falló la adición de llave (la llave original no es válida) debido a que no se encontró llave válida.</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจ (กุญแจชุดดั้งเดิมไม่สามารถใช้งานได้) ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่พบกุญแจที่สามารถใช้งานได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failed to add keys (the original key is invalid) for the maximum number of keys allowed to learn</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙（原钥匙无效）失败，原因为：达到允许学习钥匙的最大数量</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail8_9</FL>
      <MX>Falla en agregar llaves (la llave original no es válida) para el número máximo de llaves permitidas para programar</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจ (กุญแจชุดดั้งเดิมไม่สามารถใช้งานได้) ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากถึงจำนวนสูงสุดสำหรับกุญแจที่อนุญาตให้ทำการเรียนรู้ค่าได้แล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>PEPS matching result uploaded successfully, please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>PEPS匹配结果上传成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Success</FL>
      <MX>Resultado de empate PEPS cargado con éxito, gire el interruptor de ignición a la posición OFF (apagado) por más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการจับคู่ PEPS สำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>1. This program is mainly used for the purpose that the lost key can not be reused by matching the key again after the original key has been lost. \n2. Every time you use this program and successfully add keys, you will not be able to restart the vehicle (the keys are deleted) if the keys are not added this time. \n3. After using this program, if you want to add more keys, you can only use the "new keys (original keys continue to be valid)" program.</EN>
      <CH>1、本程序，主要用于原钥匙丢失后，希望通过钥匙的重新匹配，达到使丢失的钥匙无法再使用的目的。\n2、每次使用本程序，成功添加钥匙的前提下，凡是本次未被添加的钥匙，均会无法再启动车辆（钥匙被删除）。\n3、使用完本程序后，若想新增更多的钥匙，只能使用《新增钥匙（原钥匙继续有效）》程序。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>1. Este programa se usa principalmente para el propósito de que la llave perdida no se pueda reutilizar al empatar la llave de nuevo después que la llave original se perdió. \n2. Cada vez que use este programa y agregue llaves con éxito, no podrá volver a arrancar el vehículo (las llaves se eliminaron) su las llaves no se agregaron esta vez. \n3. Después de usar este programa, si desea agregar más llaves, puede usar sólo el programa "llaves nuevas (las llaves originales continuarán siendo válidas)".</MX>
      <TH>1. โปรแกรมนี้ใช้เพื่อให้ไม่สามารถนำกุญแจที่หายไปกลับมาทำการจับคู่อีกครั้งได้หลังจากที่กุญแจชุดดั้งเดิมหายไป \n2 ทุกครั้งที่คุณใช้โปรแกรมนี้และทำการเพิ่มกุญแจได้สำเร็จ คุณจะไม่สามารถสตาร์ทรถอีกครั้งได้ (กุญแจได้ถูกลบไปแล้ว) ถ้าไม่ทำการเพิ่มกุญแจในคราวเดียวกัน \n3 หลังจากที่ใช้โปรแกรมนี้ ถ้าคุณต้องการเพิ่มกุญแจเพิ่มเติม คุณสามารถใช้ได้เฉพาะโปรแกรม "กุญแจชุดใหม่ (กุญแจชุดดั้งเดิมสามารถใช้งานได้ต่อไป)" เท่านั้น</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>1. Only one new key can be added at a time; n2. Please take the extra key out of the car. Only one key is reserved in the car and put it near the handle of the hand brake.</EN>
      <CH>1、每次只能新增一把钥匙；\n2、请将多余的钥匙拿出车外，车内只保留1把钥匙，放置在手刹操作手柄附近！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>1. Sólo se puede agregar una nueva llave a la vez; n2. Por favor retire la llave adicional del vehículo. Sólo una llave está reservada en el vehículo y colóquela cerca de la manija del freno manual.</MX>
      <TH>1. สามารถเพิ่มกุญแจชุดใหม่ได้ครั้งละชุดเท่านั้น; n2. โปรดนำกุญแจชุดอื่นๆ ออกจากรถ จะต้องมีกุญแจอยู่ภายในรถเพียงชุดเดียวเท่านั้น และให้วางไว้ใกล้กับมือจับเบรกมือ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The number of keys has been matched</EN>
      <CH>已匹配钥匙数量</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Tip3_1</FL>
      <MX>Se empató el número de llaves</MX>
      <TH>จำนวนของกุญแจที่จับคู่แล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>, the remaining number of matching keys</EN>
      <CH>，剩余匹配钥匙数量</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Tip3_2</FL>
      <MX>, número de restante de llaves empatadas</MX>
      <TH>จำนวนกุญแจที่จะจับคู่ที่เหลืออยู่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>, do you want to continue adding keys?</EN>
      <CH>,是否继续添加钥匙？</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Tip3_3</FL>
      <MX>, ¿desea continuar agregando llaves?</MX>
      <TH>คุณต้องการเพิ่มกุญแจต่อไปหรือไม่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>This key has been added successfully, and all other keys have been deleted!</EN>
      <CH>本把钥匙添加成功，其余钥匙已经全部删除！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Tip4</FL>
      <MX>¡Esta llave se agregó con éxito, y todas las demás llaves se eliminaron!</MX>
      <TH>กุญแจชุดนี้ได้รับการเพิ่มสำเร็จแล้ว และกุญแจชุดอื่นๆ ได้ถูกลบไปแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failed to add key (original key is valid) because OBD is not connected.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙（原钥匙有效）失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyVa_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falló en agregar llave (llave original es válida) debido a que OBD no está conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจ (กุญแจชุดดั้งเดิมสามารถใช้งานได้) ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failed to add the key (the original key is valid) because the after-sales server could not be accessed.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙（原钥匙有效）失败，原因为：无法访问售后服务器。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyVa_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Falla en agregar la llave (la llave original es válida), debido a que no se pudo tener acceso al servidor post-venta.</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจ (กุญแจชุดดั้งเดิมสามารถใช้งานได้) ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าถึงเซิร์ฟเวอร์หลังการขายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failed to add the key (the original key is valid). The reason is that VIN failed to confirm.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙（原钥匙有效）失败，原因为：VIN确认失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyVa_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Falla en agregar llave (la llave original es válida). La razón es que el VIN falló en confirmar.</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจ (กุญแจชุดดั้งเดิมสามารถใช้งานได้) ล้มเหลว สาเหตุเนื่องจากการยืนยัน VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failed to add key (the original key is valid) because: failed to obtain ESK VC.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙（原钥匙有效）失败，原因为：获取ESK VC失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyVa_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>Falló en agregar la llave (la llave original es válida) debido a: falla en obtener VC de ESK.</MX>
      <TH>การเพิ่มกุญแจ (กุญแจชุดดั้งเดิมสามารถใช้งานได้) ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเรียกข้อมูล ESK VC ได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The key was added successfully.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyVa_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>La llave se agregó con éxito.</MX>
      <TH>เพิ่มกุญแจสำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>, to achieve the maximum number of matching keys.</EN>
      <CH>,达到最大匹配钥匙数。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyVa_Tip2_1</FL>
      <MX>, para lograr el número máximo de llaves de empate.</MX>
      <TH>เพื่อทำการจับคู่กุญแจถึงจำนวนสูงสุดที่อนุญาต</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ESCL reset failed because the after-sales server could not be accessed.</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位失败，原因为：无法访问售后服务器。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>El restablecimiento de ESCL falló debido a que no se pudo tener acceso al servidor post-venta.</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าถึงเซิร์ฟเวอร์หลังการขายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ESCL reset failed because OBD plug is not connected!</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位失败，原因为：OBD插头未连接！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>¡El restablecimiento de ESCL falló debido a que el conector de OBD no está conectado!</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อปลั๊ก OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL reset failed because ESCL is not learnt.</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位失败，原因为：ESCL is not learnt.</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Fail3_1</FL>
      <MX>El restablecimiento de ESCL falló debido a que el ESCL no se programó.</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเรียนรู้ค่า ESCL</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL reset failed due to power failure of ESCL</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位失败，原因为：ESCL上电失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Fail3_10</FL>
      <MX>Falla de restablecimiento de ESCL debido a falla de energía de ESCL</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากกำลังไฟฟ้าของ ESCL ทำงานล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL reset failed due to vehicle voltage failure</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位失败，原因为：车辆电压故障</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Fail3_11</FL>
      <MX>Falla de restablecimiento de ESCL debido a falla de voltaje de vehículo</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากแรงดันไฟฟ้าของรถทำงานล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL reset failed for unknown reasons.</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位失败，原因为：未知原因。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Fail3_12</FL>
      <MX>Falla de restablecimiento de ESCL por razones desconocidas.</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ESCL ล้มเหลวโดยไม่ทราบสาเหตุ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL reset failed due to ESCL neutral failure.</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位失败，原因为：ESCL neutral failed.</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Fail3_2</FL>
      <MX>Falla de restablecimiento de ESCL debido a falla de neutral de ESCL.</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากนิวทรัลของ ESCL ทำงานล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCLreserves, for: ESK not matched with PEPS ESK.</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位失败，原因为：ESK not matched with PEPS ESK.</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Fail3_3</FL>
      <MX>Falla de restablecimiento de ESCL, Razón: ESK no empatado con ESK de PEPS.</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก ESK ไม่สอดคล้องกับ PEPS ESK</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL reset failed due to non-OFF vehicle power status</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位失败，原因为：车辆电源状态非OFF</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Fail3_4</FL>
      <MX>Falla de restablecimiento de ESCL debida a estado de energía de vehículo no apagado</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากสถานะของกำลังไฟฟ้าของรถไม่อยู่ที่ตำแหน่ง OFF</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL reset failed due to severe grade DTC</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位失败，原因为：严重等级的DTC</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Fail3_5</FL>
      <MX>Falla de restablecimiento de ESCL debida a DTC de grado severo</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก DTC ที่ร้ายแรง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL reset failed due to other errors</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位失败，原因为：其他错误</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Fail3_6</FL>
      <MX>Falla de restablecimiento de ESCL debida a otros errores</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดอื่นๆ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL reset failed due to PEPS ECU failure</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位失败，原因为：PEPS ECU 故障</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Fail3_7</FL>
      <MX>Falla de restablecimiento de ESCL debida a falla de ECO de PEPS</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก PEPS ECU ทำงานล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL reset failed due to internal failure of ESCL</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位失败，原因为：ESCL 内部故障</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Fail3_8</FL>
      <MX>Falla de restablecimiento de ESCL debida a falla interna de ESCL</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการทำงานล้มเหลวภายใน ESCL</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL reset failed due to the failure of ESCL communication</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位失败，原因为：ESCL通讯失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Fail3_9</FL>
      <MX>Falla de restablecimiento de ESCL debido a falla de comunicación de ESCL</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการติดต่อสื่อสารของ ESCL ทำงานล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ESCL reset failed because the server does not have the car information.</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位失败，原因为：服务器无该车信息。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>Falla de restablecimiento de ESCL debida a que el servidor no tiene información del vehículo.</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากเซิร์ฟเวอร์ไม่มีข้อมูลของรถ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ESCL reset failed because failed to read VIN code.</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位失败，原因为：读取VIN码失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>Falla de restablecimiento de ESCL debida a falla en leer el código VIN.</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการอ่านรหัส VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ESCL reset result upload failed.</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位结果上传失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>Falló la carga del resultado de restablecimiento de ESCL.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการรีเซ็ต ESCL ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ESCL reset was successful.</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Success</FL>
      <MX>Restablecimiento de ESCL exitoso.</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต ESCL สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The PEPS failed to upload the matching result.</EN>
      <CH>PEPS匹配结果上传失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>PEPS falló en cargar el resultado correspondiente.</MX>
      <TH>PEPS ไม่สามารถอัพโหลดผลการจับคู่ได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>One-key startup configuration failed because OBD was not connected.</EN>
      <CH>一键启动配置失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de arranque de una llave falló debido a que el OBD no estaba conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าการเริ่มทำงานด้วยกุญแจชุดเดียวล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>One-key startup configuration failed because the after-sales server could not be accessed.</EN>
      <CH>一键启动配置失败，原因为：无法访问售后服务器。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de arranque de una llave falló debido a que no se pudo tener acceso al servidor post-venta.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าการเริ่มทำงานด้วยกุญแจชุดเดียวล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าถึงเซิร์ฟเวอร์หลังการขายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>One-key startup configuration failed because ECM learning failed.</EN>
      <CH>一键启动配置失败，原因：ECM学习失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de arranque de una llave falló debido a que falló la programación de ECM.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าการเริ่มทำงานด้วยกุญแจชุดเดียวล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเรียนรู้ค่าของ ECM ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>One-key startup configuration failed because VIN failed to confirm.</EN>
      <CH>一键启动配置失败，原因为：VIN确认失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de arranque de una llave falló debido a que el VIN falló en confirmar.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าการเริ่มทำงานด้วยกุญแจชุดเดียวล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการยืนยัน VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>One-key startup configuration failed because: failed to obtain ESK VC.</EN>
      <CH>一键启动配置失败，原因为：获取ESK VC失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de arranque de una llave falló debido a: falló en obtener VC de ESK.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าการเริ่มทำงานด้วยกุญแจชุดเดียวล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเรียกข้อมูล ESK VC ได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>One-key startup configuration failed because VIN write failed.</EN>
      <CH>一键启动配置失败，原因为：VIN写入失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail7</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de arranque de una llave falló debido a que falló la escritura de VIN.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าการเริ่มทำงานด้วยกุญแจชุดเดียวล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเขียน VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>One-key startup configuration failed because: the whole car configuration code failed to write.</EN>
      <CH>一键启动配置失败，原因为：整车配置代码写入失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail8</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de arranque de una llave falló debido a: el código de configuración del vehículo completo falló en escribirse.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าการเริ่มทำงานด้วยกุญแจชุดเดียวล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเขียนรหัสการกำหนดค่าของรถทั้งคันล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL Learning Failure, Cause of Failure: ESCL Checking ESK Failure</EN>
      <CH>ESCL学习失败，失败原因：ESCL检查ESK失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail9_1</FL>
      <MX>Falla de programación de ESCL, causa de falla: Falla de verificación de ESK de ESCL</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการตรวจสอบ ESK ของ ESCL ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL Learning Failure, Cause of Failure: Severe Level DTC</EN>
      <CH>ESCL学习失败，失败原因：严重等级的DTC</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail9_10</FL>
      <MX>Falla de programación de ESCL, causa de falla: DTC de nivel severo</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก DTC ที่ร้ายแรง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL Learning Failure, Cause of Failure: Other Errors</EN>
      <CH>ESCL学习失败，失败原因：其他错误</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail9_11</FL>
      <MX>Falla de programación de ESCL, causa de falla: Otros errores</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดอื่นๆ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL Learning Failure, Cause of Failure: Vehicle Power State Non-OFF</EN>
      <CH>ESCL学习失败，失败原因：车辆电源状态非OFF</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail9_12</FL>
      <MX>Falla de programación de ESCL, causa de falla: Estado de energía de vehículo No apagado</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากสถานะของกำลังไฟฟ้าของรถไม่เป็น OFF</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL Learning Failure, Cause of Failure: Internal Failure of ESCL</EN>
      <CH>ESCL学习失败，失败原因：ESCL 内部故障</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail9_2</FL>
      <MX>Falla de programación de ESCL, causa de falla: Falla interna de ESCL</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการทำงานล้มเหลวภายใน ESCL</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL Learning Failure, Reasons for Failure: ESCL Learned</EN>
      <CH>ESCL学习失败，失败原因：已经学过的ESCL</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail9_3</FL>
      <MX>Falla de programación de ESCL, Razones de falla: ESCL programado</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก ESCL ได้รับการเรียนรู้ค่าแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL Learning Failure, Cause of Failure: ESCL Communication Failure</EN>
      <CH>ESCL学习失败，失败原因：ESCL通讯失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail9_4</FL>
      <MX>Falla de programación de ESCL, causa de falla: Falla de comunicación de ESCL</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการติดต่อสื่อสารของ ESCL ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL Learning Failure, Cause of Failure: ESCL Power Failure</EN>
      <CH>ESCL学习失败，失败原因：ESCL上电失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail9_5</FL>
      <MX>Falla de programación de ESCL, causa de falla: Falla de energía de ESCL</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากกำลังไฟฟ้าของ ESCL ทำงานล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL Learning Failure, Cause of Failure: Vehicle Voltage Fault</EN>
      <CH>ESCL学习失败，失败原因：车辆电压故障</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail9_6</FL>
      <MX>Falla de programación de ESCL, causa de falla: Falla de voltaje de vehículo</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากแรงดันไฟฟ้าของรถทำงานล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL Learning Failure, Reasons for Failure: Unknown Reasons.</EN>
      <CH>ESCL学习失败，失败原因：未知原因。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail9_7</FL>
      <MX>Falla de programación de ESCL, Razones de falla: Razones desconocidas.</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ ESCL ล้มเหลวโดยไม่ทราบสาเหตุ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL Learning Failure, Cause of Failure: ESK Data Problem</EN>
      <CH>ESCL学习失败，失败原因：ESK数据问题</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail9_8</FL>
      <MX>Falla de programación de ESCL, causa de falla: Problema de datos de ESK</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากปัญหาของข้อมูล ESK</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>ESCL Learning Failure, Cause of Failure: PEPS ECU Failure</EN>
      <CH>ESCL学习失败，失败原因：PEPS ECU 故障</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Fail9_9</FL>
      <MX>Falla de programación de ESCL, causa de falla: Falla de comunicación de ECU de PEPS</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ ESCL ล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก PEPS ECU ทำงานล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The configuration was started successfully with one key.</EN>
      <CH>一键启动配置成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Success</FL>
      <MX>La configuración comenzó exitosamente con una llave.</MX>
      <TH>การเริ่มการกำหนดค่าเป็นผลสำเร็จโดยการใช้กุญแจเพียงชุดเดียว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The PEPS matching result uploaded successfully, please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>PEPS匹配结果上传成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Success1</FL>
      <MX>Resultado de empate PEPS cargado con éxito, gire el interruptor de ignición a la posición OFF (apagado) por más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการจับคู่ PEPS สำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The current controller is locked and will stop for 5 minutes at this interface. Please wait a moment.</EN>
      <CH>当前控制器被锁住，会在该界面停止5分钟，请稍后</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Mult_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>El controlador actual está bloqueado y se detendrá por 5 minutos en esta interfaz. Espere un momento.</MX>
      <TH>ตัวควบคุมในปัจจุบันถูกล็อค และจะหยุดทำงานเป็นเวลา 5 นาทีที่อินเตอร์เฟสนี้ โปรดรอสักครู่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The PEPS reset failed because OBD was disconnected.</EN>
      <CH>PEPS复位失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Reset_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>El restablecimiento de PEPS falló debido a que el OBD estaba desconectado.</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต PEPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจาก OBD ถูกปลดออก</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The PEPS reset failed because the after-sales server could not be accessed.</EN>
      <CH>PEPS复位失败，原因为：无法访问售后服务器。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Reset_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>El restablecimiento de PEPS falló debido a que no se pudo tener acceso al servidor post-venta.</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต PEPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าถึงเซิร์ฟเวอร์หลังการขายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Three keys match, do not meet PEPS reset requirements.The number of PEPS matching keys can be reduced to less than 3 through CN200S PEPS matching program (new key (original key failure)- after-sales maintenance program v1.0-ok.</EN>
      <CH>已经匹配了三把钥匙，不符合PEPS复位的要求，可以通过《CN200S PEPS匹配（新增钥匙（原钥匙失效））-售后返修程序V1.0-ok》程序，将PEPS匹配的钥匙数量，减少至小于三把！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Reset_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Tres llaves empatadas, no cumple los requerimientos de restablecimiento de PEPS. El número de llaves de empate de PEPS se puede reducir a menos de 3 a través del programa de empate de PEPS CN200S (falla de llave original)- programa de mantenimiento post-venta v1.0-ok.</MX>
      <TH>มีการจับคู่กุญแจ 3 ชุด ซึ่งไม่เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขของการรีเซ็ต PEPS สามารถลดจำนวนกุญแจที่จับคู่ของ PEPS ให้น้อยกว่า 3 ได้โดยใช้โปรแกรมการจับคู่ CN200S PEPS (กุญแจชุดใหม่ (กุญแจดั้งเดิมไม่ทำงาน) )- โปรแกรมการบำรุงรักษาหลังการขาย  v1.0 - ตกลง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The PEPS reset failed because unknown error.

</EN>
      <CH>PEPS复位失败，原因为：未知错误。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Reset_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>Falló el restablecimiento de PEPS debido a error desconocido.

</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต PEPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดที่ไม่รู้จัก

</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The PEPS reset failed because VIN code reading failed.

</EN>
      <CH>PEPS复位失败，原因为：读取VIN码失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Reset_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>El restablecimiento de PEPS falló debido a que falló la lectura del código VIN.

</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต PEPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการอ่านรหัส VIN ล้มเหลว

</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The PEPS reset failed because the server does not have the car information.

</EN>
      <CH>PEPS复位失败，原因为：服务器无该车信息。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Reset_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>Falla de restablecimiento de PEPS debida a que el servidor no tiene información del vehículo.

</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต PEPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากเซิร์ฟเวอร์ไม่มีข้อมูลของรถ

</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The PEPS reset failed because general reasons.

</EN>
      <CH>PEPS复位失败，原因为：一般原因。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Reset_Fail7</FL>
      <MX>El restablecimiento de PEPS falló debido a razones generales.

</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต PEPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากสาเหตุทั่วไป

</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The PEPS reset failed because VIN code clearance failed.

</EN>
      <CH>PEPS复位失败，原因为：VIN码清除失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Reset_Fail8</FL>
      <MX>El restablecimiento de PEPS falló debido a que falló la eliminación del código VIN.

</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ต PEPS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการลบรหัส VIN ล้มเหลว

</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The PEPS reset result upload failed.

</EN>
      <CH>PEPS复位结果上传失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Reset_Fail9</FL>
      <MX>Falló la carga del resultado de restablecimiento de PEPS.

</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการรีเซ็ต PEPS ล้มเหลว

</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>PEPS reset result uploaded successfully, please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>PEPS复位结果上传成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Reset_Success</FL>
      <MX>Resultado de restablecimiento de PEPS cargado con éxito, gire el interruptor de ignición a la posición OFF (apagado) por más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการรีเซ็ต PEPS สำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Reset successfully (anti-theft information ESK was successfully cleared), and then the VIN code is cleared!</EN>
      <CH>复位成功（防盗信息ESK被成功清除），接下来进行清除VIN码操作！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Reset_Success1</FL>
      <MX>¡Restablecimiento exitoso (ESK de información anti-robo se eliminó exitosamente), y el código VIN se eliminó!</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ตสำเร็จแล้ว (การลบข้อมูลระบบกันขโมย ESK สำเร็จแล้ว) และได้ลบรหัส VIN แล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>1. VIN code clearance success! \n2. Please disassemble the PEPS module and install it on the target vehicle. \n then match it with CN200S PEPS Matching (Multifunctional Version) - After-sales Repair Procedure.</EN>
      <CH>1、VIN码清除成功！\n2、请将PEPS模块拆卸下来，安装至目标车辆上，\n然后使用《CN200S PEPS匹配（多功能版）-售后返修程序》程序进行匹配！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Reset_Success2</FL>
      <MX>1. ¡Éxito de eliminación de código VIN! \n2. Por favor desensamble el módulo PEPS e instálelo en el vehículo objetivo. \n Después empate con PEPS CN200S (Versión multifuncional) - Procedimiento de reparación post-venta.</MX>
      <TH>1. การลบรหัส VIN สำเร็จแล้ว \n2. โปรดถอดโมดูล PEPS และติดตั้งลงในรถเป้าหมาย \n จากนั้นให้ทำการจับคู่โดยใช้ การจับคู่ CN200S PEPS (เวอร์ชั่นแบบมัลติฟังก์ชัน) - ขั้นตอนการซ่อมหลังการขาย</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>It's already matched.</EN>
      <CH>已经匹配了</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Reset_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Ya está empatado.</MX>
      <TH>ได้จับคู่ไว้แล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>keys have been matched!(meet PEPS reset requirements)</EN>
      <CH>把钥匙！（符合PEPS复位要求）</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Reset_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>¡las llaves se empataron! (cumple los requerimientos de restablecimiento de PEPS)</MX>
      <TH>กุญแจได้รับการจับคู่แล้ว (เป็นไปตามเงื่อนไขของการรีเซ็ต PEPS)</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>1. The reset of PEPS must be carried out on the original vehicle; \n2. After successful reset, the PEPS will be used on the original vehicle and other vehicles to re-match the PEPS anti-theft system. \n 3. The number of keys that PEPS has matched must be less than three. (The next step program automatically detects the number of keys that have been matched)</EN>
      <CH>1、PEPS复位，必须在“原车”上进行；\n2、复位成功后，该PEPS将可用于"原车"和其他车辆，重新匹配PEPS防盗系统。\n3、PEPS已经匹配的钥匙数量必须小于三把。（后续步骤程序会自动检测已经匹配的钥匙数量）</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_Reset_Tip3</FL>
      <MX>1. El restablecimiento de PEPS se debe realizar en el vehículo original; \n2. Después del restablecimiento exitoso, el PEPS se usará en el vehículo original y otros vehículos para volver a empatar el sistema anti-robo PEPS. \n 3. El número de llaves que el PEPS empata debe ser menor a tres. (El siguiente paso del programa detecta automáticamente el número de llaves que se han empatado)</MX>
      <TH>1. การรีเซ็ต PEPS จะต้องทำในรถคันเดิม; \n2. หลังจากการรีเซ็ตสำเร็จแล้ว จะสามารถนำ PEPS ไปใช้ในรถคันดั้งเดิมและรถคันอื่นๆ เพื่อทำการจับคู่ระบบกันขโมย PEPS อีกครั้งได้ \n 3. จำนวนกุญแจที่ PEPS ได้ทำการจับคู่แล้วจะต้องต่ำกว่า 3 (การตั้งโปรแกรมขั้นตอนถัดไปจะตรวจจับจำนวนกุญแจที่จับคู่แล้วโดยอัตโนมัติ)</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The PLG calibration failed because OBD was not connected.</EN>
      <CH>PLG标定失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PLGCa_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de PLG falló porque OBD no estaba conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบ PLG ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The PLG calibration failed because unknown reasons.</EN>
      <CH>PLG标定失败,原因为：未知原因。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PLGCa_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de PLG falló debido a razones desconocidas.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบ PLG ล้มเหลวโดยไม่ทราบสาเหตุ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>PLG calibration is successful, please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>电动尾门解除调试成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PLGCa_Re_Success</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de PLG es exitosa, cambie el interruptor de ignición a la posición OFF durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบ PLG สำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>PLG Calibration success</EN>
      <CH>PLG标定成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PLGCa_Success</FL>
      <MX>Éxito de calibración de PLG</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบ PLG สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>During the learning process, the tail door will be fully closed to fully open. Make sure there is enough room for operation.</EN>
      <CH>学习过程中尾门会从全闭到全开，请确保有足够的操作空间。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PLGCa_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Durante el proceso de programación, la puerta trasera se cerrará y abrirá completamente. Asegúrese que haya suficiente espacio para la operación.</MX>
      <TH>ในระหว่างกระบวนการเรียนรู้ค่า ประตูท้ายจะเคลื่อนที่จากตำแหน่งปิดสุดไปที่ตำแหน่งเปิดสุด ตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่ามีพื้นที่เพียงพอสำหรับการทำงานนี้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Refresh failed</EN>
      <CH>刷新失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Refresh_Fail</FL>
      <MX>Falló la actualización</MX>
      <TH>การรีเฟรชล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The server connection failed. </EN>
      <CH>刷新失败，原因为：访问售后服务器失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Refresh_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falló la conexión del servidor. </MX>
      <TH>การเชื่อมต่อเซิร์ฟเวอร์ล้มเหลว </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Erase FLASH failed.</EN>
      <CH>擦除FLASH失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Refresh_Fail10</FL>
      <MX>Falló el borrado de FLASH.</MX>
      <TH>การลบ FLASH ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Data validation failed.</EN>
      <CH>数据校验失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Refresh_Fail11</FL>
      <MX>Falló la validación de datos.</MX>
      <TH>การตรวจสอบความถูกต้องของข้อมูลล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Write VIN Failed</EN>
      <CH>写入VIN失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Refresh_Fail12</FL>
      <MX>Falló la escritura de VIN</MX>
      <TH>การเขียน VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>OBD connection failed. </EN>
      <CH>刷新失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Refresh_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Falló la conexión de OBD. </MX>
      <TH>การเชื่อมต่อ OBD ล้มเหลว </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>VIN failed.</EN>
      <CH>刷新失败，原因为：VIN确认失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Refresh_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Falló el VIN.</MX>
      <TH>VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>session failed. </EN>
      <CH>切换会话失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Refresh_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>falló la sesión. </MX>
      <TH>เซสชั่นล้มเหลว </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Security access failed.</EN>
      <CH>安全访问失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Refresh_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>Falló el acceso de seguridad.</MX>
      <TH>การเข้าถึงระบบนิรภัยล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Module reset failed.</EN>
      <CH>模块复位失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Refresh_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>Falló el restablecimiento del módulo.</MX>
      <TH>การรีเซ็ตโมดูลล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The request for download failed. </EN>
      <CH>请求下载失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Refresh_Fail7</FL>
      <MX>Falló la solicitud de descarga. </MX>
      <TH>การร้องขอการดาวน์โหลดล้มเหลว </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Data transmission failed.</EN>
      <CH>传输数据失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Refresh_Fail8</FL>
      <MX>Falló la transmisión de datos.</MX>
      <TH>การส่งข้อมูลล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The request for exit failed. </EN>
      <CH>请求退出失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Refresh_Fail9</FL>
      <MX>Falló la solicitud de salida. </MX>
      <TH>การร้องขอการออกล้มเหลว </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The refresh is successful. Please switch the ignition switch to the OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>刷新成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Refresh_Success</FL>
      <MX>Actualización exitosa. Cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การรีเฟรชสำเร็จแล้ว ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Current Vehicle VIN:\n</EN>
      <CH>请确认当前车辆VIN是否为:\n</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Refresh_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>VIN de vehículo actual:\n</MX>
      <TH>VIN ของรถในปัจจุบัน:\n</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Input VIN:</EN>
      <CH>请输入VIN:</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Refresh_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Ingrese el VIN:</MX>
      <TH>ป้อน VIN:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Software version:</EN>
      <CH>刷新软件号为：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Refresh_Tip3</FL>
      <MX>Versión del software:</MX>
      <TH>เวอร์ชั่นของซอฟต์แวร์:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>RSM learning success, please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>RSM学习成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_RSM_Instructions_Success</FL>
      <MX>Éxito de programación de RSM, cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของ RSM สำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The SCU calibration failed because OBD was not connected.</EN>
      <CH>SCU标定失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_SCUCali_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de SCU falló porque el OBD no estaba conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบ SCU ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>SCU calibration failed because of: motor failure.</EN>
      <CH>SCU标定失败,原因为：电机故障。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_SCUCali_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de SCU falló debido a: falla de motor.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบ SCU ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากมอเตอร์ทำงานล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>SCU calibration failed because: calibration data range error.</EN>
      <CH>SCU标定失败,原因为：标定数据范围错误。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_SCUCali_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Falla de calibración de SCU debido a: error de rango de datos de calibración.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบ SCU ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดของช่วงข้อมูลการปรับเทียบ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>SCU calibration failed because of: actuator sensor failure.</EN>
      <CH>SCU标定失败,原因为：执行器传感器故障。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_SCUCali_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de SCU falló debido a: falla de sensor de actuador.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบ SCU ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากเซ็นเซอร์ตัวสั่งงานทำงานล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>SCU calibration failed because: actuator supply voltage is not correct.</EN>
      <CH>SCU标定失败,原因为：执行器供电电压不正确。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_SCUCali_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>Falla de calibración de SCU debida a: voltaje de suministro de actuador incorrecto.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบ SCU ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากแรงดันไฟจ่ายของตัวสั่งงานไม่ถูกต้อง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>SCU calibration failed because of an unknown error.</EN>
      <CH>SCU标定失败,原因为：未知错误。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_SCUCali_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>Calibración de SCU falló debido a un error desconocido.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบ SCU ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดที่ไม่รู้จัก</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>SCU calibration is successful, please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>SCU标定成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_SCUCali_Success</FL>
      <MX>La calibración de SCU es exitosa, cambie el interruptor de ignición a la posición OFF durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบ SCU สำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Airbag module configuration failed because OBD was not connected.</EN>
      <CH>安全气囊模块配置失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_SDM_Con_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de módulo de bolsa de aire falló porque OBD no estaba conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าโมดูลถุงลมนิรภัยล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Airbag module configuration failed.</EN>
      <CH>安全气囊模块配置失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_SDM_Con_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Falló la configuración del módulo de bolsa de aire.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าโมดูลถุงลมนิรภัยล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The configuration of airbag module is successful. Please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>安全气囊模块配置成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_SDM_Con_Success</FL>
      <MX>Configuración de módulo de bolsa de aire exitosa. Cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าโมดูลถุงลมนิรภัยสำเร็จแล้ว ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TBOX replacement failed because the after-sales server could not be accessed.</EN>
      <CH>TBOX换件失败，原因为：无法访问售后服务器。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>El reemplazo de TBOX falló debido a que no se pudo tener acceso al servidor post-venta.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยน TBOX ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าถึงเซิร์ฟเวอร์หลังการขายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>TSP result error</EN>
      <CH>TSP结果错误，换件失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Fail10</FL>
      <MX>Error de resultado de TSP</MX>
      <TH>ข้อผิดพลาดของผลลัพธ์ TSP</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>TSP public key not generated</EN>
      <CH>TSP公钥未生成，换件失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Fail11</FL>
      <MX>No se generó llave pública de TSP</MX>
      <TH>ไม่มีการสร้างรหัสสาธารณะ TSP  ขึ้น</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>TSP reject</EN>
      <CH>TSP拒收，换件失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Fail12</FL>
      <MX>Rechazo de TSP</MX>
      <TH>การปฏิเสธ TSP</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>initial</EN>
      <CH>初始状态</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Fail13</FL>
      <MX>inicial</MX>
      <TH>เริ่มต้น</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure, please contact after sales</EN>
      <CH>换件失败，请联系售后人员。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Fail14</FL>
      <MX>Falla, póngase en contacto con post-venta</MX>
      <TH>ล้มเหลว โปรดติดต่อฝ่ายหลังการขาย</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TBOX replacement failed because OBD is not connected.</EN>
      <CH>TBOX换件失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>El reemplazo de TBOX falló debido a que el OBD no está conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยน TBOX ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TBOX replacement failed because VIN code failed.</EN>
      <CH>TBOX换件失败，原因为：VIN码失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>El reemplazo de TBOX falló debido a falla de código de VIN.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยน TBOX ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากรหัส VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TBOX replacement failed because failed to get ESK.</EN>
      <CH>TBOX换件失败，原因为：获取ESK失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>El reemplazo de TBOX falló debido a falla en obtener ESK.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยน TBOX ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเรียกข้อมูล ESK ได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>No Network</EN>
      <CH>无网络信号，换件失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>No hay red</MX>
      <TH>ไม่มีเครือข่าย</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>PDP Context Fail</EN>
      <CH>PDP连接失败，换件失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>Falla de conexión de PDP</MX>
      <TH>การเชื่อมต่อ PDP ล้มเหลว การเปลี่ยนล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>TSP connection fail</EN>
      <CH>和TSP通讯失败，换件失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Fail7</FL>
      <MX>Falla de conexión de TSP</MX>
      <TH>การเชื่อมต่อ TSP ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>TBOX ID unmatch</EN>
      <CH>T-BOX ID不匹配，换件失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Fail8</FL>
      <MX>ID de TBOX no coincide</MX>
      <TH>ID ของ TBOX ไม่ตรงกัน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Key exchange processing timeout</EN>
      <CH>密钥交换处理超时，换件失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Fail9</FL>
      <MX>Expiración de tiempo de procesamiento de intercambio de llave</MX>
      <TH>กระบวนการเปลี่ยนรหัสหมดเวลาทำงานแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>After the TBOX key exchange fails and the vehicle is powered on again, wait for 2min and check the secret key exchange result again.</EN>
      <CH>TBOX密钥交换失败重新车辆上电后，等待2min后，再次检查秘钥交换结果。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Read_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Después que falla el intercambio de llave de TBOX y el vehículo se vuelve a encender, espere 2 minutos y revise el resultado de intercambio de llave secreta de nuevo.</MX>
      <TH>หลังจากการเปลี่ยนรหัส TBOX ล้มเหลว และปรับสวิตช์กุญแจของรถไปที่ตำแหน่ง ON อีกครั้ง ให้รอเป็นเวลา 2 นาที จากนั้นให้ตรวจสอบผลของการเปลี่ยนรหัสลับอีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TBOX Key exchange successful.</EN>
      <CH>TBOX密钥交换成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Read_Success</FL>
      <MX>Intercambio de llave TBOX exitoso.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนรหัส TBOX สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>TBOX replacement was successful.</EN>
      <CH>TBOX换件成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Success</FL>
      <MX>El reemplazo de TBOX fue exitoso.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยน TBOX สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Write successfully, please wait for about 3 minutes in this interface, after the time arrives, automatically read the results, without operation.</EN>
      <CH>写入成功，请在该界面等待约3分钟，时间到后自动读取结果，无需操作。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TBOX_Replace_Success1</FL>
      <MX>Escritura exitosa, espere aproximadamente 3 minutos en esta interfaz, después que termine el tiempo, lee automáticamente los resultados, sin operación.</MX>
      <TH>การเขียนสำเร็จแล้ว โปรดรออยู่ในหน้าจอนี้เป็นเวลาประมาณ 3 นาที หลังจากนั้นจะมีการอ่านผลลัพธ์โดยอัตโนมัติโดยไม่ต้องดำเนินการใดๆ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The AMT clutch exhaust failure because OBD is not connected.</EN>
      <CH>AMT离合器排气失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TCM_Exhaust_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Falla de purga de embrague de AMT debida a que el OBD no está conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การไล่ลมคลัตช์ AMT ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The AMT clutch exhaust is successful, please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>AMT离合器排气成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TCM_Exhaust_Success</FL>
      <MX>La purga de embrague de AMT es exitosa, cambie el interruptor de ignición a la posición OFF durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การไล่ลมคลัตช์ AMT สำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please open the oil valve, and confirm the liquid flowing out of the state, whether to continue to exhaust?</EN>
      <CH>请打开放油阀,并确认流出的液体状态，是否继续排气？</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TCM_Exhaust_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>Abra la válvula de aceite, y confirme que el estado de flujo del líquido, ¿continúa purgándose?</MX>
      <TH>โปรดเปิดวาล์วน้ำมัน และยืนยันว่ามีน้ำมันไหลออกมา ต้องการทำการไล่ลมต่อไปหรือไม่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please close the drain valve.</EN>
      <CH>请关闭放油阀。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TCM_Exhaust_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>Cierre la válvula de drenaje.</MX>
      <TH>ปิดวาล์วระบาย</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please hang in the P file and try again.</EN>
      <CH>请挂入P档重新尝试。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TCM_Replace_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>Coloque la posición P e intente de nuevo.</MX>
      <TH>เข้าเกียร์ P แล้วลองอีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Replacement failed for unknown reasons.</EN>
      <CH>更换失败，原因未知。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TCM_Replace_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>Falló el reemplazo por razones desconocidas.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนล้มเหลวโดยไม่ทราบสาเหตุ</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Successful replacement, wait 10 seconds to re-energize ON gear.</EN>
      <CH>更换成功，等待10秒后重新上电ON档。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TCM_Replace_Success</FL>
      <MX>Reemplazo exitoso, espere 10 segundos para volver a energizar la posición ON (encendido).</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนสำเร็จแล้ว ให้รอเป็นเวลา 10 วินาที จากนั้นให้ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง ON</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TICE replacement failed because OBD is not connected.</EN>
      <CH>TICE换件失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TICE_Replace_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>El reemplazo de TICE falló debido a que el OBD no está conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยน TICE ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>TSP refused, in a failure.</EN>
      <CH>TSP拒收，换件失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TICE_Replace_Fail10</FL>
      <MX>TSP rechazado. Falla de reemplazo.</MX>
      <TH>TSP ปฏิเสธ การเปลี่ยนล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The initial state</EN>
      <CH>初始状态</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TICE_Replace_Fail11</FL>
      <MX>Estado inicial</MX>
      <TH>สถานะเริ่มต้น</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>In a failure, please contact after sales staff.</EN>
      <CH>换件失败，请联系售后人员。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TICE_Replace_Fail12</FL>
      <MX>En una falla, póngase en contacto con el personal post-venta.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนล้มเหลว โปรดติดต่อพนักงานฝ่ายหลังการขาย</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>T - ICE in a failure, the reason is: failed to get ESK.</EN>
      <CH>T-ICE换件失败，原因为：获取ESK失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TICE_Replace_Fail13</FL>
      <MX>T - ICE con falla, razón: falla en obtener ESK.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยน T - ICE ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเรียกข้อมูล ESK</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TICE replacement failed because VIN code failed.</EN>
      <CH>TICE换件失败，原因为：VIN码失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TICE_Replace_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>El reemplazo de TICE falló debido a falla de código de VIN.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยน TICE ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากรหัส VIN ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>No network signal, in a failure.</EN>
      <CH>无网络信号，换件失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TICE_Replace_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>No hay señal de red, falla.</MX>
      <TH>ไม่มีสัญญาณเครือข่าย การเปลี่ยนล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>PDP connection fails, a failure.</EN>
      <CH>PDP连接失败，换件失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TICE_Replace_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>Falla de conexión de PDP. Falla de reemplazo.</MX>
      <TH>การทำงานล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเชื่อมต่อ PDP ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>And TSP communication failure, a failure</EN>
      <CH>和TSP通讯失败，换件失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TICE_Replace_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>Y falla de comunicación de TSP, falla</MX>
      <TH>และการทำงานล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการติดต่อสื่อสาร TSP ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>T - ICE ID does not match, in a failure.</EN>
      <CH>T-ICE ID不匹配，换件失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TICE_Replace_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>ID de T - ICE no coincide, falla.</MX>
      <TH>ID ของ T - ICE ไม่ตรงกัน การเปลี่ยนล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Key exchange processing timeout, in a failure.</EN>
      <CH>密钥交换处理超时，换件失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TICE_Replace_Fail7</FL>
      <MX>Expiración de tiempo de procesamiento de intercambio de llave, falla.</MX>
      <TH>กระบวนการเปลี่ยนรหัสหมดเวลาทำงานแล้ว การเปลี่ยนล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>TSP result error, change a failure.</EN>
      <CH>TSP结果错误，换件失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TICE_Replace_Fail8</FL>
      <MX>Error de resultado de TSP, cambio de falla.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนล้มเหลวเนื่องจากข้อผิดพลาดของผลลัพธ์ TSP</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TSP public key is not generated, in a failure.</EN>
      <CH>TSP公钥未生成，换件失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TICE_Replace_Fail9</FL>
      <MX>No se generó llave pública de TSP, falla.</MX>
      <TH>ไม่มีการสร้างรหัสสาธารณะ TSP ขึ้น การเปลี่ยนล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>TICE key exchange failed to check the result of the secret key exchange again after 2min waiting for the TICE key exchange to fail to power the vehicle again.</EN>
      <CH>TICE密钥交换失败重新车辆上电后，等待2min后，再次检查秘钥交换结果。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TICE_Replace_Read_Fail</FL>
      <MX>El intercambio de llave TICE falló. Espere 2 minutos después de encender el vehículo y verifique el resultado de intercambio de llave de nuevo.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนรหัส TICE ล้มเหลว รอเป็นเวลา 2 นาทีหลังจากที่ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF แล้วตรวจสอบผลการเปลี่ยนรหัสอีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TICE Key exchange successful.</EN>
      <CH>TICE密钥交换成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TICE_Replace_Read_Success</FL>
      <MX>Intercambio de llave TICE exitoso.</MX>
      <TH>การเปลี่ยนรหัส TICE สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>TICE in a success.</EN>
      <CH>TICE换件成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TICE_Replace_Success</FL>
      <MX>Éxito de TICE.</MX>
      <TH>TICE สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>TICE key fires successfully and waits 2 minutes before reading the result of the key exchange.</EN>
      <CH>TICE更换触发成功，请在该界面等待约3分钟，时间到后自动读取结果，无需操作。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TICE_Replace_Success1</FL>
      <MX>Activación exitosa de llave TICE y espera 2 minutos antes de leer el resultado del intercambio de llave.</MX>
      <TH>การกระตุ้นการเปลี่ยนรหัส TICE สำเร็จแล้ว รอเป็นเวลา 2 นาทีก่อนที่จะอ่านผลการเปลี่ยนรหัส</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TPMS configuration failed because OBD was not connected.</EN>
      <CH>TPMS配置失败，原因为：OBD未连接。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_Con_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de TPMS falló porque OBD no estaba conectado.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่า TPMS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่มีการเชื่อมต่อ OBD</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TPMS configuration failed because failed to enter the extension session.</EN>
      <CH>TPMS配置失败，原因为：进入扩展会话失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_Con_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de TPMS falló debido a que falló en ingresar la sesión extendida.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่า TPMS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถเข้าสู่เซสชั่นแบบขยายได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TPMS configuration failed because security access failed.</EN>
      <CH>TPMS配置失败，原因为：安全访问失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_Con_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de TPMS falló debido a falla de acceso de seguridad.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่า TPMS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเข้าถึงระบบนิรภัยล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TPMS configuration failed because write tire pressure failed.</EN>
      <CH>TPMS配置失败，原因为：写入胎压失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_Con_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de TPMS falló debido a que falló la escritura de presión de la llanta.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่า TPMS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเขียนความดันลมยางล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TPMS configuration failed because failed to read tire pressure.</EN>
      <CH>TPMS配置失败，原因为：读取胎压失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_Con_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>La configuración TPMS falló debido a que falló leer la presión de la llanta.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่า TPMS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถอ่านความดันลมยางได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TPMS configuration failed because tire pressure standard pressure value configuration failed.</EN>
      <CH>TPMS配置失败，原因是：胎压标准气压值配置失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_Con_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de TPMS falló debido a que falló la configuración de valor de presión estándar de presión de llanta.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่า TPMS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการกำหนดค่าความดันลมยางมาตรฐานล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TPMS configuration failed because high pressure alarm compensation pressure value configuration failed.</EN>
      <CH>TPMS配置失败，原因是：高压报警补偿气压值配置失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_Con_Fail7</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de TPMS falló debido a que falló la configuración de valor de presión de compensación de alarma de alta presión de llanta.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่า TPMS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการกำหนดค่าความดันลมยางสำหรับการชดเชยสัญญาณเตือนล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TPMS configuration failed because failure to clear fault code.</EN>
      <CH>TPMS配置失败，原因为：清除故障码失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_Con_Fail8</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de TPMS falló debido a falla en borrar el código de falla.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่า TPMS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการลบรหัสข้อบกพร่องล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The TPMS configuration failed because the return default reply failed.</EN>
      <CH>TPMS配置失败，原因为：返回默认回话失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_Con_Fail9</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de TPMS falló debido a falla de respuesta predeterminada de retorno.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่า TPMS ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการส่งค่าเริ่มต้นกลับล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>TPMS configuration is successful, please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>TPMS配置成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_Con_Success</FL>
      <MX>La configuración de TPMS es exitosa, cambie el interruptor de ignición a la posición OFF durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่า TPMS สำเร็จแล้ว โปรดปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The online configuration failed because of the failure to clear the sensor ID</EN>
      <CH>在线配置失败，原因为：清除传感器ID失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_ConK_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea falló debido a la falla en eliminar la ID del sensor</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากไม่สามารถลบ ID ของเซ็นเซอร์ได้</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>he online configuration failed because the sensor ID learning failed.</EN>
      <CH>在线配置失败，原因为：传感器ID学习失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_ConK_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>La configuración en línea falló debido a falla de programación de ID de sensor.</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์ล้มเหลวเนื่องจากการเรียนรู้ ID ของเซ็นเซอร์ล้มเหลว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Sensor learning failed, please repair or try again.</EN>
      <CH>传感器学习失败，请返修或重新尝试。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_ConK_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>Falló la programación del sensor, repare o intente de nuevo.</MX>
      <TH>การเรียนรู้ค่าของเซ็นเซอร์ล้มเหลว โปรดทำการแก้ไขแล้วลองอีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failure to configure standard tire pressure! Please repair or try again.</EN>
      <CH>胎压标准气压值配置失败！请返修或重新尝试。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_ConK_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>¡Falla en configurar presión de llanta estándar! Repare o intente de nuevo.</MX>
      <TH>ไม่สามารถกำหนดความดันลมยางมาตรฐานได้ โปรดทำการแก้ไขแล้วลองอีกครั้ง</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>TPMS Online Configuration Successful</EN>
      <CH>TPMS在线配置成功</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_ConK_Success</FL>
      <MX>Configuración en línea de TPMS exitosa</MX>
      <TH>การกำหนดค่าแบบออนไลน์สำหรับ TPMS สำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Left front wheel:</EN>
      <CH>左前轮：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_ConK_Tip1_1</FL>
      <MX>Rueda delantera izquierda:</MX>
      <TH>ล้อหน้าซ้าย:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Right front wheel:</EN>
      <CH>右前轮：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_ConK_Tip1_2</FL>
      <MX>Rueda delantera derecha:</MX>
      <TH>ล้อหน้าขวา:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>\n Right rear wheel:</EN>
      <CH>\n右后轮：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_ConK_Tip1_3</FL>
      <MX>\n Rueda trasera derecha:</MX>
      <TH>\n ล้อหลังขวา:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Left rear wheel:</EN>
      <CH>左后轮：</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_ConK_Tip1_4</FL>
      <MX>Rueda trasera izquierda:</MX>
      <TH>ล้อหลังซ้าย:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>\n Please confirm the consistency</EN>
      <CH>\n请确认是否一致</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_ConK_Tip1_5</FL>
      <MX>\n Por favor confirme la consistencia</MX>
      <TH>\n โปรดยืนยันความสอดคล้องกัน</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please wake up with a handheld device the sensor of</EN>
      <CH>请用手持设备唤醒</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_ConK_Tip2_1</FL>
      <MX>Active con un dispositivo portátil</MX>
      <TH>โปรดกระตุ้นให้กลับมาทำงานโดยใช้อุปกรณ์แบบพกพา</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>please wait a moment.</EN>
      <CH>的传感器后，请稍等</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_ConK_Tip2_2</FL>
      <MX>espere un momento.</MX>
      <TH>โปรดรอสักครู่</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please confirm the sensor of</EN>
      <CH>请确认</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_ConK_Tip3_1</FL>
      <MX>Confirme el sensor de</MX>
      <TH>โปรดยืนยันเซ็นเซอร์</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>\n Is the nID value correct ID:</EN>
      <CH>的传感器,\nID值是否正确ID:</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_TPMS_ConK_Tip3_2</FL>
      <MX>\n Es la ID correcta de valor de ID:</MX>
      <TH>\n ค่า nID เป็น ID ที่ถูกต้องหรือไม่:</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Calibration successfully.</EN>
      <CH>标定成功。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_360Cali_Success1</FL>
      <MX>Calibración exitosa.</MX>
      <TH>การปรับเทียบสำเร็จแล้ว</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The ESCL reset result has been uploaded successfully. Please switch the ignition switch to OFF gear for more than 30 seconds.</EN>
      <CH>ESCL复位结果上传成功，请将点火开关切换至OFF档30秒以上。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Success1</FL>
      <MX>El resultado de restablecimiento de ESCL se cargó con éxito. Cambie el interruptor de ignición a OFF (apagado) durante más de 30 segundos.</MX>
      <TH>การอัพโหลดผลการรีเซ็ต ESCL สำเร็จแล้ว ปรับสวิตช์กุญแจไปที่ตำแหน่ง OFF เป็นเวลานานกว่า 30 วินาที</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>The car has no ESCL and does not need to do ESCL reset.</EN>
      <CH>该车无ESCL，不需要做ESCL复位</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_ESCLRe_Success2</FL>
      <MX>El vehículo no tiene ESCL y no se necesita restablecer el ESCL.</MX>
      <TH>รถไม่มี ESCL และไม่จำเป็นต้องทำการรีเซ็ต ESCL</TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>OBD is not connected. Please check the connection status of OBD interface and try again.</EN>
      <CH>OBD未连接，请检查OBD接口连接状态后重试</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECMDieselReset_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Reset blinking oil life lamp successfully,please switch off the vehicle for at least 50 seconds in the end</EN>
      <CH>燃油灯重置成功，请关掉电源等待至少50s。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECMDieselReset_Success</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>1.将诊断仪连接至车辆OBD接头\n2.上电，启动发动机\n3.车辆档位在P档\n4.仅在GPF灯亮起时，才需要执行触发GPF再生操作\n5.触发GPF再生，最长将持续约1小时50分钟</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Tip1</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>进入GPF服务再生测试模式失败，请联系系统管理员。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>等待超时，触发GPF再生失败！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Fail2</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>断电更换完颗粒捕集器GPF后，将诊断仪连接至车辆OBD接头，点火开关在ON档\n注意：更换GPF传感器不需要执行该操作</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Tip2</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>同步GPF里程失败，请断电5分钟后重试</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Fail3</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>请查看诊断仪中的里程和仪表的里程是否一致，若一致，则里程复位成功，进入下一步；若不一致，则里程同步失败，需要重试。\n里程数:</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Info1</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>更换GPF操作完成，请将点火开关切换至OFF档至少1分钟，确保里程信息正常存储。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Success1</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>1.请确保现在连接的是旧ECU；\n2.将诊断仪连接至车辆OBD接头，点火开关在ON档</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Tip3</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>成功将GPF里程和碳载量写入新ECU，更换ECU操作完成，请将点火开关切换至OFF档至少1分钟，确保里程信息正常存储。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Success2</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>OBD未连接，请检查OBD接口连接状态后重试</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Common_OBD</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Lock ECM Customer Mode successful</EN>
      <CH>锁定成功</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECMLockMode_Success</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Lock ECM Customer Mode unsuccessful</EN>
      <CH>锁定失败</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ECMLockMode_Fail</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Please cut off the power supply, check the installation environment of the radar, adjust the installation position, and conduct the RSM after-sales calibration again.</EN>
      <CH>请断电，检查雷达安装环境，调整安装位置，并重新进行RSM售后校准</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_RSM_CON_Instructions_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Failed to add key.</EN>
      <CH>添加钥匙失败。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Fail9</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Two keys added successfully</EN>
      <CH>两把钥匙添加成功</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_PEPSCon_AddKeyInva_Tip5</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>EDR data is not full, no need to clear.</EN>
      <CH>EDR数据未满，无需进行清除操作。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_RSMClear_Fail1</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Wait timeout!</EN>
      <CH>等待超时！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Common_TimesOut</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Clear collision data successfully!</EN>
      <CH>清除碰撞数据成功！</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_RSMClear_Success</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>Unknown Error</EN>
      <CH>未知错误</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_Common_UnknownError</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>更换完GPF后，将诊断仪连接至车辆OBD接头，插入钥匙并旋转至ON档，发动机不启动。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Tip4</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>清除EEP变量失败，请重试或联系系统管理员</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Fail4</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>需下电等待660S跑完ECU后，再次上电。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Info2</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>切换会话失败，更换GPF失败，请联系系统管理员。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Fail5</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>清除GPF soot负荷值失败，请重试或联系系统管理员</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Fail6</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>清除GPF Ash负荷值失败，请重试或联系系统管理员</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Fail7</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>更换完GPF压差传感器后，将诊断仪连接至车辆OBD接头，插入钥匙并旋转至ON档，发动机不启动。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Tip5</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>GPF压差传感器自学习值重置失败，请下电等待40S后再次上电重测，或联系系统管理员。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Fail8</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>该模块返回值有误，请更换其他GPF压差传感器并重试，或联系系统管理员。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Fail9</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>更换GPF压差传感器成功</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Success3</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>1.请确保现在连接的是旧ECU；\n2.将诊断仪连接至车辆OBD接头，插入钥匙并旋转至ON档，发动机不启动。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Tip6</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>将老ECU中存储的GPF soot值回写到新的ECU中失败，请下电等待40S后再次上电重测，或联系系统管理员</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Fail10</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>将老ECU中存储的GPF ash负荷值回写到新的ECU中失败，请下电等待40S后再次上电重测，或联系系统管理员</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Fail11</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>将老的ECU中存储的压差传感器自学习值回写到新的ECU中失败，请下电等待40S后再次上电重测，或联系系统管理员</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Fail12</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>1.将诊断仪连接至车辆OBD接头，\n2.上电，启动发动机，进入怠速</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Tip7</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>未收到触发GPF再生请求，请重试。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Fail13</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>正在进行服务再生，请等待（若等待超过60分钟未结束，则触发GPF再生失败，请踩刹车中断程序）</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Info3</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>触发GPF再生已完成，请下电至少660S，以确保数据正常存储。</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Success4</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN>
      </EN>
      <CH>请重新上电后，点击“确认”进入下一步</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ReplaceGPF_Info4</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN> Neutral</EN>
      <CH>空挡</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_Name0</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN> 1st</EN>
      <CH>1挡</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_Name1</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN> 2nd</EN>
      <CH>2挡</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_Name2</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN> 3rd</EN>
      <CH>3挡</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_Name3</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN> 4th</EN>
      <CH>4挡</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_Name4</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN> 5th</EN>
      <CH>5挡</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_Name5</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN> 6th</EN>
      <CH>6挡</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_Name6</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
    <Language Tag="English" From=".xml">
      <EN> Reverse</EN>
      <CH>R挡</CH>
      <FL>$Adv_ACU_GearLearning_Name7</FL>
      <MX>
      </MX>
      <TH>
      </TH>
    </Language>
  </Describes>
  <Files>
    <File>Multi.xml</File>
    <File>advance diagnostic phrase.xls</File>
  </Files>
</Root>